Fear of Flying
Hey, Moe, you got change for a 5?
Yeah, sure thing, Lenny.
A snake in the cash register!
Yeah, great prank, fellas. Great.
- Oh, I'm gonna be sick tonight.
- Hey, Moe, you wanna smell my flower?
Do I!
I'm burning up here!
Taking advantage
of my alcohol-soaked clothes.
Oh, it's funny and it makes you think.
I need some coffee before I black out.
Homer, pass me the sugar.
This is gonna be great.
- Oh, there's sugar all over the bar now.
- That's not funny, Homer.
Yeah. We were just messing around,
and you had to go too far.
How many people want Homer
banned from this place for life?
- Yeah!
- Come on, everybody.
This bar is like a tavern to me.
Sorry, Homer. You should've thought of
that before giving me the sugar-me-do.
I'm taking your caricature down
from Mount Lushmore...
...and I'm pulling your favorite song
out of the jukebox.
- "It's Raining Men"?
- Yeah, not no more it ain't.
Joke's on them. I'm still alive.
Cheer up, Homer.
- Can't.
- Okay.
What if you pretended
that this couch were a bar?
Then you could spend more nights
at home with us.
I am not going to dignify that
with an answer.
Look on the bright side, Dad.
Did you know the Chinese
use the same word for crisis...
...as they do for opportunity?
- Yes. "Cris-a-tunity."
You're right. I've been wasting
my life away in that dump for years.
That's it. I'm going to find
a new bar to drink in.
And I'm gonna get drunker
than I've ever been in my entire life.
Bart, where's my wallet?
- Right here, Dad.
- Thank you.
- Wow, classy.
- Good evening, sir.
Would you please leave
without a fuss right now?
Okay.
This looks like a nice, friendly place.
Sammy, you're too old
to go on a date with two twins...
...on the same night you're supposed to
marry Diane without Rebecca knowing.
I'll make you a bet. If this affects my
major-league comeback, I'll sell the bar.
Woody, give me a beer.
I think you've had enough,
Mr. Peterson.
My chiropractor says
I can't carry you home anymore.
Just give me another beer,
you brain-dead hick.
I'll kill you. I'll kill all of you!
Settle down, Normie.
Gotta save those pipes for karaoke.
I love you guys.
Wait a minute.
There's something bothering me
about this place.
I know. This lesbian bar
doesn't have a fire exit!
- Enjoy your deathtrap, ladies.
- What was her problem?
Greetings, good man.
Might I trouble you for a drink?
- Oh, get out of here, Homer.
- Homer? Who is Homer?
My name is Guy Incognito.
Oh, my God.
This man is my exact double.
That dog has a puffy tail!
Here, Puff. Here, Puff.
The last bar in Springfield.
If they don't let me in here,
I'm gonna have to quit drinking.
Shut up, liver!
My liver hurts.
- I'd like a beer, please.
- Sorry, you gotta be a pilot to drink here.
- But I am a pilot.
- Where's your uniform?
I stowed it safely
in the overhead compartment.
- Well, you talk the talk. Here's a loaner.
- We need a pilot, pronto.
- Who wants to fly to the Windy City?
- I'll go! Me! I'm your man!
Conditions are a bit windy.
Well, on second thought,
maybe I'll sit down.
- You.
- But I...
You're not just impersonating
a pilot so you can drink here, are you?
Yeah. That's exactly why I'm here.
You flyboys. You crack me up.
But I keep telling you, I'm not a pilot.
And I keep telling you
you flyboys crack me up!
- Hi, I'm Alan. I'm your copilot.
- Yeah...
As a change of pace...
...I'm gonna let you do most of the
work. I think you're ready for it, Alan.
And I'll just get us started.
We'll need that to live.
If word gets out about this, Crazy Clown
Airlines will be a laughingstock.
In exchange for your silence...
...I'm prepared to offer your family free
tickets to anywhere in the United States.
Excluding Alaska and Hawaii,
the freak states.
Good news, everybody.
Because I endangered lives...
...we can fly anywhere we want.
- Alaska!
- Hawaii!
I don't know, Homer.
We're right in the middle
of the busy housekeeping season.
But, Marge, you deserve a vacation.
It's a chance for you to clean up
after us in a whole other state.
But getting on a plane like that seems
like a hassle coupled with a burden.
Come on, Marge. I wanna shake off
the dust of this one-horse town.
I wanna explore the world. I wanna
watch TV in a different time zone.
I wanna visit strange, exotic malls.
I'm sick of eating hoagies.
I want a grinder, a sub, a footlong hero.
I wanna live, Marge!
Won't you let me live?
Won't you, please?
So, Marge, pretty sweet, eh?
Oh, I forgot to clean
the lint basket in the dryer.
If someone broke into the house
and did laundry, it could start a fire.
Oh, great. I specifically asked
not to be seated next to a baby.
We must be really flying high.
Those people down there
look all tiny and blurry.
Just like the inside of a cataract.
Attention, passengers.
Due to our policy of overselling flights,
this flight has been oversold.
In accordance with FAA rules...
...the first two people to the front
will be upgraded to first class.
Okay, you two.
Come on, Bart,
they're gonna pamper us.
Not literally, of course.
I come for the service...
...but I stay for the legroom.
Flight crew, prepare for takeoff.
I think I'll go get a picture
of the plane taking off.
Marge, what's wrong?
Are you hungry? Sleepy? Gassy?
- Gassy? Is it gas? It's gas, isn't it?
- Homer, I never told you this before...
...but I'm not a good flier.
I have to get off the plane.
Let me off the plane.
I'm asking you nicely
to open the doors.
Take it easy, Marge.
How about if we dope you up real good?
Let me off! Let me off! Let me off!
It's okay, Marge,
we don't need to go on a trip.
We'll just wait for the killer bees
to come to us.
You know, I have this feeling
that we forgot something.
- I'm sure it's nothing.
- Mom, are you feeling any better?
- Yes, but I'd rather not talk about it.
- Permit me to solve the mystery.
Your mother has a fear of flying.
So much for the days when I could say,
"At least my mother's normal."
- Everybody's got a fear of something.
- Not everybody.
- Sock puppets.
- Where?! Where?!
Mom, are you sure
you don't want to discuss it?
Sure as sugar.
Lisa, the important thing is for your
mother to repress what happened...
...push it deep down inside her
so she'll never annoy us again.
If we don't encourage her
to vent her feelings...
...they can come out in other ways.
I just realized we never had
a wedding for the cat and the dog.
They've been living in sin.
Mom, you've been cooking all night?
Judge, jury and executioner
all rolled into one, you are.
See, Dad?
I told you Mom would have problems.
No, no, honey, it's all right.
Really, I'm fine. I'm all right.
Mother always said don't complain.
Be good. Behave. Behave.
Be nice. Smile. Be polite.
Don't make waves.
You heard your mother's ramblings.
She's fine, so behave.
Marge, it's 3 a.m.
- Shouldn't you be baking?
- In a little while.
Mom, can we talk to you?
Can't talk. Keeping myself
in a state of catlike readiness.
Neat.
Anyway, Mom,
maybe you should go into therapy.
No, I don't need therapy.
I'm fine. And it's too expensive.
And I don't believe in it.
It breaks up families.
It turns wives against husbands,
children against fathers...
...neighbors against me.
You don't have to pay some
fancy psychiatrist 10 bucks an hour...
...to get top-notch therapy.
Hello. Radio Psychic.
You will die a terrible, terrible death.
I'm sorry. That was our last caller.
Okay, I'm getting something now.
Okay. You will die
a terrible, terrible death.
- But...
- Thank you for calling Radio Psychic.
- Do you have a song request?
- "It's Raining Men."
Now, Marge, "Dear Abby" says...
...seeing films about air travel
can calm your fears.
Here are some upbeat titles.
Hero. Fearless.
Alive!
No thanks to the plane,
many of us are still...
...alive!
- Alive!
We certainly are.
Pass me another hunk of copilot.
Dad, Mom's getting worse.
You have to take her to see a real
psychiatrist. Look how tense she is.
She's fine.
All right, Lisa, you got your way.
Your mom's going to a psychiatrist.
She's gonna tell Marge to leave me.
It'll break up the family.
You'll have to live with
your grandmother and pick beans.
Dad, I like picking beans
with Grandma.
- Well, keep it up, then.
- Okay, I will.
- Good. You do that.
- Fine.
- You'll be picking many a bean.
- Hope I do.
I don't believe it! Principal Skinner.
Well, well, well.
- I never thought I'd win this easy.
- This has nothing to do with you.
I have many, many issues
with my beloved smother... Mother.
Leave that man alone
with his pain and sit down.
Okay.
All right, how much do you charge?
If money is a problem,
I charge on a sliding scale.
I can go as low as $30 an hour.
- Keep sliding.
- Thirty dollars will be fine.
First, what are your qualifications?
Well...
Oh, no.
I'm not here to take a reading test.
I wanna see some credentials.
I'm sorry, doctor. He's just afraid
you'll blame all my problems on him.
I'm not here to blame anyone.
Marge, therapy can be
an intense process.
We'll go deep into your subconscious...
...and we're not going to stop until we've
exposed the root of your fear of flying.
Don't worry.
This is a private sanctuary...
...where whatever transpires
will be just between us.
Oh, that's just Murray the window
washer. He comes every day at 12:00.
But it's a few seconds before 12:00.
Ever since you started therapy,
all you can do is talk about yourself.
Well, what about me, Marge?
I just left my first session.
I haven't even opened my mouth yet.
You see? You see?
"I just left my first session...
...and I haven't opened
my mouth yet."
Marge, there's no simple explanation
for your fear of flying...
...but it can probably be traced
to some childhood trauma.
Think back.
What's the earliest memory you have
of something bad happening?
That would have to be
my first day of school.
They got this thing called a fire drill.
They use it to drill a flaming hole
in your head.
And there's only one big toilet, and they
make you all go at the same time.
The kids at school were even worse.
You like the Monkees?
You know they don't write
their own songs.
- They do so.
- They don't play their own instruments.
No! No!
That's not even
Michael Nesmith's real hat.
- Kids can be so cruel.
- But it's true.
They didn't write their own songs
or play their own instruments.
The Monkees
weren't about music, Marge.
They were about rebellion,
about political and social upheaval.
- Did you talk about me in therapy today?
- I don't think so.
Tell me the truth!
Don't tell her I raised my voice. Don't.
Happy family. Happy family.
I keep having the same dream.
I'm the mother from Lost in Space.
Ready for breakfast, Dr. Smith?
Oh, being stuck
on this godforsaken planet...
...has vanquished
what little appetite I had.
Warning! Warning!
Dr. Smith refuses to do his astro-chores.
Why, you clattering clank of cogs and...
My dear lady, as you well know,
my back is a disaster area.
D'oh, the pain! D'oh, the pain of it all!
Danger! Danger!
My hooks are flailing wildly.
Wait! Daddy, wait! Please don't leave!
Take me with you!
Marge, are you aware you just said
"Please don't leave" to your daddy?
- No, I didn't.
- Yes, you did.
And you also infringed
on any number of copyrights.
Now, let's talk about your father.
Sure, okay. I'll talk about Father.
Father Christmas. That's what
they call Santa Claus in England.
They drive on the wrong side
of the road there. Now, that's crazy.
People always say how small England is,
but you couldn't fit it all in here.
Not by a long shot.
You know what, I'm cured.
Marge, get back here
and tell me about your father.
- What did he do for a living?
- Okay.
Okay, but you're gonna make
a big deal out of this.
- He was a pilot.
- A pilot? This is a big deal.
You see?
Marge, this may not be
the best time to bring this up...
...but your last check bounced.
- Wait, I'm remembering something.
- Yes, Marge, there's still the matter of...
- I was a little girl...
Goodbye, Margie. Be a good girl, now.
- Why does Daddy have to leave?
- Because he's a pilot.
- He flies all over the world.
- I wanna see Daddy fly.
Margie! No, come back!
Daddy? Daddy, where are you? Dad...?
So who wants preflight cookie?
- Fig Newtons? Hydrox?
- Daddy?
Don't look at me! Don't look at me!
My father was a stewardess.
Marge, there's nothing
to be ashamed of here.
Today male flight attendants,
or stewards, are common.
- They are?
- Yes.
Thanks to trailblazers like your father.
You might say he was a pioneer.
Yeah.
You might even say
he was an American hero.
Let's not go nuts.
The important thing
is that we've pinpointed...
...the precise moment when
you developed your fear of flying.
Wait, some other stuff
is coming back to me.
Open wide.
Here comes the airplane.
This is what a corn field
looks like, honey.
You think those things could also
have contributed to my fear of flying?
- Yes, yes. It's all a rich tapestry.
- Oh, thank you. You've changed my life.
We've really just begun
to scratch the surface.
There's still the serious problem
of your husband.
That's okay. You don't have
to make her into a superwoman.
- She can get on the plane, that's plenty.
- Thank you, doctor.
Whenever the wind whistles
through the leaves...
...I'll think, "Lowenstein. Lowenstein."
- My name is Zweig.
- Lowenstein...
Don't worry about a thing, honey.
I'm gonna help you through this.
Those are all normal noises.
Luggage compartment closing.
Cross-checking.
Just sit back and relax.
That's just the engine powering up.
That's just the engine struggling.
That's just the carp
swimming around your ankles.
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group
[ENGLISH]