Homer the Great
- Looks like you got a leak.
- Could you start fixing it?
The basement is getting awfully flooded.
And I think the cat's down there.
Yeah, I probably won't be able to get
the parts I need for two, three weeks.
And that's if I order them today.
- Which I won't.
- Oh, dear.
Emergency call. Gotta go.
- What should we do until you get back?
- Put a pan down there.
It didn't work.
Lousy traffic jams.
The traffic report will
get me out of this one.
This is Ernie Pie.
We got a little accident that's backing
traffic up as far as this reporter can see.
Hi, Dad.
Hey, how come you guys
got such great parking places?
- It's a secret.
- Shut up.
All right, Econo-Save,
you just made the list.
Hey, will you guys help me fix my...?
Hey, how come you guys
got better chairs than me?
- It's a secret.
- Shut up.
Hey, you guys
wanna go bowling tonight?
- No, we're busy.
- Yeah, we got things to do.
Like what?
It's a secret.
Shut up.
So Lenny and Carl are never
around on Wednesdays.
They don't tell me where they go.
It's like a conspiracy.
A conspiracy, eh? You think they're
involved in the Kennedy assassination?
I do now.
I'm gonna follow them tonight
and see where they go.
Oh, Homer, don't start stalking
people again. It's so illegal.
You stalked Charles Kuralt because
you thought he dug up your garden.
- Well, something did.
- I don't want you stalking anyone.
Oh, okay.
Have it your own way, Marge.
I'll be back in a minute.
I'm going outside...
...to stalk...
...Lenny and Carl...
All I have to do
is follow the yellow-drip road.
- There's our secret meeting place.
- Yes. Let's go inside.
Sounds good.
I can see everything
and they're none the wiser.
- An intruder!
- He will pay the ultimate price.
Yes, the ultimate price.
Get out of here!
I saw weird stuff
in that place last night.
Weird, strange, sick, twisted, eerie,
godless, evil stuff. And I want in.
We don't know what
you're talking about, Homer.
You can't join the Stonecutters.
It's too exclusive.
Oh, well.
That was a real nice
secret organization we had once.
Stonecutters, eh? How do I join?
There are two ways
to gain membership:
- Be the son of a Stonecutter.
- Next.
Or save the life of a Stonecutter.
Hey!
I saved your life. That egg sandwich
could've killed you by cholesterol.
Forget it, Homer. While it has been
established eggs contain cholesterol...
...it has not been proven
that they raise the level...
...of serum cholesterol
in the human bloodstream.
Those Egg Council creeps
got to you too?
Oh, you got it all wrong, Homer.
It's not like that.
You'd better run, egg!
Why don't people like me, Marge?
Everyone likes you.
You're a wonderful person.
Why don't those stupid idiots
let me in their crappy club for jerks?
- I'm sure it's nothing personal, Homer.
- It is.
It's been happening to me all my life.
Hey, Billy, hey, Joey, come on in.
There's plenty of room.
- Sorry. Not you, Homer.
- Why not?
But you let in Homer Glumpet.
It says "no Homers."
We're allowed to have one.
I felt so left out.
- Kids can be so cruel.
- We can? Thanks, Mom.
Cut it out, Bart!
I'd give anything
to get into the Stonecutters.
- What do they do there, Dad?
- I'm a member.
What do they do?
What don't they do?
Oh, they do so many things,
they never stop.
- Oh, the things they do there. My stars.
- You don't know what they do, do you?
- Not as such, no.
- I'm a Stonecutter.
Remember those self-hypnosis classes
we took to help us ignore Grampa?
Do I ever. It's five years later
and I still think I'm a chicken.
- I'm a chicken, Marge.
- I know, I know.
Maybe we should be
listening to him now.
I'm a member!
- What?
You're a member of
the Stonecutters, Grampa?
Oh, sure. Let's see.
I'm an Elk, a Mason, a Communist.
I'm the president of the Gay & Lesbian
Alliance, for some reason.
Here it is. The Stonecutters.
This is it. My ticket in.
They have to let me join
if I'm the son of a member.
I'll take this Communist one too.
Coming through. Can't throw me out.
My father's a member.
- I'm in, I'm in.
- Okay, okay, Homer, you're in.
Just don't point that thing at me.
Thanks, Lenny.
When am I gonna be initiated?
- As soon as Number One gets here.
- Number One?
What kind of stupid
wiener name is that?
"Hello, my name is Number One."
And so forth.
We call each other by number.
Carl is Number 14, I'm Number 12.
Burnsie is Number 29.
- You outrank Mr. Burns here?
- Sure. Watch.
Hey, 29, get over here!
Thank you, sir. May I have another?
Patience, Monty. Climb the ladder.
- Is he the leader?
- Of this chapter.
There are chapters all over the world.
And it has been foretold...
...that someday a Chosen One will...
Okay, okay. I didn't ask
for your life story.
Let the initiation begin.
All Stonecutters must take
the Leap of Faith.
If you survive this five-story plunge,
your character will be proven.
Happy landings!
I think I have to do it again.
My blindfold came off.
This ritual is called
Crossing the Desert.
And this we call the Unblinking Eye.
Hey, have you ever noticed
that the Crossing the Desert...
...is a lot like the Unblinking Eye?
And exactly like
the Wreck of the Hesperus.
And now the final ordeal:
The Paddling of the Swollen Ass,
with paddles.
And by the sacred parchment,
I swear that if I reveal the secrets...
...of the Stonecutters,
may my stomach become bloated...
...and my head be plucked
of all but three hairs.
He should have to take
a different oath.
Everyone takes the same oath.
Welcome to the club, Number 908.
You have joined the Sacred Order
of the Stonecutters...
...who since ancient times
have split the rocks of ignorance...
...that obscure the light
of knowledge and truth.
Now let's all get drunk
and play Ping-Pong.
He's already kind of heavy,
you know, and...
Well, to be honest, I never got around
to ordering that part for you.
So it's still gonna be
a couple of weeks.
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
- Really?
- Yes. Yes.
But what if I were to shake your hand
in this way?
Well, I didn't realize
you were a member.
So long, suckers.
- Same old space, huh, Dad?
- Yep.
But they gave me these Rollerblades
so I can glide to the front door.
Sweet.
- Jealous?
- Well, no. We've got the same chair.
You're jealous.
- Your membership pack.
- What's this?
You put that on your car
so you won't get any tickets.
This keeps paramedics
from stealing your wallet.
Oh, and don't bother calling 911
anymore. Here's the real number.
I still don't believe all the
Founding Fathers were Stonecutters.
That's because you trust
your stupid schoolbooks.
Here's what really happened
at the signing...
...of the Declaration of Independence.
And a nation is born.
Now let us party like 'twere 1799!
Quaff! Quaff! Quaff!
Please, sir. You're destroying
my establishment.
We just created the greatest democracy
on earth, lowlife commoner! Get out!
Wanna see how Davy Crockett really
died at the Alamo? You must be 18.
Homer, a man who called himself
"you know who"...
...just invited you to a secret
"wink-wink" at the "you know what."
Sure are popular
now that you're a Stonecutter.
Oh, yeah. Beer busts, beer blasts,
keggers, stein hoist...
...AA meetings, beer night.
It's wonderful, Marge. I've never
felt so accepted in all my life.
These people look
deep within my soul...
...and assign me a number
based on the order in which I joined.
Who controls the British crown?
Who keeps the metric system down?
We do
Who leaves Atlantis off the maps?
Who keeps the Martians under wraps?
We do
Who holds back the electric car?
Who makes Steve Guttenberg a star?
We do
Who robs cavefish of their sight?
Who rigs every Oscar night?
We do
Thank you. Tonight we are here...
...to commemorate our glorious
society's 1500th anniversary.
And in honor of this
momentous occasion...
...we're having ribs.
- Yeah!
I need a bib. If I slop any on my shirt,
I could lose the respect of my brethren.
So let us rejoice and enjoy our meal...
...in the shadow of the hallowed
sacred parchment.
- Homer.
- Oh, yeah. Thanks, Lenny.
This is just appalling and outrageous.
What? Did I miss something?
Oh, God!
No, Homer, no! This is outrageous!
You can't do that!
- No!
- You really are stupid.
And the official Stonecutter
underwear too.
Please don't kick me out.
This society's everything to me.
Please give me another chance.
I've learned my lesson!
That's it!
- How can we punish him further?
- Oh, sorry.
Homer Simpson, for your continuing
and baffling desecration...
...of our beloved sacred parchment...
...you are hereby banished
from the Stonecutters forever.
And as a final humiliation,
you must walk home naked...
...dragging behind you
the Stone of Shame.
The mark!
Oh, that. It's just a birthmark.
And I'll thank you not to stare.
He's the Chosen One.
You are the Chosen One...
...whom the sacred parchment
prophesied would lead us to glory.
Now to the top of Mount Springfield
for the coronation.
Remove the Stone of Shame.
Attach the Stone of Triumph!
Mental note: Don't overdo this.
Peekaboo!
I always wondered
if there was a God.
And now I know.
There is, and it's me.
- You're not a god, Homer.
- Remember, Dad, all glory is fleeting.
- So?
- Beware the Ides of March.
- No.
- I know you're happy now...
...but it won't last forever.
- Everything lasts forever.
Getting what you want all the time
will leave you unfulfilled and joyless.
Remove the girl.
You're not with your Stonecutters. There
are no lackeys around to carry out your...
Another strike for the Chosen One!
Hurrah!
That's just an excellent break.
- Oh, most assuredly.
- Absolutely.
- I'm out.
- No, no, no. Homer...
...you have a royal sampler.
Oh, I win again, don't I?
- Good one.
- Nice hand, Chosen One.
You know, I think you guys
are letting me win.
No! No! No!
From now on I want you
to be honest with me.
I mean, I'm not perfect, right?
- Yeah.
- Well...
Run.
The grand exalted leader
requests a moment of your time.
Class dismissed.
Lisa, you were right.
My happiness is fading.
You're experiencing spiritual emptiness
because your power has isolated you...
...from other human beings.
- What do you mean, isolated?
Well, maybe you could reach out to
the community and help other people.
I could help others.
I'll get a bunch of monkeys, dress them
up and make them reenact the Civil War.
Dad, that doesn't help people.
Couldn't hurt. Unless the monkeys
started hurting people.
Which they almost certainly would.
Brothers. Brothers!
Brothers, I've learned
a wonderful lesson.
Helping others makes our own lives
better and makes us better people.
So instead of just shooting pool
and drinking beer...
...let us Stonecutters use what we have
to help the less fortunate.
He's gone mad with power,
like that Albert Schweitzer guy.
Oh, for the love of God!
Somebody get the Jaws of Life!
Higher! Higher!
Oh, I'll give you higher,
my filthy little urchin.
You've won this round.
Oh, thank you, Mr. Simpson.
It looks so much better.
A beautiful sky blue.
You were right, Lisa.
I've never felt so spiritually fulfilled.
And with my brothers
the Stonecutters behind me...
...this is the beginning
of a better world for all of us.
- We gotta kill him!
- Take it easy, Moe.
Let's hear from the Stonecutter World
Council before we act too rashly.
- Kill him.
- Kill the fool!
- Afraid I have to disagree...
...with Orville, Jack and Mister. Can't
we just do something to his voice box?
We might as well face the truth.
As long as we're Stonecutters,
he will control our lives.
Maybe. But maybe we don't
wanna be Stonecutters no more.
This is much better than
the old Stonecutter hall.
Silence. I now call to order
the first meeting...
...of the ancient, mystic society of...
...No Homers.
Hey, fellas. Can I join?
Sorry. No Homers.
Loyal Stonecutters...
...let us begin our reenactment
of the Battle of Gettysburg.
Homer, you can't just keep hanging out
with these Colobus monkeys.
Somebody's gonna get parasites.
Oh, Marge, kids, I miss my club.
Oh, Homie.
You know, you are a member
of a very exclusive club.
- The Black Panthers?
- No, the family Simpson...
...which has just five members.
And only two of those members
have special rings.
- Yeah!
I meant our wedding rings!
You know, Marge, you're right.
The Simpson family is the best
possible club I could belong to.
This club better be worth it.
All right, all right, it's Lisa's turn.
Who controls the British crown?
Who keeps the metric system down?
We do
Who keeps Atlantis off the maps?
Who keeps the Martians under wraps?
We do
Who holds back the electric car?
Who makes Steve Guttenberg a star?
We do
Who robs cavefish of their sight?
Who rigs every Oscar night?
We do
Shut up.
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group
[ENGLISH]