Grampa vs. Sexual Inadequacy
We now return to the 1971 film...
...Goodtime Slim, Uncle Doobie,
and the Great Frisco FreakOut...
...starring Troy McClure.
Slim, if we've got the bag
with the stolen diamonds...
...then what happened to the bag
with our stash?
There's more than one way
to get high, baby.
Please, Marge. How often
can I see a movie of this caliber...
...on late night TV?
- Is there something wrong, Homie?
It's just that I've only seen this
twice before...
...and I've seen you every night
for the last 11 ye...
What I meant to say is,
we'll snuggle tomorrow, sweetie.
I promise.
Enchiladas.
Mom! Dad!
Don't turn on the light!
There's a UFO outside my window.
Seriously.
Oh, Bart, it's just an old golf umbrella
stuck in a tree.
Can I sleep in there
with you guys tonight?
- No.
- Can I sit on the roof...
...with a baseball bat
in case a UFO comes?
Yes, that's fine. Good, good.
I hope you kept
the Homie fires burning.
- Homer! Homer, wake up. Wake up.
- What?
We need to talk about the marital
difficulties we've been having lately.
Marge, there's just too much pressure.
What with my job, the kids,
traffic snarls...
...political strife at home and abroad.
But I promise you the second all those
things go away, we'll have sex.
I simply can't wait that long.
Maybe we should get some help.
- How about a book?
- Okay.
A tasteful book.
Oh, all right.
Hey, Marge, this guy looks like Apu!
I don't want people to see us
looking at these books.
What you looking at?
I'm just reading up on artillery.
Yes, and I'm pursuing my interest in...
This one's a good choice
and it's not smutty.
It's a book on tape by Paul Harvey.
That Midwestern man on the radio
who's like a pleasant version of Grampa.
Mr. And Mrs. Erotic American.
Mom, Dad, look!
This biography of Peter Uebberoth
is only 99 cents.
- And I found the new Al Gore book.
- Sane Planning, Sensible Tomorrow.
I hope it's as exciting
as his other book:
Rational Thinking,
Reasonable Future.
I'm getting this book on UFOs.
Did you know they're real?
But there's a conspiracy
to cover it up.
Oh, that's just a paranoid fantasy.
Mr. Vice President, someone finally
bought a copy of your book.
Well, this calls for a celebration.
Celebrate good times
Come on!
I will.
Hello, Americans. Paul Harvey here.
Did you know every good American
is at heart an erotic American?
It's true.
A famous couple...
I don 't need to tell you it was
Dwight and Mamie Eisenhower.
- Offered this advice:
"Double your pleasure with a bath...
...together."
Homie, I can't quite fit.
The faucet's jammed into my back.
I'm stuck.
So am I.
- Kids?
A romantic vacation
can provide titillation.
Sensual, sanitary seclusion
awaits you at any of America 's fine...
...AAA-approved motor lodges.
The Arabian Nights Room looks nice.
The Pharaoh's Chamber
has a vibrating sarcophagus.
Sorry there, Fred and Ethel.
Should have made a reservation.
We only got one room left.
The toilet is overflowing
in the Caveman Room.
Oh, here we are. The Utility Room.
This isn't very erotic.
I think it's an actual utility room.
No, honey. It's a romantic fantasy.
I imagine I'm the janitor, and you're...
...the janitor's wife, who has to
live with me in the utility room.
Don't mind me, folks.
Just need to get the old wet-dry vac.
By now, your new improved love life
should have you flinging woo...
...like nobody's business.
So to you,
Mr. And Mrs. Erotic American, I bid...
...good day.
Welcome home, son. I broke two lamps
and lost all your mail.
- What's wrong with your wife?
- You wouldn't understand.
- Flu?
- No.
- Protein deficiency?
Pneumonoultramicroscopic-
silicovolcanoconiosis?
- No.
- Unsatisfying sex life?
N... Yes! But please,
don't you say that word.
What? Sex?
What's so unappealing
about hearing your elderly father...
...talk about sex?
I had sex.
You're home safe. See you
the next time we need your signature.
Oh, you never wanna spend
any time with me.
But I can help you
with your loving problem.
I got a home remedy that'll put
the dowsers back in your trousers.
Legend has it my great grandpappy
stumbled upon this recipe...
...when he was trying to invent
a cheap substitute for holy water.
Here you g... Hey!
Here you go, you ingrate!
Think of me when you're having
the best sex of your life.
Drink it!
Here's $50. Go to the movies,
then take a cab to your aunt's.
Stay there. Call you later.
Now, now, now.
- Homie, what's...?
- Marge, I'll explain to you afterwards.
What do you think Mom and Dad
are doing?
I don't know.
Here he is, Rex Harrison
and Paul Anka rolled into one.
That tonic really works.
You and Grampa should bottle it
and go into business together.
You want me to spend
more time with Dad?
What about my New Year's resolution?
You can make a lot of money.
Yeah. Where are my pants?
You threw them out the window.
You said you'd never
need them again.
Oh, hurry, Neddie. They're awful.
You just be ready
with that garbage bag.
Oh, mama!
This is finally really happening.
After years of disappointment
with get-rich-quick schemes...
...I know I'm gonna get rich
with this scheme.
And quick.
Sir? Hello, sir. Yes.
You look like a man who needs help
satisfying his wife. So...
I guess people have some sort
of moral objection to our sex drug.
Let me sell it, you idiot.
Step right up and witness
the magnificent medicinal miracle...
...of Simpson & Son's
patented Revitalizing Tonic!
Put some ardor in your larder
with our energizing, moisturizing...
...tantalizing, romanticizing, surprising,
"her-prising," revitalizing tonic!
I doubt very highly that one elixir can
boast so many fantastic properties.
What say we amscray out
of here and have a wild wingding...
...at the cyclotron, doctor.
Anything you say, professor.
Tonight, we'll push
the twin beds together.
And I found something for Milhouse
down at the mall too. A pup tent.
Oh, boy!
Now I can sleep out in the yard!
Yeah! Every single night.
I've discovered that
the rejuvenating effect...
...is actually a mild form of poisoning.
No doubt a result
of the unsanitary conditions...
...in Grampa Simpson's bathtub.
Nonetheless...
What's going on?
Where are all the grownups?
Who cares?
With no adults around, I run this city.
Carry on.
Listen to this.
"Unexplainable behavior.
Individuals acting
in a secretive fashion...
...are often involved with UFOs
or other paranormal phenomena...
...e.g. Telephone explosions."
Jeez! If it's in a book,
it's gotta be true.
Scary, no? And this guy is head
of the Spaceology Department...
...at the Correspondence College
of Tampa.
Will you cook my dinner for me?
My parents aren't around and
I'm not allowed to turn on the stove.
Hurry up. We got a lot of tonic to sell
and a lot of towns to visit.
Frigid Falls, Mount Seldom,
Lake Flaccid.
Great. I'm gonna be stuck in a car
all weekend with that wheezy windbag.
And that's what's wrong
with Bart's generation.
Now as for your generation...
And for the minimal outlay
of one dollar...
...you can take home a bottle
of liquid Lothario...
...distilled Don Juan,
catalytically carbonated Casanova.
Lock old Rover in the shed,
because man has a new best friend...
...in Simpson & Son's
Revitalizing Tonic.
I'm not convinced.
I've had bad luck with aphrodisiacs.
All questions will be answered,
all fears will be allayed...
...with one incontrovertible
demonstration.
May I have a volunteer
from the audience?
Yes, you, sir.
You've never seen me before,
is that correct?
That is correct.
Well, then how come his face
is on the bottle?
You're the worst shill ever!
You're a disgrace
to the medicine show business.
They didn't start chasing us until
you turned on that getaway music.
Okay. It's now painfully clear.
The adults are definitely paving the way
for an invasion by the saucer people.
You fool. Can't you see
it's a massive government conspiracy?
Or have they gotten to you too?
Hey, hey, hey! Stop it! Stop it!
Why are you guys jumping
to such ridiculous conclusions?
Haven't you ever heard
of Ockham's razor?
The simplest explanation
is probably the correct one.
- So, what's the simplest explanation?
- I don't know.
Maybe they're all reverse vampires
and they have to get home before dark.
- Reverse vampires!
- Vampires! The undead!
Hey, wait a minute.
That's Amos Pierson's moose farm.
Make a right here.
Why are we stopping at this dump?
That's the house you grew up in, son.
Let's go find
that hot dog tree I planted.
Yeah, we lived here
till the bank foreclosed in '63.
Farm went bust after the cows
started giving sour milk.
Something must've
spooked them good.
Stupid cows!
Oh, memories.
If this old place could talk, it'd say...
There she is. The old Radiation King.
You'd park yourself right there
and watch for hours on end.
If I may, Helen,
I'd like to respond to that question...
...with yet another flip remark.
Look at me, Mom.
I am President Kennedy.
Oh, Abe, maybe our Homer
could grow up to be president someday.
You, president?
This is the greatest country in the world.
We've got a system set up
to keep people like you...
...from ever becoming president.
Quit your daydreaming, melonhead.
Dad, how come you never gave me
any encouragement?
Maybe I could've been
something more than I am.
Like a travel agent...
...to a great scientist.
Or the inventor
of a hilarious refrigerator alarm.
Who are you to complain?
You lock me up in a home...
...and give me the same damn
shower safety seat every Christmas.
Your whole life,
you never said one nice thing to me.
That's because you're a screwup.
- You're the screwup!
- Why, you little...
All right.
All right, that's it.
We're going home.
I'm sick of you and your stupid tonic.
If I hadn't taken that stupid tonic
38 years ago...
...you'd have never been born
and I'd have been happy.
You were an accident!
Get out.
- I'm sorry I said that.
- Out.
I'm gonna get out of the car.
And I hope you'll find it in your heart
not to drive awa...
Well, I'll be all right as long
as I can remember my Army training.
Dang.
I'm sorry.
Hi?
Homie, are you really going to
ignore Grampa for the rest of your life?
Of course not, Marge.
Just for the rest of his life.
He said I was an accident.
He didn't wanna have me.
You didn't wanna have Bart.
You're never supposed
to tell the child.
You tell Bart all the time.
But when I do it, it's cute.
So finally, we're all in agreement
about what's going on with the adults.
- Milhouse.
- Okay, here's what we've got.
The Rand Corporation...
...in conjunction with the saucer people...
- Thank you.
...under the supervision
of the reverse vampires...
...are forcing our parents
to go to bed early...
...in a fiendish plot
to eliminate the meal of dinner.
We're through
the looking glass here, people.
Kids, your daddy and his daddy
are involved in a very sticky...
...nutty, chewy, chocolatey...
Put it away, boy! ...situation.
And your daddy has realized
something very important.
A father should always make
his kids feel wanted.
Starting now, I promise to spend
more time with you...
...and give you the attention
you deserve.
I can't breathe.
And feast your ears
on this tantalizing testimonial...
...from my own flesh and blood.
The son who puts the fun
in Simpson & Son...
...my son, Barney.
I used to be a fat, disgusting slob.
That medicine seems to be
giving your son a lot of gas.
I assure you his belching is the result
of an unrelated alcohol problem.
It just ain't the same without Homer.
He knew how to drive a car.
Son. My dear son.
From now on, I'm going to be
a good and attentive father.
And for starters, your old man
is gonna teach you how to ride...
...your very first bike.
Dad, number one:
I know how to ride a bike.
Number two: I already own a bike.
And number three: That is a girl's bike.
You're no girl, you're a boy.
A good boy. You can be president.
- Scratch that. You will be president!
- Dad!
I think Lisa needs another push
on her new tire swing.
No, Dad. I wanna get down.
This tire is filthy
and the steel belts are poking me.
No! No!
No offense, but your half-assed
under-parenting was a lot more fun...
...than your half-assed over-parenting.
But I'm using my whole ass.
Dad, it's just that too much
of your love can really be...
...scary.
Someday you'll thank me
for all this scary love.
But now I've gotta go somewhere
and do some serious thinking.
- I'm sure he meant to say "drinking."
- That's what I assumed.
Here's where it all started
to go wrong.
How am I supposed to be a good dad
when I never had one myself?
Oh, Dad wasn't even around
on Christmas morning...
...when I actually got to meet
Santa Claus.
Some father.
Wait a minute...
Dad!
This photo is a blessing.
It eases my pain.
This tonic's caused me nothing
but trouble.
You've done all the damage
you're gonna do.
Oh, nuts!
- Dad!
- Son!
I'm a screwup.
I burned down our house.
No. I'm a screwup.
- You know what?
- What?
- We're both screwups.
- It doesn't matter.
What matters is you were right
when you told me...
...I never said anything nice about you.
So are you gonna say
something nice now?
I hadn't thought that far ahead.
Okay, here it goes.
I'm not sorry I had you, son.
And I was always proud...
...that you weren't a short man.
Oh, Dad.
What do you say
we roll on the grass, son?
I'm with you, Dad.
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group
[ENGLISH]