BART'S GIRLFRIEND
Remember, Bart...
I mean, Dances in Underwear.
- We take the white man alive.
All right, Thinks Too Much.
It shall be so.
Keep your eyes peeled for Injuns.
I mean, Native Americans.
They're after us because we gave them
blankets infected with cooties.
I ate all my caps.
Throw down your weapons
and kiss the prairie, cow dorks!
Why do we have to play
this corny old game anyway?
I brought my jacks!
I got twosies!
That's not fair, Nelson. They didn't have
the Killmatic 3000 back then.
Hey, records from that era
are spotty at best.
Bart! Lisa! Time for church!
Milhouse, time for church!
Shlomo, time for your violin lesson!
Why the crap do we have
to go church anyway?
You just answered your own question
with that commode mouth.
Besides, you kids need to learn
morals and decency...
...and how to love your fellow man.
And with flaming swords, the Aramites
did pierce the eyes of their fellow men...
...and did feast on what flowed forth.
Among whom also we all
once conducted ourselves...
...in the lusts of our flesh...
I'm a troll man
I don't want you playing with something
that has such bizarre hair.
Awful, awful hair.
And now my daughter, Jessica...
...who has just returned
from boarding school...
...will read the same passage
I just read.
I noticed a few of you
weren't paying attention.
Wow, there is a God.
I'm telling you, the light would
work better if it pointed out to sea!
Shut up, I know what I'm doing.
I hate the sea and everything in it.
Bye. Bye-bye. Bye-bye.
Thank you for choosing our church.
I've never felt this way
about a girl before.
My long search is finally over.
Hi, I'm Bart Simpson.
I was incredibly moved by your reading.
I don't think God's words
have ever sounded so plausible.
Thanks, Art.
I have to go over here now.
Don't be so hard on yourself, Bart.
It's not your fault Jessica
doesn't like you.
Is it my hair? My overbite?
The fact that I've worn the same clothes
for the last four years?
No, Bart. I just think you and Jessica
are too different to get along.
She's a sweet, kind reverend's daughter,
and you're the devil's cabana boy.
Good. Very good.
Ralph, Jesus did not have wheels.
- Bart Simpson?
- Yes, ma'am.
I'd like to return to your wonderful
Sunday school, please.
But, Bart, we banned you
from Sunday school.
You were happy. We were happy.
Everybody was happy.
Particularly the hamster.
I've changed my ways.
Please give me
another chance, ma'am.
All right, Bart.
The Bible does teach forgiveness.
Class, I want you to welcome back
our prodigal son.
- What?
- What's prodigal mean?
Oh, dear.
You know, the great thing about
Sunday school...
...is we're finally learning
something we can use.
Yeah, so true.
I have to turn my chair this way now.
Somehow I gotta convince her
I'm a good person.
All right, I have to sit here and behave,
no matter what.
Okay, class. We have a special
treat today for pass-around.
A replica of the slingshot
David used to slay Goliath.
While you kids are looking at that,
I'll just busy myself in this file cabinet.
Must fight Satan.
Make it up to him...
...later.
You know, I was considering
staying after school...
...and helping teacher clean up.
Do you ever think anything
you don't say?
There is just no pleasing
a girl like that!
All that unnecessary behaving.
I'm all tense through the chestal area.
I need relief.
Now, the kilt was only
for day-to-day wear.
In battle, we donned a full-length
ball gown covered in sequins.
The idea was to blind
your opponent with luxury.
'Tis no more than what God gave me,
you Puritan pukes.
That'll hold me, at least till I get
my hands on some kind of explosives.
Congratulations, Simpson.
You just fell for our sting and won
yourself three months' detention.
There's no such thing
as Scotchtoberfest!
There's not? You used me, Skinner!
You used me!
Three months?
Hi, Bart.
I saw the way they set you up.
That was really unfair.
Wanna have dinner
at my house tonight?
Really? Sure.
Great. We eat at 7.
There's only one thing to do
at a moment like this:
Strut.
I can't believe my little boy
is already going on his first date.
Oh, that's sweet, Homer.
Our son is growing up, isn't he?
No, it's not that. Didn't you hear?
They have no bananas.
They have no bananas today.
So, Bart, how's school going?
Jessica always gets straight A's.
Well, in my family,
grades aren't that important.
It's what you learn that counts.
Six times five! What is it?
Actually, numbers don't have
much use in my future career:
Olympic gold-medal rocket-sled champ!
I didn't know the rocket sled
was an Olympic event.
Well, no offense, but what you
don't know could fill a warehouse.
Young man, explain yourself!
Sorry. I have kind of a short fuse,
which some find charming.
Speaking of charming,
watching Fox last night...
...I heard a rather amusing story.
This character named Martin
was feeling rather randy...
...and he was heard to remark...
And don't you ever come near
my daughter again!
Never have I heard such
gratuitous use of the word "butt"!
- But... But... But...
- Make him stop!
You're bad, Bart Simpson.
No, I'm not. I'm really...
Yes, you are. You're bad.
And I like it.
I'm bad to the bone, honey.
- Let's go find some fun.
- But your father said...
I told the rev I was going
to my room to say my prayers.
Smart, beautiful and a liar.
So much better than that
Sarah, plain and tall.
Right there! Put that there!
Excellent! You're incredible, Jessica.
Your throws, your catches,
your spirals, your loops.
It's like the toilet paper
is an extension of your body.
No way would a minister's daughter
go out with you.
Oh, yeah? I'll prove it.
- Hey, Jessica.
- Yes?
- Am I supposed to know you?
- Jessica, we just...
That's for besmirching
an innocent girl's name.
- Why?
- I'm sorry, Bart.
You know my parents
can't find out about us.
And besides, if it's secret,
it's even more exciting.
- I guess.
- Hey, you wanna go skateboarding?
Actually, I was hoping I could
sit down for just a second.
Come on, it'll be fun.
Now I have the energy to do anything.
Just give me two minutes.
Jessica, I think this is too steep.
Bart, you can't trust your perception
at this altitude.
Actually, if the road surface
maintains its integrity...
...I just might be able to hold on.
The glue will slow me down.
- Any glue leaking?
- No. That glue ain't going nowhere.
Nothing's ever gonna stop me.
Oh, no. There goes the glue after all.
Fun, huh?
Have you noticed any change in Bart?
- New glasses?
- No.
He looks like something
might be disturbing him.
Probably misses his old glasses.
I guess we could get more involved
in Bart's activities.
But then I'd be afraid
of smothering him.
- Yeah. And then we'd get the chair.
- That's not what I meant.
It was, Marge. Admit it.
- Hi.
- We should get to class.
- What's the hurry?
- We could get in trouble for being late.
You worry too much.
Come on. If you stay here a while,
I'll let you hold my hand.
Teamwork! Come on, Bart.
If I don't save the wee turtles,
who will?
Save me from the wee turtles!
They were too quick for me!
I can't believe it, Bart.
I'd always thought Jessica
was so sweet.
She's like a Milk Dud, Lis:
Sweet on the outside,
poison on the inside.
- You gotta give her up.
- No, no, wait. Hear my plan.
Put up with her for seven more years.
Then we'll get married.
Once the first baby comes, she's bound
to settle down and treat me right.
After all, I deserve it.
Bart, it's naive to think
you can change a person.
Except maybe that boy
who works in the library.
Do you have Go, Dog, Go?
That's in Juvenile.
This is Young Adult.
Well-read and just a little wild.
If only someone could tame him.
You're right, Lisa.
Love isn't about fixing someone.
I'm just gonna give her up cold turkey.
I'm not gonna talk to her or see her.
It's over.
Thanks for the advice, sis.
There. If I can just get through
this many days without seeing her...
...she should be completely
out of my system.
Okay, day one.
Time for church, Bart.
I bet your little friend Jessica
will be there.
- Jessica.
- Bart, be strong.
You don't need that little hellcat.
Oh, Lis, she's already
drawn me to her...
...with her beautiful siren song.
That's very disturbing.
Hey, Bart. What? What's wrong?
Well, Jessica, I don't think we should
hang out together anymore.
You're turning me into a criminal
when all I want to be is a petty thug.
Oh, good.
Here comes the collection plate.
"Thirty cents off Shake ’N' Bake."
- Homer!
- We can spare it, Marge.
We've been blessed.
You're right about everything, Bart.
I have been too reckless.
From now on,
I am going to settle down.
Jessica, what are you doing?
Well, it takes money
to start a new life.
Stealing from the collection basket
is really wrong. Even I know that.
Fine. You just lost your cut.
I'll just take that.
Everyone turn around and look at this.
What is it? A Unitarian?
Now just relax. For once,
you didn't do anything wrong.
Just explain yourself
and everyone will understand.
- L...
- Took the money? Yes, we know.
- He confessed!
- Okay.
Stop him!
He's headed for the window!
Son, if you look me in the eye and say
you didn't take the collection money...
...that's all I need.
- I didn't take it.
- Why, you little...
How can you lie like that?
Homer, stop that! I believe him.
Tell me, if he didn't take the money,
why is he wearing those fancy clothes?
That's what he wore to church.
How convenient.
Bart, honey, do you know
who did take the money?
- No.
- See, son?
Telling the truth isn't so bad.
- Boo!
- Why, you little...!
- Crook!
- Thief!
- Stealer of money from the church!
We've gotta talk.
Listen, thanks for not turning me in.
That was sweet.
Well, it seems like if you really
care for me, you should come forward.
Don't you see? It's because I care
for you that I can't come forward.
That doesn't make any sense.
Then I just don't feel like it, okay?
Jessica, you're really beautiful,
but you are not very nice.
With the way you treat me,
why should I protect you?
Because if you tell,
no one will believe you.
Remember, I'm the sweet,
perfect minister's daughter.
And you're just yellow trash.
So here's where you're hiding.
This is my only refuge from the taunts
and accusations of the townspeople.
Thief.
Bart, we can't just let her
get away with this!
Give it up, Lis.
She's a criminal mastermind.
She's got a 108 IQ,
she reads at a fifth-grade level.
And her hair smells
like red Froot Loops.
Yeah? Well, I eat Froot Loops
for breakfast.
Because of last week's problems...
...we'll be taking certain precautions
with this week's collection.
We shouldn't have let them do this.
It can't be helping his self-esteem.
Now for our offertory reading,
Lisa Simpson...
...who we'll all be keeping an eye on.
I know most of you have already judged
my brother guilty without any proof.
But doesn't the Bible teach us
"judge not, lest ye be judged," Reverend?
I think it may be somewhere
towards the back.
There is someone among us
with a guilty conscience.
After much soul-searching, I decided
it would be wrong of me to name names.
But I urge that guilty person here,
under the eyes of God...
...to come forward, to confess...
...and save yourself from the torment
of your own personal hell!
I smelled some marijuana smoke
in Vietnam!
I was the one that canceled Star Trek!
I left my Porsche keys
inside Mrs. Glick.
I am talking to
the collection-money thief!
Only you can come forward
and end this injustice!
Oh, what the heck.
It was Jessica Lovejoy!
If you search her room,
I am certain you will find the money.
- To the little girl's room!
- Yeah!
That's the collection money!
Oh, yeah. Smells like church.
I guess it's obvious
what's happened here.
Bart Simpson has somehow managed
to sneak his bedroom into my house.
Well, come on! Use your imaginations!
No, Dad. I did it.
It's your classic cry for attention.
Well, young lady, I suppose
we brought you home...
...from boarding school
a little prematurely.
I was expelled, Dad.
Remember the pipe bomb?
The glee club brawl?
Remember the school chapel
collection plate?
The exploding toilets ring a bell?
Come on, Dad, pay attention to me!
Hello, in there. Hello?
I think you all owe my son an apology.
- Very sorry.
- That's okay. Appreciate it.
- Hi, Jessica.
- Hi, Bart.
Come to watch me suffer?
I just wanted to let you know that even
though this was a difficult experience...
...I really learned a lot.
I'm a little wiser
and a little less naive.
Well, I learned that I can make men
do whatever I want.
Well, don't you see, Jessica?
Then you really haven't learned...
Would you finish scrubbing these steps?
Will I?
Hey, Jessica!
Coming!
Poor sucker. It's amazing what
some guys will do for a pretty face.
Not me though.
Wait till she sees the second-rate job
I do on these stairs.
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group
[ENGLISH]