[ Chorus ]
# The Simpsons #
[ Bell Ringing ]
[ Whistle Blowing ]
[ Beeping ]
## [Jazzy Solo ]
[ Tires Screeching ]
D'oh!
[ Screams ]
[ Groans, Gasps ]
[ Alarm Blaring ]
Fire! Fire! Fire!
[ Gasps ]
Oh, no! What do I save?
[ Screeches ]
Trophies, trophies.
Oh- Ooh! Attendance.
Don't panic! Don't panic!
Don't panic!
Get in. Move it.
This is not a drill.
Good work, everyone.
We're sure to be first in line for Duff Days.
You set off the smoke alarm
to rush us to a beer festival?
[ Chuckles ]
I know. I'm a character.
Now, a little beer music
to get in the mood.
- ##[ Rolka ]
- [ Both Gasp ]
Looking for these?
## [ Humming ]
- ##[ Stops ]
- [ Both Sigh ]
## [ Polka ]
Drink Duff...
[ Softly ] responsibly.
Drink Duff... [ Softly ]
responsibly.
- Now, which one of you is our designated driver?
- [ Homer Grunting ]
- Twist off, damn it!
- [ Moaning ]
I guess I'll be driving.
Right this way to the Duff
Designated Drivers' Rockin' Fun Zone.
Rockin' Fun Zone?
That sounds fun.
I don't see the need
for razor wire.
Ooh, there's Ulysses S. Grant,
Babe Ruth-
[ Gasps ]
Ben Franklin.
Early to bed. [ Hiccups ]
Early to rise.
Ya think-Ya think
you're better than me? Huh?
[ Groans ]
Okay, kids, who wants to see
what it's like to get drunk?
[ All Shouting ]
[ All Moan ]
[ Screaming ]
Now you're charming.
You don't know me.
[ Moaning ]
This guy here, this is the guy.
[ Laughing, Moans ]
[ Man ]
All right, Springfield...
belly up for the Duff Beer-tender
of the year contest.
Now, fresh from his appearance before the House
Subcommittee on Teenage Alcoholism...
- ##[ Dance Rock ]
- Duff Man!
Are you ready
for some Duff love?
- [ Cheering ]
- All right!
Today, we're gonna find out
which of these bartenders...
- has the right stuff to dispense Duff?
- ##[ Dance Rock ]
From the Green Potato Pub
at O'Hare International Airport...
- Michael Finn.
- [ Cheering ]
From Juggernauts
in Hollywood, California, Titania.
[ Cheering ]
And now, the local lug who fills
your mug with the drug you chug-
oh,yeah-
give it up for Moe Szyslak.
Hello, Springfield.
How ya-
- [ Moaning ]
- [ Cheering ]
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Okay, our first event
qualifies for course credit...
at Dartmouth College-
Trick Pouring.
[ Man ]
#For goodness sake #
#I got the hippy, hippy shakes #
# Yeah, I got the shakes ##
[ Carl Chuckles ]
That spells ''Duff.''
Go, Moe!
Boo, everyone else.
I think we know
who wins this round.
- Titania!
- [ Cheering ]
Duff Beer is brewed
from hops, barley...
and sparkling clear mountain what?
- [ Bell Dings ]
- Goat.
- Uh, close enough!
- [ Cheering ]
[ Sighs ]
You can really taste the goat.
making the previous rounds
a complete waste.
- ##[ Dance Rock ]
- [ Cheering ]
Don't forget. Today's winner will be
immortalized on our new Duff calendar.
All right, guys, one, two, three.
Moo? Lenny, you were
supposed to be ''E.''
See what happens
when you skip rehearsal.
##[ Fanfare]
All right, bartenders,
toss your drunks.
- [ Grunts ] And stay out!
- [ Cheering ]
- [ Moaning ]
- Ew!
You said if I slept with you,
I wouldn't have to touch the drunk.
Duff Man says a lot of things.
Oh, yeah!
Hmph!
[ Straining ]
- [ Screaming ]
- [ Gasping ]
[ Crowd Sighs ]
- [ Groans ]
- [ Cheering ]
And the winner, Moe Szyslak!
Oh, that's great.
Thank you. Thanks a lot.
Uh, I just want to say
that it was an honor for me...
to compete with the mick
and the, uh, chick with the rack there.
- Yeah, all right, Moe!
- That's my Moo!
And now, to take
your official calendar portrait...
Duff's vice president
in charge of calendars and fake I.D.'s...
Phil Angelides!
[ Cheering ]
- [ Gasps ]
- That's a mug you don't wanna chug.
Knock it off, Larry.
We can't put this face on our calendar.
[ Grunting ]
When I get home, there are
gonna be a lot of open pickle jars.
That one.
- Kids, would you like a balloon?
- Yeah, right, Mom.
Then I'd like a rattle and a ''wollypop.''
Actually, I would like a ''wollypop.''
Those balloons won't biodegrade for
1 0,000 years.
If Bart gets a wollypop,
I want a wollypop.
Ah, Maggie wants a balloon.
And Daddy will take a hand stamp
so he can get back in.
- [ Groans ]
-Just kidding.
Remember my face.
[ Moe]
Ah, boy.
[ Moans ]
[ Groans ]
Moe, the new Duff calendars are out-
the ones with your picture!
Oh, boy!
Move over liquor license.
Hey, Moe, this license
expired in 1 973...
and it's only good in Rhode Island,
and it's signed by you.
Yeah, yeah, I've been
meaning to get that updated...
for this state and real.
Now, let's see the poster boy
for the new Moe-llenium!
Hey-They put
a sticker over my face.
Hey. ''Viva la''-
''Kiss Me''-
What? Hey!
Ah, for the love of Jeff.
Ah! Oh.
Am I really that ugly?
- Moe, it's all relative. Is Lenny really that dumb?
- Huh?
- Is Barney that drunk?
- [ Moans ]
- Is Homer that lazy, bald and fat?
- [ Sighs ]
Oh, my God!
It's worse than I thought!
- [ Sobbing ]
See, this is why
I don't talk much.
I can't believe they put
those stickers over my face.
[ Sighs ]
I must be the ugliest man alive.
Oh, Moe, there's lots
of people uglier than you.
Like, you ever been
to White Castle?
Oh, boy.
Pigtown, U.S.A.
Come on. Look at me.
I'm a gargoyle...
what, with the cauliflower ear
there and the lizard lips-
- Little rat eyes.
- Caveman brow.
- Don't forget that fish snout.
- Okay, I get it. I ain't pleasant to look at.
- Or listen to.
- Or be with.
Come on, Moe.
Don't feel bad.
There's too much emphasis
on looks these days.
That's why they won't let Bill Maher
on TV before midnight.
Hey, Moe, if you're tired of being an eyesore,
why not get some plastic surgery?
Plastic surgery, huh?
Maybe they could dynamite Mount Crapmore
here and carve me a new kisser.
I don't know. Plastic surgery might
make you look good on the outside...
but you still might feel
bad on the inside.
But I'd look good
on the outside, right?
- Yeah, but you'd feel bad inside.
- Plastic surgery it is!
- Carl Carlson, you just saved my life.
- [ Cash Register Dings ]
Hey! Get outta there.
- [ Giggling ]
- Look at her.
Must be great to be a baby
and be so easily amused.
I wish I could be entertained by two cents worth
of rubber shaped like some colorful animal...
dancing and twirling,
dancing and twirling.
- Hey, give me that!
- It's mine!
[ Whimpering ]
- [ Screams ]
- The door!
- [ Grunts ]
- [ Wind Gusting ]
Oh, no!
[ Sobs ]
Okay, don't panic.
I'll get the bikes.
I hope they're hoverbikes.
- Oh, man, that would be so awesome!
- [ Moans ]
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
Hmm.
[ Imitates Bomb Falling, Exploding ]
- It's hopeless, ain't it?
- No, no, no, I love a challenge.
First, we must install buttocks.
Nah, nah, nah, no luxury items.
Just a face.
Okay, I'm gonna move this up.
This wider.
I'm gonna lose that.
I've never even seen one of these.
Can the medical mumbo jumbo.
Can you fix me or not?
Well, we'll see. You know,
most faces need a little remodeling...
but this is a total teardown.
Let me clean up
this mess I made.
Hey, hey!
Hey, that really burns there!
Oh, stop it.
You're worse than Faye Dunaway.
[ Bart Grunting ]
Oh, we've gotta get closer.
[ Moans ]
I'm trying.
Can't I get on your shoulders?
I'm not riding a girl's bike.
Hey, it's getting away!
Step on it. Hyah! Hyah!
- Stop kickin' me!
- Hyah!
Ooh, boy, what a mug!
Yeah. You should see his genitals.
Would you like to see them?
I'm awake here.
Uh-oh. This isn't anesthetic.
It's new car smell.
Sorry, Doctor.
Ho!
# Silver bells #
It's going into that building.
[ Bart ]
Nice suit,Jeeves.
Daddy, I'm stealing!
I'm stealing!
Oh, that's my little dude.
We need a symbol. Something
that says we're gay and Republican.
A little on the nose,
don't you think?
Excuse me.
We just came to get our balloon.
- Here you go. And have a bumper sticker.
- Thank you.
- ''A gay president in 2084''?
- We're realistic.
Hurry! Hurry up!
I have to pee!
- Beautiful.
- Okay, now do Moe.
Well, Moe, now we see...
if you go on my wall of fame,
or my blooper reel.
Oooh.
[ Groans ]
- [ Both Gasp ]
- What? I'm a monster, right?
I knew it. I guess I'll just
crawl back to live in a sewer...
periodically emerging
to sue you.
[ Gasps ]
Is that me?
Oopsie. We got some leakage.
Let me just cauterize that for you.
- [ Searing ]
- [ Moe Moaning ]
- Bye, Moe.
- Don't be a stranger, handsome.
Bye-bye.
Homer, did you hear that?
She called me handsome.
Me? It's like
I've gone to heaven. Uh-
Wait a minute.
I died on the operating table, didn't I?
Yeah, but just for a minute. It's a funny story.
I'll tell you sometime.
- So this is all real?
- Oh, you dear, dear man.
You're one of us
beautiful people now.
And your new life begins today.
A new life.
A second chance... for revenge.
That brown patch
needs a little H2O.
Oh, yeah!
Hey, Duff Man, let's see how you like
a sticker on your face! Yeah!
Duff Man... can't breathe.
Oh, no! Oh!
- [ Doorbell Rings ]
- Hello.
Yeah, hello yourself.
I'm Moe Szyslak.
Back in high school, I asked you...
to the Springtime Pumpkin Dance
and you turned me down.
Well, I just wanted to show you the face
that you could have been kissing.
- Yeah.
- Oh, I was just a stupid kid back then.
And I feel terrible
about hurting you.
- Will you accept my apology?
- Apology?
Uh, geez.
I wasn't expecting that. Uh-
Run!
Man, that felt great!
Okay, last stop, Channel 6.
You gonna get even with that lottery guy
that never picks our numbers?
Nah, nah, nah.
This is personal.
It all goes back to my acting days.
I was auditioning for the role
of Dr. Tad Winslow...
on the hit soap It Never Ends.
- Angela, I'm afraid I-
- [ Woman ] Thank you. Next.
- What were you thinking?
- Well, you said you wanted ''gritty.''
In other words, ugly.
I wanted Mary Ann
on Gilligan's Island ugly...
not Cornelius on
the Planet of the Apes ugly.
TV ugly, not ugly-ugly.
I've been called ugly,
pug ugly, fugly, pug fugly...
but never ugly-ugly.
Well, it's time to get some closure.
Extreme closure.
But I've been Dr. Tad
Winslow for 25 years.
It's time I got a raise!
Oh, shut up, you windy old hack.
And another thing, you have
to stop calling me that.
Remember me?
Twenty-five years ago...
you said I was too ugly
to play Dr. Tad Winslow.
I did? Well, that's why
pencils have erasers, hon.
- You're our new Dr. Tad Winslow.
- Really? You mean it?
But there can't be
two Dr. Tad Winslows!
That's going to- Oh.
[ Moans ]
I've been waiting
all my life for this moment.
[ Laughing ]
Homer, whoa, whoa!
Homer! Change of plans.
Whatever.
[ Male Announcer]
Like the cleaning of a house, It Never Ends.
With Gabriella DeFarge
as Gabriella St. Farge.
Allegra Hamilton as Sister Bernadette
and Roxie Monoxide.
And as Dr. Tad Winslow,
Moe Szyslak.
I don't know if I'll be able to accept
Moe as Dr. Tad Winslow.
Well, I'm gonna keep watching...
as long as they have shocking story twists
and endless pillow talk.
Cleo Cleo You brought music to my
heart
but this relationship
can never work.
I'm a doctor, and you're a 5,000-year-old
mummy I brought back to life.
But I love you, Tad, and together
we can burn all the cities of the Earth.
It's against hospital regulations,
damn it!
And Clive Dancer
is just waiting for me to slip up.
So, Lenny, how are things working out
with you and that girl next door?
Eh, it's over.
She got a window shade.
[ All Gasp ]
Whoa, whoa. If you must grope me, ladies,
please, a little softer.
- Okay, now harder.
- [ Women Sigh ]
- Hey, there are women in our bar.
- Hey, Moe, beer me.
I'm a little busy, Homer.
You can pour it yourself.
Hmm. This isn't nearly
as complicated as Moe made it seem.
[ Screaming ]
[ Gurgling ]
[ Chuckles ]
I didn't bring you back to life so you could
make a fool of me at the club!
''You don't love me. The only thing you love
is your ear, nose and throat pavilion.''
I've dedicated my life to diseases
of the head holes.
But the one hole I've never been able
to fix is the one in my soul!
That was amazing, Moe.
I'm actually a little turned on.
Hey, I got a gift. As a child,
I was bitten by the acting bug.
Then it burrowed under my skin
and laid eggs in my heart.
Now those eggs are hatching,
and the feeling is indescribable.
I know what you mean.
Our dog had that.
- [ Knocking ]
- Excuse me.
I got a delivery here
for the producers.
Top secret story lines?
Uh, I'll sign for it.
Uh, might as well have a little peak.
[ Chuckles ]
Hmm. Hmm!
Looks like my character gets back together
with that evil contessa.
- The one with the amulet?
- Precisely.
Then I get in a skydiving accident and have
to be rushed to the graveyard!
They're killing off
Dr. Tad Winslow.
What? Let me see that.
''Interior: Coroner's office.
''Close-up on Dr. Winslow's
mangled corpse.
Coroner: Let's get that brain out
and weigh it and call it a day.''
Yep, that does sound
kind of bad.
Well, if they're gonna
stomp on my dreams...
the least I can do is go out
in a blaze of sour grapes.
I never used to trust you,
Contessa...
but now you seem so nice.
Why don't we celebrate
your newfound trust in me...
by taking a skydiving lesson?
Well, how can I say no
to such a captivating-
- [ Homer] Ding-dong.
- Whoa! It's the door!
Dr. Winslow.
- Why, who are you?
- I am an angel from the future.
- Angel?
- What the- [ Bleeps ] Should I cut him off?
No. Let's see where this is going.
And what do you have to tell us,
O angel of the future?
You're going to die
in a skydiving accident.
How tragic.
Tell me more.
Gabriella's baby shower
will be invaded by terrorists...
with sexy results.
Ooh, that's unexpected.
What else?
Well, Sister Bernadette will leave
the convent and start a softball team...
- with sexy results.
- What's Dad doing on the show?
Who cares?
He's dishing out the dirt.
And only then do we find out
that Professor Galloway's half-sister...
is plotting to take over
International Perfume and Wine.
[ Groans ]
He just gave away a year's worth of story lines.
Cut him off... now.
- [ Both Laughing ]
- Yes!
What the hell are you doing?
Sticking it to you
for killing off my character.
- Yeah!
- Whoo!
You idiot. Dr. Winslow
was only going to die in a dream.
- Wha-
- Pink pages always mean a dream.
I thought dreams
was on goldenrod.
No, goldenrod
is for coma fantasies.
I see.
So, uh, what time tomorrow?
Escort these men out...
now.
Get your hands off me! Get off!.
I don't need your stinkin' show anyway!
With a mug like this,
I can get on any soap in Springfield.
Hmph!
[ Screams ]
Oh! Oh, my face!
I'm not supposed to put weight on it!
[ All Gasp ]
- [ All Gasp ]
- What? What?
- Sorry about your face, Moe.
- Nah, it's just as well.
That handsome face was nice,
but it was too much maintenance.
I had to wash it,
rub it with neat's-foot oil.
You did me a favor, Homer.
And to think...
- I was about to sell the bar to Hooters.
- Yeah, you were- D'oh!
Well, I guess that wraps it up.
There's one thing I don't get though.
When my face was crushed,
why did it go back to my old face?
Shouldn't it have turned into some kind of
third face that was different? Don't make no-
- Shh!
- [ Duff Man ] Oh,yeah!
www.tvsubtitles.net