The Simpsons
D'oh!
Oh, my God!
The Mad magazine special edition.
They only put out 17 of these a year!
Boy, they're really sockin' it to that Spiro Agnew
guy again. He must work there or something.
- Let's do the fold-in.
- Okay.
"What higher power
do TV evangelists worship?"
- I'll say God.
- I'll sayJesus.
- "The almighty dollar"?
- You fold it, you bought it.
Whoo! "Snappy answers
to stupid questions. "
I'm great at these. Ask me
if something smells funny in here, boy.
- Does something smell funny in here?
- I don't think so, stupid.
- Homie, you want pork chops?
- No, I want roast beef, you clod!
Look at this. Special insert:
"Iron-on madness.
Ban the bath.
Don't trust anyone over 10.
Sock it to me!"
Those magazines
create a dangerous amount of laughter.
"The 'all-ighty ollar"'?
I get it.
Say, business stinks tonight.
Where's Barney, Lenny and Carl?
They never come around anymore now
that they got their mistresses.
Might as well close the dump.
- I am gonna drink you under the table.
- No.
I am going to drink you under the-
Well, you're closin'. It's gettin' late.
My kids are probably wondering
where their daddy is.
There's gotta be some other place
we can go. Think, Moe! Think!
Sorry. It's league night.
I couldn't give a lane to my own mother.
I have no son.
Man, you go through life,
you try to be nice to people...
you struggle to resist the urge
to punch 'em in the face, and for what?
For some pimply little puke that treats ya
like dirt unless you're on a team.
Well, I'm better than dirt.
Well, most kinds of dirt.
I mean, not that fancy, store-bought dirt.
That stuff's loaded with nutrients.
I can't compete with that stuff.
That I cannot bowl wreaks havoc with
my self-esteem as well, but who am I to complain?
Well, I'm tired of being a wannabe
league bowler. I wanna be a league bowler!
Hey, we can be a team.
Excuse me, but my team
is ready to bowl.
- You're short one person.
- Uh...
that long-haired freak's
bowled with us for years.
I don't care if it takes me all night.
I'm gonna get me that lobster harmonica.
Come on, lobstie. Whoo.
- Oh, okay. Then I just need your $500 registration fee.
- $500!
Oh, no problem. Would you take
an out-of-state, two-party, bad check?
No, I will not
pay you $500 for sex.
Aw, come on, Marge. You're getting something
in return, and I'm getting a bowling team.
- It's win-win.
- It's sick...
and I don't have that kind
of money to spend on sex.
Maybe you could get someone with money
to sponsor your team, like Mr. Burns.
Burns never gives money to anybody.
- Just last week, I asked him for $1,500.
- For what?
Oh, I gotta
get the third degree from you too?
- Tonight's homework assignment is-
- Oh, man, is it hot in here.
I'd better take off my sweater.
"Down with"-
"homework"?
- Don't look at it, children.
- His shirt makes a good point.
I'm with the shirt!
Homework rots!
Down with homework!
Mmm.
As I was saying, my yearly evaluation
couldn't have come at a better time.
Well, Seymour, I must say,
for once, I am impressed.
In fact, I am going
to give this school a perfect 10.
I'll just write the zero first.
Now a vertical line
to indicate the one.
Down with homework!
Skinner, why are there children
walking on my head?
So, we meet again,
Mad magazine.
- How do you know it's from Mad?
- The year was 1968.
We were on recon
in a steaming Mekong delta.
An overheated private removed
his flak jacket, revealing a T-shirt...
with an iron-on sporting
the Mad slogan "up with miniskirts. "
Well, we all had a good laugh,
even though I didn't quite understand it.
But our momentary lapse of concentration
allowed Charlie to get the drop on us.
I spent the next three years
in a P.O.W. camp...
forced to subsist on a thin stew
made of fish, vegetables...
prawns, coconut milk
and four kinds of rice.
I came close to madness
trying to find it here in the States...
but they just can't
get the spices right.
- Uh, my punishment?
- Hmm? Oh, I'm gonna have to think about that.
Meanwhile, wear this home.
No-o-o.
I need some more ether.
I can still feel
the movement of the emery board.
- We're fresh out, sir. I'll get some more.
- Leave the rag.
Mmm.
Uh, excuse me, Mr. Burns.
Pop 'n' Fresh,
you glutinous little dough boy!
There's something
I've wanted to do to you for years.
Ow.
Mr. Burns,
I was wondering if you'd like...
to sponsor my bowling team
for $500.
Why, certainly, Pop 'n' Fresh.
I owe my robust physique to your tubes
of triple-bleached goo.
Whoo-hoo! Hey, everybody, if you wanna
ask Burns for a favor, now's the time!
He's doped up
or dyin' or somethin'!
Uh, excuse me.
I'd like to request $17...
for a push broom rebristling.
Why, it's that delightful TV leprechaun!
I'm going to get your Lucky Charms.
Oh, no. My brains.
Hey, nice, quote,
uniforms, end quote.
This just in. A new addition
to our worst-dressed list: those guys!
Oh, forget this.
I am far too fragile...
to withstand an evening
of barbs like that.
Oh, come on. If we quit now, we'll never
know how badly they're gonna beat us.
Yeah, you're right. That's the kind
of thing that would haunt ya.
- Hey!
- Sí.
: Buenas noches, senoritas.!
What did he say? What did he say?
Was that about me?
Okay, Otto. Pressure's on.
Don't choke. Don't choke.
Don't choke. Don't... choke.
Oh, man!
I knew I was gonna choke.
- That's a funny-lookin' strike.
- Come on, guys.
Let's be the team
that supports each other.
You can do it, Otto!
Help each other out!
That'll be our motto!
You can do it, Otto!
Make this spare,
I give you free gelato!
Then back to my place,
where I will get you blotto!
- Domo arigato, Mr. Roboto.
- You can do it, Otto! You can do it-
Guys, I made the spare.
We won.
Yes! Yeah! All right!
Those beers
are five dollars apiece.
- Let me set the scene for you, Marge.
- All right.
- It's a 7-10 split, the hardest shot in bowling.
- Uh-huh.
It was all up to me,
so I got up all my courage.
Right away,
my lips started to move...
and I came up with a chant
that won the match!
- Who knocked down the pins?
- I don't know. You know, some guy. Otto, I guess.
- Good for him.
- Yes, but, Marge, you're missing the point.
The individual doesn't matter.
It was a team effort.
And I was the one who came up
with the whole team idea.
- Me.
- I can't believe Otto picked up a 7-10 split.
- He's phenomenal. Wow.
- But-
Several days ago,
a violent riot erupted...
incited by an inflammatory T-shirt slogan.
No, no. Now, don't try to remember
what that slogan was.
To ensure that this frenzied dance
of destruction is never repeated...
I've decided, starting Monday,
all students will be required to wear uniforms.
Huh? Uniforms?
Say hello to our little genius, Martin,
who looks even smarter...
in this vest and short pant combination
from Mr. Boy of Main Street.
Or how about little Lisa Simpson?
She'll have no reason to play the blues
in this snappy ensemble...
topped off with a saucy French beret...
that seems to scream "silence. "
All right. Pick your size:
extra small or extra large.
We've got both.
No pushing now. I-What?
Oh, I've just been informed
we've run out of extra large.
Go, Moe.! Go, Moe.!
Don't make Homer shout out, "D'oh.!"
Yeah!
Yea!
All right, Snake.
Make us proud.
One, two, three,
four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10.
Bye!
Ah, we forfeit.
We'll take it.
There it is, boys:
the championship trophy.
Whoo.
We will never possess it.
The Holy Rollers
have won it five years in a row.
They think they're so high and mighty...
just 'cause they never
got caught drivin' without pants.
God boy couldn't get a strike!
It's me. Ned.
Mom, my slingshot doesn't
fit in these pockets...
and these shorts leave nothing
to the imagination.
- These uniforms suck.
- Bart, where do you pick up words like that?
Yeah, Moe, that team sure did suck
last night. Theyjust plain sucked.
I've seen teams suck before, but they were
the suckiest bunch of sucks that ever sucked.
- Homer, watch your mouth!
- I gotta go. My damn wiener kids are listening.
- We are not wieners.
- Then what are you dressed like that for?
- They made us.
- Oh. "They made us. "
That's loser talk. You gotta start acting
more like me and my team...
the future league champions
of the world.
Nothing's gonna stop us now.
Stop everything! I don't remember
writing a check for bowling.
- Sir, that's a check for your boweling.
- Oh, yes. That's very important.
Yes, sir.
Remember that month you didn't do it?
Yes, that was unpleasant for all concerned.
Anyway, back to the checks.
Stop everything!
- I don't remember writing a check for bowling.
- Hmm.
The memo says,
"To my pal, Pop 'n' Fresh. "
Oh, yes.
That greedy, grasping glob of chemicals.
Probably one of your
ether-induced hallucinations, sir.
I'll check the employee files to see
who could pull off such an impersonation.
It was either Pops Freshenmeyer...
or Homer Simpson.
Simpson, eh? Let's shut down
this bowling scam right now.
Come on, Homer. Come on, Homer.
Pretend this is baseball and hit us a homer.
You rolled it. You rolled it.
By the way, rhyming "Homer"
with "Homer"-
Look at them, Smithers,
enjoying their embezzlement.
I have a much uglier word
for it, sir: misappropriation.
Simpson.!
Listen here. I want to join your team.
- You wanna join my what?
- You wanna what his team?
I've had one
of my unpredictable changes of heart.
Seeing these fine young athletes reveling
in the humiliation of a vanquished foe-
I haven't felt this energized
since my last... boweling.
Oh, man.
He'll blow our winning streak.
Yeah. Call this
an unfair generalization if you must...
but old people
are no good at everything.
Look, guys,
it's not that simple. He's my boss.
I'll tell you what.
I'll give him a shot, and if he stinks...
it'll be easier to tell him no.
Ooh-
Welcome aboard!
It wasn't any easier.
Ah, these uniforms
are a godsend.
Horseplay's down 40%.
Youthful exuberance has been cut in half.
High spirits
are at an all-time low.
- They've even begun blinking in unison.
- I love that sound.
Now, children,
while you're having quiet time...
I'm going to make sure
my desk is exactly parallel to the rear wall.
Oh, there's something I used...
to do in this situation,
but can't remember.
Ha- ho?
I can't believe I got
booted off the team for Mr. Businessman.
I bet I'll get a little respect
once I get that Harvard diploma.
Look at that. All the way
to the end with only one push.
That's the third game
in a row he cost us, Homer.
- Mamma mia.!
- Hoot, mon!
- Yee-haw!
- Arr, me mateys. Arr.
Whoo! They begged me
to join their team- begged me.
Well, we certainly
got walloped tonight, eh, fellas?
Well-
Uh, Mr. Burns, next week
is the big championship game.
Ah, yes,
that silly championship.
The only ship worth a damn
is friendship.
Look. Here comes the "friend ship"
sailing your way.
Ooh, here.
Let me get that, friend.
Oops. Lost a nail.
Well, that's leprosy for you.
You're it.
- Now you are the one who is it.
- Understood.
Well, I've gotta hand it to you, Seymour.
These drab student coverings...
have created the perfect
distraction-free environment...
thus preparing the children for
permanent positions in tomorrow's mills...
and processing facilities.
Best of all, with less
than a minute to go before I leave...
absolutely nothing has gone wrong.
Well, it is starting to rain,
but I could hardly be blamed for that, can I?
Yes. Very good.
Wow!
Look at all the colors, man!
Red, green, yellow, orange!
I remember all of these!
I'm freaking out!
Hey, something's
comin' back to me!
- Down with homework!
- And down with uniforms.!
Yea!
Ow, ow, ow, ow! Skinner...
why aren't these uniforms colorfast?
I don't understand it. I got them
at the same place I buy Mother's dresses, and-
- Good Lord! Mother's in the park!
- This I've gotta see.
Oh, Marge, we were so close
to winning the championship.
Now, thanks to Burns,
it's never gonna happen.
And I spent so much time
building that trophy case.
Homer, maybe Mr. Burns will bowl
a great game, and you will win your championship.
So you're saying we're
definitely gonna win? Whoo-hoo!
I won't need this anymore.
Marge, someone broke the toilet.
Don't worry about nothin', Homer.
I have a feeling...
that Mr. Burns is gonna have
a little accident that might keep him...
from bowlin' with us
tonight, heh, heh, heh.
Smithers, I'm afraid
I won't be able to play tonight.
My old gimpy knee
has gone akimbo again.
- Take that!
- Ooh!
Smithers, that precision assault popped it
back into place. Thank you, masked stranger!
D'oh! He's gonna ruin everything!
All right. That's it, Homer.
Either Burns goes,
or Moe goes.
Yes, I am afraid that I am going
to have to make a similar threat...
with my name in place
of Moe's name.
So, who's ready to
kick some Christian keister?
Oh, uh, Mr. Burns,
as team captain...
it's my duty to inform you that-
Ooh, I almost forgot!
I brought you all a little something.
Aww, would you look at that?
The "Pin Pals. "
At last, I finally have a garment
fine enough to be married in.
I've always been wealthy, but this
is the first time I ever felt... rich.
- Aww.
- Now, Homer, you were about to say something to me.
- You're off the team.
- What?
He's just ribbin' ya, Monty.
Yes.
- Had you going there.
- Guys.
Hey, hey, hey!
- Hallelujah.
- Hallelujah.!
Aww.
- Nice one, Homer.
- Thanks.
Okay. The Holy Rollers are ahead by one pin...
and we only
have one bowler left: Mr. Burns.
Hmm?
Well, next time, a few steps more
toward center, don't you think?
Good-bye, trophy.
Ooh. Whatever
I got ahold of is big.
- Yes!
- Excellent.
Yes!
Whoo-hoo! We won! We won!
- You mean, I won.
- But we were a team, sir.
Oh, I'm afraid I've had one
of my trademark changes of heart.
You see,
teamwork will only take you so far.
Then the truly evolved person
makes that extra grab for personal glory.
Now I must discard my teammates, much
like the boxer must shed roll after roll...
of sweaty, useless, disgusting flab
before he can win the title.
- Ta.
- I guess some people never change.
Or they quickly change
and then quickly change back.
You know what?
We don't need him or his trophy.
- We got each other, huh?
- Yeah, yeah. That's right, Moe. Aww.
- Go, Homer, you're our man!
If you can't do it, nobody can!
Ooh!
No! Oh, God!
- Well, I guess no one can.
- Run, before they're through feeding!
No.! Oh, God.!
No.!
Shh!