##[ Chorus Singing ]
[ Bell Ringing ]
[ Whistle Blowing ]
[ Beeping ]
## [Jazzy Solo ]
[ Tires Screeching ]
D'oh!
[ Screams ]
## [ Humming ]
[ Homer's Voice ]
Hey, Bart-Bart...
looks like a beautiful day to
swipe some ''pic-i-nic'' baskets.
[ Bart's Voice ]
But, ''Homi,'' Ranger Ned's not gonna like that.
I'll handle Ranger Ned.
After all, I'm smarter
than the average bear.
Well, hello there, Ho-didilly-omi.
Well, I'm afraid I'm gonna have
to ask you to hand over that-
[ Shouting ]
Gee, Homi, it's not very nice
to maul Ranger Ned.
- You want some of this?
- Uh-uh.
- [ Shouting ]
- [ Groaning ]
[ Growling ]
- Dad, wake up! Wake up!
- Dad, wake up!
[ Moans ]
I was having the most wonderful dream.
I had a hat and a tie,
with no pants on.
Yeah, yeah. Anyway, you promised
to take us to the lake.
I promise you lots of things.
That's what makes me such a good father.
Actually keeping promises
would make you a good father.
- No, that would make me a great father.
- So Are we going to the lake?
Yes, we'll go to the darn lake.
Now go back to bed. It's 4:00 a.m.
Aw, 4:00 a.m.? Now I'll never get back to-
[ Snoring ]
## [ Singing Cartoon Theme Song ]
Hey, you shouldn't have oughta
taken my banana, Mr. Peebles.
[ Roars, Hoots ]
- [ Horns Honking ]
- [ Marge ] Wow.!
It looks like the lake
is the place to be, huh?
Well, if we'd left at 4:00 a.m
like I wanted to-
Dad, you really should be
watching the road.
- Hey, Homer. Enough traffic for you?
- [ Neck Cracks ]
- Homer, your spine.
- [ Cracks ]
Hey, pfft. Screw this.
Hang on, everyone.
We're taking the old Simpson shortcut.
- [ Tires Squeal ]
- [ Homer] So long, suckers.
[ Bart ]
Whoa!
[ Chuckles ]
Eat my dust, suckers.
[ Marge ]
Stop calling everyone suckers.
## [ Homer Scatting ]
Hmm.
[ Chomps ]
Ugh! Pesticides.
Carbamate, if I'm not mistaken.
Yep. Carbamate.
- [ Marge ] Tree!
- I see it.
Hmm. This is such a secluded area.
I wonder who lives in that house.
[ Homer ]
Way out in the sticks like this?
It could only be hillbillies.
So I suppose that's
a hillbillyJacuzzi.
Yep. That's where
they cook up their vittles.
[ Chattering ]
[ Laughs ]
- [ Rod And Todd Giggling ]
- Hey, here come the Simpsons.
Now be careful, Homer. There's a fella
in the sand right in front of you.
[ Shouts ]
Okay, remember where we parked.
[ Ned ]
Homer, is that my muffler?
There you go. And I assume
you've read the boat safety manual.
Oh, yeah. Couldn't put it down.
Come on, boy. Let's get me a six-pack.
Uh, sir, you can't operate a boat
under the influence of alcohol.
Oh, that sounds like a wager to me.
- Life jackets?
- Check.
- Tow rope?
- Secure.
- Skier?
- Ready.
Here we go.
She's down.
- Oh, look at it go.
- Stay there, honey.
We'll come back for you.
[ Screams ]
- How's he doing?
- I don't know.
I think Dad might be
a little heavy for parasailing.
Faster, Marge! Faster.
The snapping turtles are massing.
- Heads up! Coming through.
- [ Clamoring ]
Hey, volleyball.
Can I play later?
Hi, Apu.
Oh, dear. You have ruined my work,
you flying fat man.
- [ Screeching ]
- [ Clamoring ]
Hey!
[ Sighs ]
Step on it, Mom. Dad's signaling
that he wants to go higher.
[ Gurgling ]
Higher.
[ Spits ]
Bye-bye, ''fishies.''
Higher. Higher!
I'm soaring-
Soaring majestically, like
a candy wrapper caught in an updraft.
Higher, Marge. Higher!
- It won't go any.
- Higher, I say.
I wanna soar higher
than any man has ever soared.
I wanna look down
on the clouds with contempt.
I wanna sneer at God's creation...
and spit on his- Uh-oh.
[ Whimpering ]
Lower! Lower!
- There goes my turn.
- [ Whimpering ]
This is not good.
[ Whimpers, Gasps ]
Aw, nuts.
[ Shouting ]
[ Buzzing ]
Huh? What? Oh, already?
- [ Woman Gasps ] What the hell-
- Sorry, lady.
[ Gasps ]
I know you. You're Kim ''Basin-jer.''
- It's Basinger.
- Oh, my God.
I'm such a huge, huge
fan of yours, Miss ''Basin-jer.''
Thanks. Um, listen.
- You think you could slide over a little?
- Well, I am a married man.
- You're crushing my husband.
- [ Man Groans ]
[ Gasps ]
Billy Baldwin!
I'm Alec Baldwin.
Could you get off me?
So what are you two kids
doing in my neck of the woods?
- Well-
- Wait! Tell me over breakfast.
Who's for pancakes?
Are you sure you don't want to go
to the hospital, Mr. Simpson?
You had an awful lot of glass in you.
Oh, I don't want to be a bother.
Anyway, what are you two big Hollywood stars
doing in good old Springfield?
Sometimes we need
to get away from Hollywood.
L.A. is just so phony.
Well, why don't you just
move to, say, Bethesda?
- Not phony enough.
- What we really like here is the privacy.
Most people don't even know
where Springfield is.
Yeah. Tell you the truth,
I'm not even sure.
We're trying to keep a low profile.
We don't even go to the supermarket.
Yeah, we've been living off
congratulatory muffin baskets.
Blech! Zucchini.
- Don't just put that back in the basket.
- I'm gonna eat it later.
You shouldn't have to survive
on dry, crumbly muffins from...
''the Gersh Agency.''
You should let me do your shopping.
I know where I can get you
some great muffins.
- No more muffins.
- Okay, fine.
But I could do all kinds of stuff for you.
I notice that skylight
in your bedroom's broken.
Yeah, I'm not sure we need
an assistant, Mr. Simpson.
Please. Homer. Come on.
If you let me hang around a while,
I can do all kinds of stuff for ya.
Well, we are down
to our last roll of toilet paper.
And I have been brushing
my teeth with hair gel for a week.
I suppose we could give it a try.
- Yeah, you owe me that much.
- Okay, you're on.
But look- Nobody knows we're in
Springfield, and we wanna keep it that way.
Will you promise to keep our secret?
Absolutely, if you promise to keep mine.
- Okay. What is it?
- I can't read.
But you just read that card
from the Gersh Agency.
I recognized the logo.
## [ Whistling ]
Homie, are you okay?
We've been lookin' all over for you, Dad.
Where did you land?
- Nowhere famous.
- Where'd you get that muffin?
Gersh Agency.
Apu, I'm about to purchase some weird
and fruity items, and I don't want any guff.
First of all, I'll need
the following mushrooms:
- Portobello.
- Yes.
- Porcini.
- Right.
- Chanterelle.
- Uh-huh.
- And Shiitake.
- Okay. We have none of those. What is next?
A gallon of wheatgrass juice, a five-pound
wad of tofu, some jellied zinc...
and a couple of pairs
of $600 sunglasses.
Mr. Simpson, these exotic items
are suspiciously different...
from your usual order
of beer and pork.
- What gives?
- Uh, nothing, nothing.
I'm just broadening my horizons.
By the way, do you have extra-wide
bumper stickers for a Humvee?
Wow. You got everything, Homer-
Even the Oscar polish.
- [ Squeaking ]
- Honey, why don't you give that thing a rest?
You're taking the finish off.
When you win one,
you can take care of it however you want.
Whoo-hoo. Meow.
- [ Doorbell Rings ]
- I'll get it. I'll get it.
- Yes?
- Hi. I'm Ron Howard.
- Ron Howard?
- Yeah. I'm looking...
for Alec Baldwin and Kim Basinger.
Alec Baldwin and Kim Basinger?
Oh, hey, Ron. We heard you were
looking for a place in Springfield.
Yeah, well, it's the only town in America
that'll let me fish with dynamite.
Uh-What's with him?
Oh, that's just Homer.
He's a new friend of ours.
Really? You giant stars
consider me a friend?
Well, for the first time
in my life I feel like I'm somebody.
Ronny, are you also my close friend?
[ Sniffs ]
Do I smell vodka? And wheatgrass?
It's called a lawn mower. I invented it.
- You want one?
- Yeah, okay.
- And I'll have a rum and zinc.
- Ooh, I'll have one of those too.
- Hey, can I crash here tonight?
- Sure. We'll all stay.
A cell phone?
Last Thursday's Variety?
- [ Door Closes ]
- ##[ Whistling ]
[ Gasps ]
I'll do that. You go upstairs and have a beer.
Homer, when did you
become a member of PETA?
Well, you know me.
I love animals-
Beef, chicken, veal.
If you're not part of the solution, Marge,
you're part of the problem.
- That's not what PETA stand-
- [ Ringing ]
- Imagine Films.
- Hmm?
A, uh, division of, um, Homer Co.
- ##[ Disco Beat ]
- And lift. And strain.
And hyperextend.
Keep those knees rigid.
Jerk that lower back.
Homer, I'm- I'm feeling some
sharp pains in my neck.
That' right, force it.
Whip that neck.
Um, does anybody know
where this came from?
Oh, there's that movie script I wrote.
- Where did you find it?
- On my pillow.
The important thing is,
it's got the perfect part for you.
Either one of you.
It's about a killer-robot
driving instructor...
who travels back in time
for some reason.
Ron Howard's attached to direct.
- I am not.
- Well, he expressed an interest.
- No, I didn't.
- Did too.
- I did not.
- You lie!
Yeah, Homer, um,
most movie scripts are 1 20 pages.
This is only 1 7...
and several of the pages are
just drawings of the time machine.
- So you're saying you don't want
to star in my movie?
- I'm sorry, Homer.
Well, if Alec is out, I'm out too.
You're on your own, Potsie.
''The Terminizer:An Erotic Thriller. ''
[ Chattering, Laughter ]
So I'm in the grocery store the other day,
buying some cotton balls.
- The absorbent kind?
- You got that right, my friend.
- [ Laughing ]
- I round the corner and I head
down the ointment aisle...
when who should I spot-
None other than Kent Brockman.
The local news guy?
''Mr. Channel 6''?
- [ Chattering ]
- My God! What I'd give to meet him.
- Oh, they don't come much bigger than that.
- [ Blows Raspberries ]
Kent Brockman? Please.
Oh, what? I suppose you've seen a bigger star.
- I might have.
- Come on, make with a name.
[ Groans ]
I can't. I promised I wouldn't.
You've got to keep
our secret, Homer.
Homer, we're out of vodka.
Tell the people, Homer.
They have a right to know...
about the celebrity summer house.
- Who the hell are you?
- What do you care?
I'm telling you what you want to hear.
All right, I'm gonna
let you guys in on something.
But you've got to keep it
much more secret than I did.
[ Grunts ]
- [ Grunts ]
Yes! In your freckled face, Howard.
- Unbelievable.
- What?
Nothing, nothing. Good hustle.
- [ Rhythmic Rumbling ]
- My God-The lemonade. Look at the lemonade.
- [ Rumbling Continues ]
- Uh-oh.
[ Chattering ]
Hey, look at that.
Isn't that something?
Quick- Everybody inside.
The shuttlecock-
Where's the shuttlecock?
- [ Chattering ]
- [ Panting ]
[ Chattering Continues ]
Arr. I loved Splash, Mr. Howard.
- It was totally, uh, uh, arr. [ Chuckles ]
- Uh, Miss Basinger?
Those red pumps you wore
in L.A. Confidential were fabulous.
Where can I get a pair for my, uh, mother?
She wears a 1 2 double-E.
Alec, Alec- Regarding that so-called
silent propulsion system...
in The Hunt for Red October-
I printed out a list
of technical errors...
which I think you'd
enjoy discussing.
Somebody must have
told them we live here.
I'm looking at you, Horshack.
Homer, how could you?
Okay, okay, it was me.
I'm sorry I blew your secret.
But you don't know
what it's like to be a nobody.
I just wanted to bask
in your reflected glory.
Reflected glory!
Homer, you betrayed our confidence.
I just don't think
we can be friends anymore.
- But where will I bask?
- Anywhere but here.
Come on, Ron. We're not wanted here.
All right, I'll go.
But the next time you want someone
to remind you which brother is which...
- or smell your hair while you're sleeping-
- [ Gasps ]
just remember, old Homer
won't be here anymore.
- [ Clamoring ]
- [ Moe ] Hey, come on.!
[ Sideshow Mel ]
Wait a minute. Somebody's coming out.
- Who is it? Is it anybody?
- No, no. It's nobody.
Throw your stones. It's nobody.
[ Clamoring ]
Oh, how could Alec and Kim
just cut me out of their lives?
Homer, you haven't
touched your food.
When Kim makes a Manwich,
she uses focaccia bread.
And would it kill you
to put some fennel in it?
Alec Baldwin? Wow! That is
the coolest person you've ever been fired by.
- What was it like at their house?
- Oh, it was so great.
I didn't have to fake it with them.
I was actually excited
to hear about their day.
- I washed the dog today.
- Was it the dog from the Beethoven movies?
- Of course not.
- [ Groans ] Our dog isn't famous.
And you kids aren't exactly
John and Joan Cusack.
And you-You couldn't open a movie
if your life depended on it.
I'm about ready
to ankle this family.
Ankle? Focaccia?
What are you talking about?
See? It's like we don't even speak
the same language anymore.
The only one who understands me
is that guy who married Martha Raye.
Don't blame us, Dad. The celebrities
are the ones who canned you.
Hmm. She may not be famous,
but she's right.
Those big-shot stars
used me up and spit me out.
I did their laundry.
Got their pictures developed.
Took their garbage to the dump.
And I still got
a carful of their crap.
Crap, eh?
[ Chattering ]
Hey, is it too late
to see the movie stars?
No, no.Just, uh, hop that fence...
sneak up and, uh,
peek in the window there.
All right.
- [ Crackling ]
- [ Groans ]
[ Chuckles ]
I never get tired of that.
[ Horn Honks ]
[ Homer On Loudspeaker ]
Attention, starstruck fools.
Step right up and see
the world's greatest mobile collection...
of Alec and Ron and ''Kim-o-rabilia.''
- [ Chattering ]
- Only five- No wait. Ten dollars.
- You heard right. Twenty dollars.
- [ Lenny ] Homer, me first. Come on, man.
[ Chattering ]
[ Barney ]
Oh! Hundred-year-old stuff.
Hey, it's Alec Baldwin's
Medic Alert bracelet.
That's right, ''Mr. Tough Guy''
can't handle a little penicillin.
Oh, and look at this.
We can't even pay our bills,
and they're drinking Royal Crown Cola.
- Hey, hey. Go easy on the celebrities, huh?
- Yeah. What gives you the right?
- Leave 'em alone.
- We love celebrities.
Oh, yeah? What have they
ever done for you?
When was the last time Barbra Streisand
cleaned out your garage?
And when it's time to do the dishes,
where's Ray Bolger?
I'll tell ya.
Ray Bolger is lookin' out for Ray Bolger!
Oh, look. Wasn't that a fun weekend?
Yeah. Homer was a pretty good guy.
And we just tossed him out
like a Golden Globe award.
I've got to admit, I miss the way
he used to tuck us in...
and kiss us on the forehead.
- Forehead?
- Oh, maybe I should have made his movie.
Yeah. It wasn't that bad.
I mean, the script
might even work...
if you got rid of the talking pie.
What, are you crazy?
It's a buddy picture.
Without the pie, it would just be me
on screen for two hours.
Oh, yeah, and you'd hate that.
No, no, no. You can't lose the pie.
The pie is your heart.
Okay, okay. Keep the damn pie.
The point is, we weren't fair to Homer.
He screwed up, but he deserves
another chance.
Yeah. Everyone makes mistakes.
I mean, we'd want another chance
if one of us ever made a bad film, right?
[ Birds Singing ]
[ Ducks Quacking ]
I'm really looking forward
to seeing Homer again.
He always has the most
interesting odors.
[ High-Pitched Voice ]
Ooh, look at me.
I'm Kim Basinger,
the big movie star.
I'm so beautiful.
I think I'm so great.
I'm too important to take
Homer to the Oscars.
- What the-
- [ Screams ]
Got to go. Thank you for supporting
the Museum of Hollywood Jerks.
- Let's get him.
- And this time it's personal.
What? It is personal.
He's got our underpants.
[ Tires Screeching ]
- [ Horn Honking ]
- I'll never outrun them in a museum.
- Pull over, you maniac.
- No!
Just jump over there, Alec.
It's not that far.
Yeah, you're a big
screen tough guy.
Uh, gee, I'd love to, but I'm not really
wearing the right shoes.
[ Imitates Chicken ]
Fine.
- [ Grunts ]
- [ Screams ]
[ Laughing ]
Hey, I made it. All by myself.
Hey, were you watching,
sweetheart? I made it!
Ow! Aaah! My watch is caught.
Oh, for the love of- Hold on.
- Can you drive?
- Not well, but I'll give it a shot.
- [ Grunts ]
- [ Thump ]
- Oh, God!
- [ Tire Screeching ]
[ Kim Screaming ]
[ Both Screaming ]
I guess it's up to me.
- [ Groaning ]
- [ Both ] Ron!
- You killed Ron Howard.
- Okay, I'll stop.
[ Gavel Banging ]
- Mr. Simpson, do you have
anything to say for yourself?
- Yes, I do.
I believe that famous people
have a debt to everyone.
If celebrities didn't want
people pawing through their garbage...
and saying they're gay, they shouldn't have
tried to express themselves creatively.
In closing, you people must realize...
that the public owns you for life,
and when you're dead...
you'll all be in commercials,
dancing with vacuum cleaners.
Thank you, Your Honor.
Mr. Simpson, you are forbidden
to come within 500 miles...
of any celebrity, living or dead.
[ All ]
Whoo-hoo!
Well, I'll always have
my crank calls.
[ Beeping ]
Hello? Old lady from Titanic?
You stink!
[ Giggles ]
And it grows to a powerful,
emotional climax...
when the father has to choose...
which one of his children will live...
and which one will die.
- Pass.
- [ Groans ]
- What else you got?
- Uh-
Well, there is this one thing.
It's about a killer-robot
driving instructor...
that travels back in time
for some reason.
- I'm listening.
- Okay, okay.
Well, you see, this robot-
He's got a heartbreaking
decision to make...
about whether his
best friend lives or dies.
- Eh.
- His best friend's a talking pie.
Sold! Howard, you've done it again.
##[ Man Singing ]
- [ Murmuring ]
- Shh!
[ Ron Howard ]
Homer, we're out of vodka.
www.tvsubtitles.net