##[ Chorus Singing ]
[ Bell Ringing ]
[ Whistle Blowing ]
[ Beeping ]
## [Jazzy Solo ]
[ Tires Screeching ]
D'oh!
[ Screams ]
[ All ]
Whoa!
## [ Singing ]
## [ Continues ]
## [ Singing Rock Song ]
I didn't think it was physically possible,
but this both sucks and blows.
## [ Singing Ends ]
[ Chuckles ]
Whew. Mercy.
Good evening. Our old friend Noah Webster
defines ''laughter''...
as ''the act or sound of laughing.''
[ Nelson ]
Ha-ha.!
[ Chuckles ]
Well illustrated, Nelson.
And now, fasten your funny bones
for Groundskeeper-
Oh. Or should I say
''Grinskeeper''?
No, I'm sorry.
Groundskeeper was correct. Willie!
- ## [ Bagpipes ]
- [ Applause ]
How many of you hail from
the fair city of Edinburgh?
So, have you noticed...
how North Edinburgh golfers
putt like this...
and South Edinburgh golfers
putt like this?
- [ Man Coughs ]
- Eh?
- ## [ Bagpipes ]
- [ Crickets Chirping ]
- Oh, I see.
Willie's not funny unless
he's down on his knees...
scooping up your little brats' puke!
[ Laughing, Applauding ]
Thank you! You've been great!
##[Jazz ]
## [ Singing ]
## [ Continues ]
- [ Groaning ]
- ## [ Continues ]
- [ Balloons Popping ]
- Kill me.
Well, Seymour,
it seems we put together...
a baseball team,
and I was wondering-
Who's on first?
Yes. Not the pronoun,
but rather a player...
with the unlikely name
of Who is on first.
Yes. Well, that's
just great, Seymour.
We've been out here six seconds.
You've already managed to blow the routine.
Sexless freak.
- ##[ Rim Shot ]
- [ Laughs ]
Well, seems as though
we're just about at the halfway point...
- so why don't we call it intermission?
- [ Chattering ]
Whoa! Don't go too far.
If you like cafeteria workers
in Beatle wigs with tennis racket guitars...
you won't want to miss
the second half.
- Oh, no! No!
- [ All Shouting ]
You drive. I eat.
Dad, you were supposed
to pay for those snacks.
I saw Krabappel's butt.
I paid.
[ Horns Honking ]
Whoopsie.
Mm, this could take a minute.
- There's an opening, Mom.
- I don't know.
I- I hate to change lanes
once I get going.
- That's really for race car drivers.
- Mom, to your left.
He's letting you in. Go!
- [ Lisa ] Come on, Mom.!
- [ Homer ] Gun it, woman.!
No. No. As soon as I get over,
that lane will stop moving.
Erma Bombeck said so,
and Dave Barry agrees.
- [ Horns Honking ]
- Aw! You suck, Marge.
- Come on! Move it, you clowns!
- [ Honking ]
What in blazes?
So long, schlubs!
Wow. Did you see that thing, Marge?
So powerful. So commanding.
- So forceful and raw.
- [ Horse Neighs ]
It didn't ask. It just took.
- ##[ Man Singing Country Music ]
- [ Man #2 Shouts ]
- ##[ Ends ]
- [ Groaning ]
Oh, Canyonero.
[ Laughs ]
Go ahead. Drool all you want.
You can't hurt that finish.
Now, rainwater- that'll strip it right off.
Ah, I shouldn't have
said that. I'm Gil.
Hey, a red one!
[ Laughing ]
Can I buy that? Please?
Well, you- If you-
[ Babbles ] Really?
Wha- Ha!
Hot dog! A sale!
[ Laughing ]
- [ Laughing Continues ] Huh?
- I'll take it from here, Gil.
No! Wait! Ah, no!
You can't take my sale!
My wife's gonna leave me
if I don't start bringing in the green.
Come on. Let me have this one, Stan.
I'm begging you.
Look at me.
I'm begging you, Stan.
Mm-hmm.
Let's go write this up, shall we?
Honey, you should've seen me
with my last customer. I-
No, but I came so close.
This guy was-
Whose voice is that?
Is that Fred?
Ah, you said it was over!
No, don't put him on!
Hello, Fred. H-Hi.
Okay. You've got
the undercoating...
clear coating, rustproofing,
under guard spray...
Gravel Guard XJ,
Vita-Seal, Repels-It...
but if you want to protect the paint,
you better keep it in this tent.
- Will do.
- Okay. Here's how your lease breaks down:
This is your down payment, then here's
your monthly, and there's your weekly.
- And that's it, right?
- Yup.
Oh, then after your final monthly payment,
there's the routine C.B.P....
- or crippling balloon payment.
- But that's not for a while, right?
- Right.
- Sweet.
[ Bird Caws ]
- Whoo! Hello!
- Whoo!
Hey, baby!
Oh. Sorry, Homer. We thought you were
one of those hot-to-trot soccer moms.
Yeah. You don't see many men
driving the ''F'' Series.
Huh?
See? Instead of a cigarette lighter,
it's got a lipstick holder.
[ Gasps ]
Ah, crap! It's a girl's car!
I can't drive this!
Oh, sure, you can, doll face.
[ Kisses ]
[ Chuckles ] Pretty thing like you
can do whatever she wants.
[ Both Laughing ]
Shut up! Screw you guys!
Lousy ''F''Series frilly, girlie, fruity car.
[ Mutters ]
Where's your keys?
I'm taking your car to work.
You cashed in your 401 (k) to buy
that stupid Canyonero.
- Why can't you drive it?
- Are you saying I'm gay?
Because if that's what you think,
then just come right out and say it.
I don't think you're gay.
I just have to do my grocery shopping.
Now, please, give me my keys.
Fine.
## [ Humming ]
- [ Engine Starts ]
- [ Laughs ]
- Ha-ha! Sucker!
- Oh!
Good Lord!
[ Groans ]
How am I supposed
to get in this beast?
Hmm. Well, that's a nice feature.
Not much headroom though.
Ooh!
Oh, I guess I can
drive it for a little while.
But, Mom, I read that
sport utility vehicles...
are more likely to be involved
in fatal accidents.
Fatal to the people in the other car.
Let's roll.
Hang on. The manual says
I need to log on to the onboard computer.
M-A-R-G-E.
[ Electronic Female Voice ] Hello, Marge.
Where would you like to go today?
[ Gasps ] No one has ever asked me
that before in my life.
Well, that's a first.
I've never been able...
to fit 3 2 grocery bags
into one car before.
Ew! Why is Courtney Love
on the Wheaties box?
- Hmm. I thought it was Sandy Duncan.
- Uh-oh. Gridlock at 1 2:00.
- [ Horns Honking ]
- [ People Shouting ]
Oh, crud.
And we're so close to the house.
Um, I don't want to alarm you,
but the ice cream's starting to go south.
Hmm. Mm-hmm.
[ Gags ]
Hey, give me some of that!
[ Screams ]
Mom! Bart sprayed
whipped cream in my eye!
- I did not.
- [ Screams ]
- [ Both Grunting ]
- Kids, cut it out!
- [ Sighs ] All right.
- Hey!
Come on, Mom.
Just cut across the field.
Oh, I don't know.
It doesn't seem right.
[ Scoffs ] Do you want to spend
your whole life doing what's right?
Of course not.
- Let's do it!
- ##[ Man Singing Country Music ]
[ Man #2 Shouts ]
- ##[ Continues ]
- Whoa! You the man, Mom!
Out of my way, nature!
[ Chittering ]
##[ Ends ]
[ Gasps ]
Look at me, Lise.
I'm Baron Von Chicken Pants.
[ Clucking ]
Bart, that's
tomorrow night's dinner.
- You're tomorrow night's dinner.
- Mom!
Bart took what I said
and turned it into an insult!
That's nice, dear!
Okay, Mr. Peanut,
you think you can keep-
[ Sputtering ]
A three-chambered peanut!
Marge, look what I did!
Come quick! Hurry!
Marge?
- Marge, you've been out there all morning.
- So?
So, lying on the couch and eating stuff
isn't the same if you aren't around to see it.
Oh, I'll come watch you
do nothing after I try out...
my new high-intensity
halogen headlights.
[ Laughs ]
Nobody will ever cut me off again.
Ah, please come in!
Maggie smells bad, and the cat wants
something, but I don't know what.
I'm almost done.
And tell Bart to get out of my purse.
[ No Audible Dialogue ]
- [ Marge ] S.U. V. coming through.
- [ Horn Honking ]
- Open up for Marge. Thank you.
- [ Honking Continues ]
Thank- Whoa.!
And daylight.!
Come on.! Come on.!
- [ Honking Continues ]
- Geez. Try the gas pedal, Grandma.
It's right there next to the brake.
- Oh, for God's s- Go back to New Jersey.
- [ Horn Honks ]
[ Tires Squeal, Screech ]
[ Muttering ]
- [ Muffled Shout ]
- [ Honks ]
Come on, come on!
Get that corpse off the road!
The streets are for the living!
- [ Both ] Whoa!
- Slow down, you maniac!
Show some respect for this
coffin full of bricks...
representing
a young man lost at sea.
- Hey!
- [ Siren Wailing ]
Oh, great. What did I do?
- This better be important.
- Can the sweet talk, Thelma & Louise.
You have a serious mental illness.
The technical term is ''road rage.''
I'll see you tomorrow morning
at traffic school, speedy.
And you got exactly five seconds
to get out of my sight.
- [ Grumbles ]
- [ Tires Squeal ]
[ Sighs ]
Why are the pretty ones always insane?
[ Marge Groaning ]
Okay. I assume you all know
why you're here.
That's right.
You're all angry...
- sick people.
- [ Snoring ]
But over these next eight hours, you will be
broken down to the level of infants...
then rebuilt as functional
members of society...
then broken down again,
then lunch...
then, if there's time,
rebuilt once more.
All right, roll it, Lou.
## [ Instrumental ]
Hello. I'm Sergeant Crew...
and I'm here
to talk to you about...
road... rage.
- Duh!
- Quiet, fatso! The sergeant's talking!
Go on, dear.
In these modern,
hectic days of fast food...
answering machines and one-night stands,
people are getting angrier.
Now, what you're about
to see is not pretty.
Cut me off, will you?
[ Grunting ]
- [ Horn Honking ]
- Learn to drive, dimwit!
I sentence you to kiss my ass.
[ Screaming ]
Look familiar? It should.
Anger is what
makes America great.
But you must find
the proper outlet for your rage.
Fire a weapon
at your television screen...
pick a fight with someone
weaker than you...
or write a threatening letter
to a celebrity.
So when you go out for a drive...
remember to leave your murderous
anger where it belongs- at home.
[ Applause ]
And as if that film wasn't enough,
we have a special guest.
Why, it's Curtis E. Bear,
the courtesy bear.
## [ Hums ]
For the next three hours, this bear will
take your verbal and physical abuse...
with good nature and aplomb.
So, if you'll all just grab one of these
two-by-fours-
Um, Chief, can I at least
shield my crotch?
Bears can't talk, Eddie.
- [ Shouting ]
- [ Eddie Gasps ]
- [ Blows Landing ]
- [ Chattering ]
Well, Simpson,
did you learn something today?
Oh, did I ever.
And that herbal anger rinse
just washed the rage right out of me.
And remember, Midge, you feel
the need to rage, you call me, right?
I won't even get sexual or nothin'-
unless that's what you want.
- [ Door Opens, Closes ]
- But that's not what you want, right?
No, thanks.
But thanks.
[ Chattering ]
After you, sweetheart.
Oh, no. You first, ma'am.
Well, somebody go first.
- Well, not me.
- I'm not goin' until she goes.
Oh, for crying out loud!
Oh. Oh. Okay.
Calm down.Just think.
What would Curtis E. Bear do?
- [ Honking ]
- Move it! I gotta return this suit!
[ Tires Screeching ]
Hmm.
Get out of the way!
-[ Tires Screeching ]
- Oh, no! No!
[ Horn Honking ]
[ Screams ]
- Ya!
- [ Alarm Wailing ]
We're free! We're free!
Whoa! Thanks, chick-dude.
Well, I hope you're happy, Simpson.
Those prisoners were one day away
from being completely rehabilitated.
I'm tearing up your license.
Ah, geez. Darned laminated-
Would you mind? I got stubby fingers.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Groans ]
How could they take away my license?
- It feels like I lost a limb.
- Well, that's a turnoff.
Hey, why don't you come
to the wild animal park with us?
No. Your father drives
like an old lady.
At least I've got a license.
- [ Groans ]
- Come on, kids. I went too far.
- [ Door Slams ]
- [ Sighs ]
[ Elephant Trumpets ]
- [ Growling ]
- [ Trumpeting Continues ]
Ah, what a gyp.
They're all just lyin' around.
Do something!
Bart, they're not here
to entertain us.
I've seen plays
that were more exciting than this.
Honest to God. Plays!
[ Animal Calling ]
I don't wanna pay four bucks to watch
some monkey wannabe laying in the sun!
But, Dad, lemurs are nocturnal.
Don't worry, honey.
Daddy will fix that broken animal.
- No!
- I'm not gonna hurt him.
I'm just gonna wake him up.
[ Shrieking ]
[ Shrieks ]
[ Roars ]
- [ Snarling ]
- [ All Growl ]
[ All Snarling, Grunting ]
Uh-oh. Here's a slingshot, Lisa.
[ Australian Accent ] I told 'em
a chain link fence wouldn't hold rhinos.
Oh, wait. No, I didn't.
I meant to tell 'em.
[ Shrieks, Muffled Grunting ]
[ Muffled Laughing ]
[ Screaming ]
- [ Screaming ]
- [ Snarling ]
Don't worry, kids.
I know just what to do.
-Jumanji!
- [ All Snarling ]
Does anything from the movies
actually work?
[ Both Whimpering ]
- [ Both Grunt ]
- Ah, nuts!
Isn't there anybody who can
round up these thunder lizards?
Uh, they'd need
a pretty rugged vehicle.
- And a heart to match.
- Hmm.
I'd like to help you, Chief,
but my license was revoked.
Seems I'm full of rage.
Then do it for this adorable
little puppy.
Look at the puppy, Marge.
- That's your hat.
- She's good, Chief.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I've got some dust that needs busting.
- [ People Screaming ]
- This is Kent Brockman...
at the scene of
a level three rhino alert.
- [ Screaming ]
- Authorities say there's no
immediate danger to anyone-
except those three luckless people
whom we'll identify...
once the rhinos
spit out their wallets.
- [ Gasps ]
- Back! Back, I say!
[ Snarling ]
Oh, no! I'm out of popcorn!
- Throw your peanuts!
- You throw your peanuts!
[ All Screaming ]
- [ Tires Screeching ]
- [ Horn Honking ]
- [ Bart ] Look! It's Mom!
- Out of the way!
- [ Honks ]
- Move it or lose it! Get going, you!
[ Horn Honking ]
This ought to hold 'em.
There's one missing, mate. If we don't find him,
it'll be my ass on the barbie!
- [ Snarling ]
- [ All Whimpering ]
[ Horn Honking ]
- Get in! Get in!
- [ Both Grunt ]
- Come on, Homer!Jump!
- [ Grunts ]
Oh! When will Detroit build a sunroof
for the husky gentleman?
- [ Shrieks ]
- [ Snarling ]
[ Screaming, Whimpering ]
[ Screaming ]
Ah, no!
[ People Gasping ]
[ Whimpering, Sobbing ]
Hey, anybody seen Homer today?
- Here. [ Babbling ]
- There he goes.
[ Screaming ]
Ow!
- It's not my rhino!
- [ All Gasp ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Screams ]
Oh, thank you, God.
And thank you, Port-a-John.
You really saved my-
[ Screams ]
Who's out there?
[ Shrieks ]
Oh, I'm gonna die!
Jesus, Allah, Buddha,
I love you all!
- [ Groans ]
- [ Homer ] Nice rhino.
[ Gasps ]
Oh, no! She's not gonna make it.
Hmm. Looks like it's time
for plan ''B.''
One, two...
three, ''B''!
[ Grunts ]
[ Shrieks, Snarling ]
It's okay, Homie.
You can come out now.
Uh, give me a minute.
[ Grunting, Yelps ]
Oh, Marge! You saved me!
Wow! You are so much cooler
than Milhouse's mom.
Yeah. Way to channel
that rage, Simpson.
How did you know your plan
would work, Mom?
Thanks for asking.
Well, I was watching Dateline...
and Stone Phillips said S.U.V.'s
always roll over when you turn sharply...
and the gas tanks explode
at the drop of a hat.
And she also knew
if a rhino sees a flame...
he'll instinctively
try to put it out.
Stone Phillips again.
Is there anything
that guy doesn't know?
Why, this Stone Phillips
sounds like quite a bloke.
What television network
is he on?
Why, NBC, of course.
NBC has lots of great shows, and their
news and sports coverage can't be beat.
Do you think there's anything great
on NBC right now?
Oh, I'm sure of it.
But there's only one way
to find out.
[ Homer ] I'd like to read
the following statement...
- but I do so under-
- [ Gun Cocks ]
my own free will.
''It has come to my attention
that NBC sucks.
''I apologize for misleading you and urge you
to watch as many Fox shows as possible.
So, in summary, NBC bad, Fox good. ''
CBS great.
- [ Gunshot ]
- [ Body Hits Ground ]
[ Gunshots Continue ]
- [ Gunshot ]
- [ Body Hits Ground ]
[ Gunshots Continue ]
www.tvsubtitles.net