## [ Chorus Singing ]
[ Bell Ringing ]
[ Whistle Blowing ]
[ Beeping ]
## [Jazzy Solo ]
[ Tires Screeching ]
D'oh!
[ Screams ]
- 'Scuse me. Pardon me. 'Scuse me.
- [ Marge Groans ]
- Hmm.
- Hey.
Ah, but Paris would make a tres bon site
for the next Olympic Games.
And why is that?
We don't have to explain ourselves
to the likes of you!
I await your reply.
I recommend Moscow, where
the American dollar buys seven rubles.
- [ Pager Beeps ]
- Twelve rubles.
- [ Beeping Continues ]
- Sixty rubles. 1 ,000 rubles! I must go!
- I suggest Motown.
- Detroit.
No, no. Mongolia Town-
home of the Motown sound.
## [ Vocalizing ]
You are all crazy!
The answer is Buenos Aires.
- Hokkaido!
- Budapest.!
- Cleveland!
- England!
- Bangkok!
- People! People! Please.
You are forgetting what
the Olympics are all about-
giving out medals
of beautiful gold...
so-so silver and shameful bronze.
- [ All Murmuring ]
- [ Woman ] It's so true.
I have here a letter
from a little girl named Lisa Simpson.
She says her town might not be important
enough to host the Olympics...
but she asks if the torch
could just pass by...
so she can experience the glow
that we feel every day.
Well, I say we don't
bring her the torch.
I say we bring her...
the Olympic Games!
- Who is with me?
- [ Cricket Chirps ]
Well, I don't care.
It's my decision.
Springfield was shocked today
to learn it will host the next Olympics.
Economists predict our city
will experience the same boom...
that Sarajevo enjoyed
after the 1 984 Games.
And it's all because
of your letter, Lisa.
Well, actually, I just wrote it
for a school assignment.
Everyone else wrote
to the Backstreet Boys.
To honor the arrival
of our foreign friends- and enemies-
Channel 6 is sponsoring a contest
to find a Springfield Olympic mascot.
The winner will join
such other memorable mascots...
as the Atlanta whatsit
and the Montreal vampire.
A mascot contest?
I'm sure to win that-
unless one of you jinxes me.
No one's gonna jinx you, Homer.
In fact, we're rooting for you.
- Yeah. Go for the gold, Dad.
- Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Well, you said I couldn't do it,
but here it is.
Meet Abby, the Olympic Tabby!
[ Bart ]
How'd you get the eyes to move?
- [ Plaintive Meowing ]
- [ Gasps ] You papier-mached my cat?
Just for the prototype, honey.
[ Meows ]
- [ Hisses ]
- [ Yelps ]
Knowing you always hate my first idea,
I prepared a backup.
How about a big Olympic hello
for Springy-
the Springfield spring!
[ Bart ]
Those aren't the dog's eyes, are they?
- Hey, that's cute.
- Good work, Dad.
It's fun for the whole family.
And the ends are razor sharp-
to protect our nation
and its interests.
- Ow!
- God bless America.
[ Spray Can Rattles ]
- [ Squeaking ]
- Hit the road, Lefty. You too, Rizzo.
- [ Chirps ]
- Oh, Cinnamon, don't make this
harder than it already is.
[ Crowd Cheering ]
Bravo, Springfield.
- I have never seen such a clean sewer.
- [ Chuckles ]
And we are positively inspired
by your solar power plant.
Yes. Love that sun, man.
We will do anything, including
but not limited to anything...
to make your stay here tolerable.
Yes. You'll be completely
above the law.
Uh, women, guns, cash-
whatever you need. It's yours.
- [ Man ] Ach du Lieber.!
- [ Wolf Whistle ]
- [ All Murmuring ]
- And that's not all.
We've just chosen
our official Olympic mascot.
- [ Crowd Oohs and Aahs ]
- [ Applause ]
[ Gasps ]
They picked Springy!
In your face, Patty and Selma!
- Well, we still love you, Ciggy.
- Yeah.
Mmm! That glue really
gives it a pop.
And now, because the children
are our future...
here are the children
of Springfield Elementary...
with a song they call
''The Children Are Our Future.''
- Children?
- ##[ Up Tempo ]
## [ Singing ]
##[ Continues ]
I've never wanted a beer
worse in my life.
[ Gasp ]
I love you, honey.
Are you talking to me or the beer?
To you, my bubbly, long-necked,
beechwood-aged lover.
## [ Continue Singing ]
- ## [ Ends ]
- Bravo!
Magnifigue.!
Muy bueno.
It gives me great pride
to officially declare...
the next Olympics
will be held right here in-
Wait! Wait!
We have one more act.
The patriotic comedy stylings
of Bart Simpson!
- [ Man ] Oh, fine.
- Thank you, thank you.
- So, uh, you're from Russia, huh?
- Da.
- You drunk yet?
Poland, eh? [ Chuckles ]
Too easy.
How ya doin', Germany? Here's my impression
of an East German woman.
''Kees'' me, or I'll crush you.
[ Laughing Hysterically ]
- He says what we're all thinking.
- I'm not thinking that.
Hey, Swiss miss.
There's no missin' you, babe.
- Lay off the cocoa.
- [ Laughter ]
[ Mutters In German ]
Now I'd like to say one last thing
to our Olympic representatives.
If there was a medal for horrible audiences,
you'd get the gold.
- Peace out.
- [ Loud Feedback ]
[ Gasps, Grunts ]
[ Tires Screeching ]
Skinner!
How could you put this boy on
with that horrible material?
Well, it really did
seem funny in rehearsal.
- And he didn't even get to his Ubangi routine.
- [ Laughing ]
Ha, ha, ha.
Laugh it up, ya punks.
'Cause you and Jan Murray here
just cost our town the Olympics.
- Hey, Chalmers. Where are you from?
- Huh?
Well, I was born in Queens,
went to Ball State...
then made the move
to Intercourse, Pennsylvania.
- Uh, why do you ask?
- Don't worry, sir.
I'll teach these children
some respect for their town.
I'm assigning each of you
20 hours of community service.
- [ Groaning, Grumbling ]
- Community service?
- No, no!
- Intercourse?
- What if we refuse?
- You won't pass to the next grade.
I fail to see the threat.
Skinner! Good idea.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm off to my vacation at Lake Titicaca.
Let's see you make a joke
out of that, Mr. Smart Guy.
All right, Martin.
For your community service...
you'll be setting up a midnight basketball
program for inner-city street gangs.
All right, gang.
Shirts and skins.
- Let's hustle.
- [ Gunshot ]
[ Tires Screeching ]
- Milhouse, do you like the beach?
- Who doesn't?
Good.
I want you to pick up
all this medical waste...
that's washed up on the shore here.
Ow! I pricked myself.
Well,just keep working.
You'll prick yourself with the antidote
sooner or later.
[ Sighs ]
- What are ya gonna do to me?
- Bart, not all community service...
is gang warfare
and dangerous infection.
And to illustrate that point,
here's where you'll be working.
The fireworks, candy
and puppy dog store?
[ Puppies Yipping ]
No, no, no.
Next to it.
Settle a bet.
Boil or mole?
[ Groans ]
Okay.Just breathe
through your mouth...
and don't ask how they're feeling.
##[ Muzak ]
- [ All Groaning ]
- [ Creaking ]
Oh, man.
- [ Wheezing Groan ]
- [ Yelps ] Whoa!
- [ Grunts ]
- [ Dentures Chattering ]
- Aren't you a beautiful-
- Let's pull his skin.
- [ Yelps ]
- Look at that.
Oh, be a dear and snap my support hose
to my girdle.
[ Shuddering ]
2:00. Recreation time.
- Oh, goody!
- Whew! Saved by the bell. Whoa!
- Where do you think you're goin'?
- [ Gulps ]
Oh, no.
Lise, they got you too?
Got me?
What are you talking about?
I got a nice diagonal goin' here.
B-3.
- You sunk my battleship.
- [ All Laughing ]
G-52.
- You sunk my battleship.
- [ All Laughing ]
Oh! I got a bingo!
What do I win?
- A banana.
- A whole one?
- Yep.
- That's the prize? A banana?
Their natural mushiness prevents choking
and promotes regularity.
They're not babies, Lisa.
Give 'em something fun-
like cigars or booze.
We tried giving them
eggnog at Christmas...
but it led to widespread
''de-shawling.''
Well, that's what they get for wearing
such tight little shawls.
- Oh!
- [ Chuckles ]
- Okay. 4:00. Nap time.
- [ All Snoring ]
- You tell 'em when to sleep?
- [ Whispering ] Shh. Don't wake them.
[ Vacuums Whirring ]
While they sleep,
we suck up excess dirt and crumbs.
Here you go. Make sure
you get into every crevice.
- [ Snoring ]
- Cool.
Grampa. Homer.
Don't play with the faces.
So, Bart, how was your first day
of forced volunteerism?
That place sucks. The nurses don't let
Grampa do anything.
They practically
chew his food for him.
Lucky stiff.
I'm workin' my ass off here.
Good steak, honey.
The elderly aren't
like you or me, Bart.
They thrive on consistency,
predictability...
and a life with no surprises.
Sounds good to me.
- [ Doorbell Rings ]
- I'll get it!
- [ Laughing ]
- Delivery for Homer Simpson.
[ Grunting ]
Mmm! Whoo-hoo!
My springs.
They finally came.
But we lost the Olympics
to Shelbyville.
Yeah, but I should have no problem
selling a thousand springs.
- To who?
- Idiots.
Ooh! These are fun.
Oh, Rhett! Rhett!
Oh, Rhett.
Where will I go?
- What'll I do?
- Frankly, my dear-
[ Different Male Voice ]
I love you. Let's remarry.
- Ahh. That's sweet.
- What a lovely ending.
They cut out the best word.
Didn't that movie
used to have a war in it?
Come on, you. You've been warned.
- Picture yourself on a beautiful sailboat.
- [ Waves Lapping, Gulls Crying ]
Ah. Can't you just feel
the sea breeze in your hair?
- [ Man ] Oh, boy.
- Or scalps.
Say, I hear a foghorn.
[ Imitating Foghorn ]
Boring!
Come on, Bart. We don't want to overstimulate
these people. They just had pudding.
[ Doorbell Rings ]
Hello, little girl.
Is your mommy home?
You'll need to ask her for five dollars
to buy Mr. Bouncy Best Friend.
I know you. Your little smart-mouthed boy
cost this town the Olympics.
- [ Agnes Grunts ]
- [ Skinner ] Who is it, Mother?
- Bart Simpson's father.
- Oh. I'll be right down.
[ Footsteps ]
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
[ Grunting ]
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Boy, Lenny,you sure look hungry.
- Have some nuts.
- Hey, thanks.
- Ow! My eye! Ow! Ow! Ow!
- [ Chuckling ]
Now, if you wanna be the life of the party
like Lenny here...
just place your order
for this hilarious novelty item.
- [ Lenny Screaming ]
- Homer, get outta here.
Boy, Moe, you sure look angry.
- Here. Have some nuts.
- Hey, thanks.
Ow! God! My eye!
- Ow! Get it out! Geez! Gaagh!
- [ Lenny Yelping ]
Don't pull. Don't pull.
[ Groans ]
I said don't pull! Don't.!
Now we're pulling into port.
Ah! And who's waiting
for us at the dock?
Why, it's all your childhood dogs!
I see Petey and Blackie
and Schnoodle.
- Oh, no! Pirates!
- Pirates!
Ahoy, mateys! It's me-
Long Bart Silver.
- And I'm gonna rip you a new I.V. hole.
- [ All Gasp, Shudder]
- Bart, what are you doing?
- I'm just trying to liven things up around here.
These people need to ride motorcycles
and play rockin' electric guitars...
like the old people on TV.
Excuse me. But when
those pirates boarded...
I swallowed my wedding ring
for safekeeping.
- Get me some ipecac. I'd like to expunge it.
- [ Sighs ]
Okay, she's gone.
Let's break out of here and have some fun.
- Shouldn't we ask someone first?
- If I get up, somebody will take my chair.
Got that right.
It's the only one left with padding.
[ All ]
Padding.
[ Sighs ]
What about you, Chief?
Don't you wanna be free
like the eagle?
Oh, I don't live here. I'm just
dropping off Indian casino pamphlets.
Vote ''yes'' on Prop 21 7.
[ Grunts ]
You know, the door was open,
Chief Break Everything.
Come on, people. You don't wanna stay in
a place where they vacuum you while you sleep.
- They do what now?
- Now's our chance. Let's go!
- [ All Shouting ]
- [ Woman ] I'm gonna follow him.
Oh, no. Bart has stolen the elderly.
[ Yelps ]
Forgot my hat.
- ##['60s Pop ]
- [ Cheering, Whooping ]
Oy!
[ Laughing ]
[ Shouting ]
[ Both Grunting ]
Oy!
[ Murmurs ]
Uh-oh!
##[ Ends ]
Ow! Today's grass is far sharper
than the grass in my day.
Hey, everybody.! How'd you like
to go on a real boat trip?
- Oh, that would be nice.
- I'm there!
Arr! Not a looker among 'em.
Full speed ahead!
Damn the torpedoes!
What'd he say?
Put on our tuxedos?
I want some taquitos.
[ Homer ]
Welcome to the kitchen of tomorrow- today.!
- How much would you pay for
a self-flipping hamburger pan?
- Nothing.
Don't answer yet. Watch how easy it is
to flip hamburgers...
with the help of God's
greatest creation- the spring!
Now watch this.
[ Screaming ]
[ Moans ]
- Are you okay?
- Some second-degree burns.
But some first-class burgers.
[ Groans ]
I want you to get rid of these springs.
But you haven't seen
the baby of tomorrow.
Ta-da!
- Now if I drop her, no more tears.
- [ Gasps ]
## [ Humming Basketball Theme ]
- Give me my baby!
- ''D'' it up, Marge. I'm goin' to the hole.
[ Marge ]
I want these springs out of our house today.!
[ Toilet Flushing ]
## [ Singing Drinking Song ]
You're not flushing those springs
down our toilet, are you?
- Of course not.
- [ Toilet Flushes ]
##[ Singing ]
[ Groaning ]
Mm-mm-mm.
##[ Big Band ]
## [ Continues ]
Oh, Abe, you dance divinely.
I haven't felt this relaxed
and carefree...
since I was watch commander
at Pearl Harbor.
Aw, geez. This place used to be
crawlin' with Russian subs.
Now there's just four.
- [ Gasps ] Sea hag.!
- Bart Simpson!
Bart, are you crazy?
You've got to get the old folks home
to the old folks' home.
No way. They're finally
having some fun.
- ##[ Calypso ]
- How low can I go?
- [ Bone Snaps ]
- [ Yelps ] That's it.
- Gee, Bart, maybe you're right.
- [ Watch Alarm Beeps ]
They don't even seem to care
that it's medication time.
- Medication time? Hot dog!
- [ All Murmuring ]
- Gimme, gimme, gimme!
- [ Chattering ]
But I've set you free.
No more nap time. No more bingo.
You can do whatever you want.
- Let's play bingo.
- Yeah! Let's play bingo.
- You sunk my battleship.
- [ All Laughing ]
[ Sighs ]
Now, Smithers,you say you painted
all your navy buddies this way?
Until I was discharged, sir.
I don't get it, Grampa.
If you guys like all that boring stuff...
why did you follow me out here?
Gotta do somethin' till bingo.
[ All Gasp ]
[ All Screaming ]
How could you miss that huge boat
coming right at us?
- Oh. Two glass eyes.
- [ Clink, Clink ]
Oh, it's not fair.
I'm not supposed to die now.
I'm supposed to die in a foolish
motorcycle stunt at the age of 1 5.
Ha, ha! You're not dead yet,
you pudgy little pisher.
- [ Together] Jack La Lanne!
- Don't worry.
I'll save you theJack La Lanne way!
[ Grunts ]
[ All Cheering ]
- [ Yelping ]
- [ All Screaming ]
Uh-oh.
- This is all Bart's fault.
- Let's get him.
- I blame him.
- He's killed us all.
I want some taquitos.
Leave him alone!
Sure, Bart's responsible
for our deaths.
But he gave us the most fun
we had in 20 years.
So before we go
to our watery graves...
I say that we-
[ Gurgling ]
[ All Screaming ]
[ All Sigh ]
[ All Scream, Sigh ]
What the heck's going on?
##[ Homer Singing, Echoing ]
Ah. What a shame.
Not a looker in the bunch.
So, you workin' tomorrow
at the home, Bart?
Well, I finished
my community service.
Oh. Right.
But I could swing by after school.
- I'll bring the limbo stick.
- Hot diggety!
## [ Humming Calypso ]
## [ Vocalizing ]
Hey. Stop shakin' the harness.
How low can I go!
[ Water Splashes ]
##['60s Pop ]
[ Loud Shout ]
##[ Ends ]
www.tvsubtitles.net