##[ Chorus Singing ]
[ Bell Ringing ]
[ Whistle Blowing ]
[ Beeping ]
## [Jazzy Solo ]
[ Tires Screeching ]
D'oh!
[ Screams ]
[ All Shout ]
Hey, why didn't you tell me
the new issue of Weird was here?
[ Chuckles ]
I love their hilarious send-ups of hit movies.
- Dad, it's not-
- ''Gigabytes.''
[ Laughing ]
They've done it again.
''Gigabytes.'' Wait-This isn't Weird.
Why, there's no magazine
called Weird, is there?
This is Wired.
It's about computers and technology.
Hey, look. There's a cybercafe
opening right here in Springfield.
Will you take me, Dad? Please?
I'll show you how to order pizza
over the Internet.
The Internet? Is that thing still around?
I know a Web site
that shows monkeys doin' it.
Bart, the Internet is more
than a global pornography network.
- It's a-
- [ Horn Honks ]
- Come on, Lisa. Monkeys.
- [ Groans ]
Ach. Let's see what's been captured
on the up-kilt camera.
[ Beeps, Whirs ]
Ew. This lass needs
a bit of grounds keeping.
Eh? Aah! That's Willie!
My name is Mary.
I'm 45, heavy and willing
to settle for less.
Wow. This Mary's got
the whole package.
Wow, Dad. You're surfin' like a pro.
Oh, yeah. I'm betting on jai alai
in the Cayman Islands.
I invested in something
called News Corp-
- Dad! That's Fox!
- [ Screams ]
Undo! Undo!
[ Groans ]
Dad, do we have any money left?
Well, let's check
the old bank account.
- [ Beeps ]
- See? Even after my cyber squandering...
we've still got $1 ,200.
- All right, dorks, this is a holdup.
- [ Gasping, Murmuring ]
Oh, yes!
Download to papa.
- [ Beeping ]
- Yoink dot adios, back-slash losers.
- [ Groans ]
- [ Marge ] We were robbed?
You seem to know an awful lot
about this for an innocent person.
We were saving that money
for our family vacation.
Now we're gonna have
to start all over again.
- [ Groans ]
- Aw, don't worry, sweetheart.
I'll get us the money-
even if I have to get a second job.
Evenin', neighbor.
Low on funds again?
- Yes, sir.
- Now, Homer, we can't have you burglarizing us...
every time you got a bill to pay.
I know, sir. I'm sorry, sir.
It's just that you and Maude live
like royalty in your fancy castle...
while I got Marge trapped
over there like a pig in a mud beehive.
Oh, we're-We're not
as well off as you think.
We give to eight different churches
just to hedge our bets...
and the Leftorium's business
has gone way down hill...
since Leftopolis moved in next door.
If you're not rich, then how come
you have a new refrigerator...
an electric can opener,
a milk shake machine?
[ Chuckling ]
We picked those up cheap.
- They were evidence at a murder trial.
- Sweet.
We got that tip at the Chuck Garabedian
Mega-Savings Seminar.
- Go on.
- He taught us how to live...
a Burt Reynolds lifestyle
on a Mac Davis income.
We've already got tickets
for his next seminar.
I think you'll find living thrifty
a lot more satisfying than stealing.
Maybe you're right, Ned.
Maybe you're right.
Are you tired of missing out
on the good things in life-
Family vacations,jet packs,
Solid Gold Dancers?
There's only three left in the world.
Well, stick around,
'cause I'm gonna tell you...
the 1 2 savings secrets
Wall Street won't tell you.
Then I'll show you the three ways
to get back to the highway-
including one shortcut those
Wall Street fat cats don't want you to know.
- [ Cheering ]
- Oh, here we go with the fat-cat bashing.
Well, what do you expect?
These yokels are pure Baltic Avenue.
[ Chuckles ]
Uh-oh! I'm late for the Short Line Railroad.
[ Tires Squeal ]
Let's start with mega secret number one:
''Ya gotta squeeze every penny.''
You see this tux? I got it cheap
'cause Roy Cohn died in it.
- [ Murmuring ]
- That fancy yacht?
A bargain, 'cause it smells like cat pee.
- [ Murmuring ]
- And those beautiful women?
- They used to be men.
- [ Groaning ]
The point is, ya gotta squeeze every penny.
Come on, let me hear you.
[ Together]
Squeeze every penny. Squeeze every penny.
I'm squeezing. I'm squeezing it.
- [ Slurping Sound ]
- Hey, I squeezed so hard it went into my hand.
Oh, Homer, not again.
Ew. We're gonna do our grocery
shopping at a 99-cent store?
Well, maybe for your wedding.
- [ Bart ] How about here?
- Not if we want that vacation.
Look, Mom. They have your dress.
[ Groans ]
Thirty-three cents? I paid almost double that.
Blue?
Wow! This plankton's only 33 cents.
According to the Mexican
Council of Food...
this expired two years ago.
Sure, by their standards,
but we live in America.
[ Chomping, Groaning ]
This also says it can cause
red tide poisoning.
But it's so cheap.
Well, let's see what's
in the old vacation fund.
Homer, you could have
just unscrewed the bottom.
A little late for
''could-haves,'' Marge.
I don't think there's
enough here for a vacation.
There is for a Mega-Savings vacation.
Chuck Garabedian says
you can fly mega cheap...
if you don't care where you go.
That's right.Just go to the airport
and wait for some no-shows.
Then you can buy their seats
for a fraction of the price.
Are you going through our garbage?
That's right. You fat cats
didn't finish your plankton.
Now it's mine.
Hawaii, here we come.
No. No. We're going to Paris. I can feel it.
Come on, Transylvania.
[ With Jamaican Accent ]
No, mon, let's go home toJamaica.
I and I been in Babylon too long.
[ Woman On P.A.] Attention.
Flight 605 to Tokyo is ready for departure...
and has four available
mega-saver seats.
- [ Both ] Yeah!
- Come on, Homer.Japan.
No, notJapan,Jamaica. I wanna
pass the dutchie on the left-hand side.
Never mind. Looks like the Flanders
are gonna get those seats anyway.
Oh, so Flanders thinks
he can steal our vacation, huh?
- [ Groans ]
- Come on!
- Whoo!
- [ Horn Honking ]
- Sayonara, suckers.
- [ Snarls ]
Yea! The Simpsons
are going toJapan.
[ Gong Sounds ]
Hey, watch the gong,jerk.
Come on, Homer.
Japan will be fun.
- You liked Rashomon.
- That's not how I remember it.
Besides, if we wanna see
Japanese people...
- we could have gone to the zoo.
- Homer!
What? The guy who washes
the elephants is Japanese.
His name is Takashi.
He's in my book club.
Look, Mom. The safety instructions
are written in haiku.
''Fasten seat belts tight.
''Your seat cushions float gently.
Headsets, five dollars.''
[ Beeping ]
Sir, it is not safe
to use electronic devices yet.
- You're the waitress.
- [ Beeps ]
[ Attendant ]
Turn it back on.! Turn it back on.!
Ooh. I never knew Jim Belushi
made so many movies.
Yeah, isn't it amazing?
They're filming one right now in the bathroom.
Gonna be on towards the end of the flight.
Toga! Toga! Toga 2,000!
Marge, they stole my idea.
The local time is... tomorrow.
[ Homer]
Here's our room.
Homer, you're supposed
to slide those doors open.
I don't have time for that.
[ Grunts ]
[ Man's Voice ]
Welcome. I am honored to accept your waste.
- [ Beeps ]
- ## [ Bells ]
[ Gasps ]
They're years ahead of us.
Mom! Lise! Check it out. Dad's on TV.
- Oh, yeah!
- [ Marge, Bart, Lisa Screaming ]
[ Gasps ]
It's breathtaking.
Look. There's the Imperial Gardens.
The Meiji Shrine.
The Hello Kitty factory.
[ Cats Yowling ]
[ Yowling Stops ]
Who's up for some exploring?
- Hey, I'm still checking outJapanese TV.
- ## [ Synthesizers ]
Isn't this that cartoon
that causes seizures?
[ Beeping ]
[ Grunting, Groaning ]
Bart, what are you doing?
Hey, what the-
[ Grunting, Groaning ]
Hmm. All right.
- Robots be right back.
- Whoo!
- All that seizing made me hungry.
- Me too.
Let's go to an authentic
Japanese noodle house.
The toilet recommended
a place called Americatown.
Dad, we didn't come halfway
around the world to eat at Americatown.
I'd like to see theJapanese take
on the club sandwich.
I bet it's smaller
and more efficient.
[ Man ]
We now return to Battling Seizure Robots.
- [ Beeping ]
- [ All Moaning ]
[ Mechanical Clicking ]
I can't believe they stuck us
at ''Tax-a-chusetts.''
- Hey, you know, I once knew a man
from Nantucket.
- And?
Let's just say the stories about him
are greatly exaggerated.
Howdy, gangstas.
I am average American Joe
salary-man waiter.
These prices suck.
1 0,000 yen for coleslaw?
Don't you serve anything
that's even remotelyJapanese?
Don't ask me. I don't know anything.
I am product of American
education system.
I also build poor-quality cars
and inferior-style electronics.
[ Laughs ]
Oh, they got our number.
One square watermelon, please.
Oh, my goodness.
Homer, those are $1 50.
It's worth every cent.
I'm tired of fumbling
with round fruit. D'oh!
Well, maybe we should
just head back to the hotel.
But you promised me
we'd do something Japanese.
Oh, of course you're right.
You know, I read
about a Shinto teahouse...
where they practice
the traditional- Run, Bart!
- Hey. Isn't that Woody Allen?
- Hmm. Looks like he's doing a commercial.
Oh! [ Clears Throat ]
Hello.
[ Clears Throat ]
So many rice crackers claim to be low-cal...
but only Fujikawa rice crackers
make your interiors go bananas.
What did I do to deserve this?
Oh, right.
Mmm. Fifty-dollar pretzels.
Hey, what's Baby Huey doin'?
- Says here they throw salt before
they wrestle to purify the ring.
- Hmm.
- Spare some salt, tubby?
- Tubby?
[ Speaking Japanese ]
- Yoink.
- Hey, that's mine! [ Yells ]
- Hey.
- [ Grunts ]
- [ Crowd Groans ]
- Like we say in my county, ''Hasta la vista, baby.''
Congratulations.
I am the emperor.
Yeah? And I'm ''clobber-saurus.''
[ Gasping, Sighing ]
All hail Emperor Clobbersaurus.
[ Booing ]
Your wife has paid your bail,
Mr. Simpson-san.
Thank God. Couldn't take another
minute in this hellhole.
[ Chomping ]
Now can we do something Japanese?
Oh, I'm sick of doing Japanese stuff.
In jail we had to be in this dumb
Kabuki play about the 47 Ronin...
and I wanted to be Yoshi,
but they made me Ori.
Then we had to do two hours of origami...
followed by flower arranging
and meditation.
[ Speaking Japanese ]
Honey, I know you wanna seeJapan...
but we're down to our last million yen.
Don't worry, ichiban.
I'll show you something Japanese.
Oh, it's beautiful, Dad.
It's a crane. TheJapanese believe
they bring good luck.
Oh, be careful.
We need that money to get home.
- [ Marge Gasps ] No!
- [Japanese ]
[ Man ]
Now, Mr. Simpson...
I know you lost all your money,
but don't worry.
The United States
will not stand idly by...
while one of its citizens
is stuck here like this.
[ Grunts, Groans ]
But, Mr. Ambassador,
how are we going to get home?
Beats me. Try getting a job
and earning some money.
That's what I did.
By the way, ''ambassador'' is taken.
[ Groaning ]
Every truckload of fish we gut...
brings us 31 cents closer
to those tickets home.
And I think I finally found
what I was put on this Earth to do.
Knife goes in, guts come out.
Spare my life and I will
grant you three wi-
- [ Screams ]
- Knife goes in, guts come out.
Yippee! Time for the company loyalty song.
## [ Singing ]
[ Groans ]
Well, this sucks.
What else is on?
- [ Bell Ringing ]
- [ Cheering ]
[ Laughs ]
Thank you.
You have fulfilled our dreams,
and dreams of our ancestors.
[ Male Announcer ] Tune in tomorrow,
when another lucky family...
tries to win their dreams...
on Happy Smile Super
Challenge Family Wish Show.
Family Wish Show. Hmm.
That gives me an idea.
I think we all had that idea.
I didn't. What is it? Lunch?
Thank you, thank you.
And welcome to our contestants
from America, the Simpson family.
- You honor us.
- Don't patronize me.
Now, Simpson family,
have you picked a wish?
Well, I haven't talked it over with the family-
[ Chuckles ]
but I think we'd all like
a free dinner at Americatown.
No, no, no. We want
plane tickets home to Springfield.
[ Cheering, Whistling ]
Now, our game shows
are a little different from yours.
Your shows reward knowledge.
We punish ignorance.
Ignor-What?
[ Screams ]
- [ Laughing ]
- Okay, let's begin.
Our categories are:
''Ow. That hurts. ''
''Why are you doing this to me?''
- And ''Please let me die. ''
- [ Bell Dings ]
- ''Ow. That hurts.''
- Oh, yeah, number one. Definitely.
I don't know.
I like ''Why are you doing this?''
- ''Ow. That hurts.''
- We'll go with ''Ow. That hurts,'' Skip.
- My name is Wink.
- [ Groans ]
[ Laughing, Chattering ]
All right, Simpsons,
whack the pinata.
- [ Groaning ]
- Come on!
Whack that pig open.
Once more.
Harder. Whack it open.
- [ Laughing ]
- Good. All right.
You may remove your blindfolds.
- [ Groaning ]
- Oh, sorry, Dad.
- We didn't know.
- I had an inkling.
- Could someone please whack my hernia back in?
- Sure, thing, Dad.
Mr. Simpson, we'll cut you down...
as soon as you answer
one question aboutJapan.
- Is the answer ''Japan''?
- Actually, it is.
[ Speaking Japanese ]
That means you move on
to the lightning round.
- [ Moans ]
- [ Thunder Rumbling ]
- [ Screams ]
- He seems okay...
but he is being burned internally.
[ Screaming ]
Hey, isn't that Homer
on theJapanese Channel?
If that's Homer, then who the hell's
been puttin' beers on his tab?
D'oh. Whoo-hoo.
Uh-That boy ain't right.
[ Host ]
Congratulations, Simpsons.
The airline tickets are yours.
All you have to do
is to pick them up...
from inside that volcano.
- Why are you so cruel?
- [ Laughing ]
This vacation really blows.
Well, at least we're past
the lighting round.
[ Screams ]
Hmm. I see.
I sure hope they don't have an ice cream round.
[ Screams ]
Mmm. I don't think that bridge
can support much weight.
Well, Maggie weighs
a lot less than- Oh, I'll just go.
[ Groaning ]
[ Together] Plummet! Plummet!
Plummet! Plummet!
Plummet.! Plummet.! Plummet.!
Yes! Got 'em.
- [ Together] U.S.A.! U.S.A.! U.S.-
- [ Buzzes ]
[ Screams ]
[ Gasps ]
Lisa!
- [ Screams ]
- [ Grunts ]
- Oh.!
- Marge! Your shoe!
The plane tickets!
[ Grunting ]
Whoa! Whoa!
Oh, I'm afraid this might be the end.
Well, at least we'll die
doing what we love-
inhaling molten rock.
[ All Screaming ]
[ Cheering ]
[ Screams ]
It burns! It burns!
Don't worry, that ''lava''
is just orangeade...
made by our sponsor,
Osaka Orangeade Concern.
- It burns! It burns!
- It's loaded with wasabi.
Kudos, Simpsons.
You have won your freedom.
[ Audience Cheering ]
Before I go, I want to say something.
Game shows aren't about cruelty.
They're about greed
and wonderful prizes...
like poorly built catamarans.
But somewhere along the line,
you lost your way.
- For shame.
- [ Groaning ]
Coming up next, a Canadian couple...
who say they are
deathly afraid of scorpions.
- Oh, that stings, eh.
- [ Screams ]
- Ooh, God! Ow! Ooh!
- [ Screaming ]
Sting those Canucks.
[ Laughs ]
I love this show.
Take that, you stupid hosers.
[ Groans ]
Good-bye,Japan. I'll miss your
Kentucky Fried Chicken...
and your sparkling, whale-free seas.
- Hey, what's goin' on?
- What's happening?
[ Beeping ]
[ Man On P.A.]
Folks, we're experiencing...
some moderate Godzilla-related turbulence
at this time, so I'm gonna go ahead...
- and ask you to put your seat belts back on.
- [ Screeching ]
When we get to 35,000 feet
he usually does let go...
so from there on out,
all we have to do...
- [ Yawning ]
- is worry about Mothra, and we do have reports...
he's tied up with Gamera
and Rodan at the present time.
- Thank you very much.
- [ Roaring, Screeching ]
[ Godzilla Screeches ]
- [ Murmuring ]
- Shh!
[ Homer Screams ]
Undo.! Undo.! [ Groans ]
www.tvsubtitles.net