##[ Chorus Singing ]
[ Bell Ringing ]
[ Whistle Blowing ]
[ Beeping ]
## [Jazzy Solo ]
[ Tires Screeching ]
D'oh!
[ Screams ]
- [ All Gasp ]
- [ Channel Changes ]
[ Snoring ]
[ Chattering ]
Hey, hey.
Settle down, children.
Now, who's ever wondered
how the post office works?
- No one?
- I did until we came here last year.
Ah, yes, last year.
Anyway, look.
Here comes our guide
for the day, Postmaster Bill.
[ Chuckling ]
Howdy, partners.
Welcome to your post office.
Wow! It's ours?
- [ Skinner ] Bart.!
- Be with you in a minute.
This is the lobby
where customers come...
for all their ''postalistic'' needs.
''Legends of comedy,'' my tuchus.!
What has Fatty Arbuckle done
that I haven't done?
This machine reads zip codes.
These five digits tell us
where to direct your mail.
But it's nine digits now. What's the point
of these other four numbers?
Those are citizen relocation codes.
With any luck,
we'll never need 'em.
- She's onto us. Should I flood the chamber?
- Not yet. Let's get some lunch.
Well, children, any questions
for Postmaster Bill?
You ever gone on a killing spree?
No, no. The day of the gun-toting,
disgruntled postman...
shooting up the place
went out with the Macarena.
Well, I'm just glad I work
at an elementary school.
And this is where our employees
gather to unwind...
after a hard day
of serving the public.
Bingo! Birthday card!
- Graduation!
- Ding-ding-ding! Wedding!
[ All Cheering ]
[ Chuckling, Moans ]
I'm sure you all heard
of the dead letter office.
Well, as a souvenir of your visit...
you can each help yourself
to one piece of undeliverable mail.
- [ Cheering ]
- I'll take you.
- [ Growling ]
- I got some dog food!
I got my letter to Santa.
A coupon book? What am I gonna do
with this piece of junk?
- Happy birthday, Dad.
- Wow!
A Val-U-Qual coupon book!
Let's see. Ten percent
off carpet cleaning. Ten!
[ Gasps ] Two pizzas
for the price of one at Doughy's!
- Doughy's has terrible pizza.
- Yeah, but there's two!
Oh, free foot pain analysis.
Oh, Marge. That's just a trick to get you
in there, so they can cure your foot pain.
I guess.
[ Moaning ]
See ya, kids. Me and my Val-U-Qual book
are gonna paint the town red...
with savings!
I'll start with a couple of pizzas,
then a complimentary tango lesson.
And I'll cap it off
with a smooth, refreshing colonic.
- Um, Dad?
- ## [ Singing Upbeat Song ]
##[ Continues ]
Now, this wheel balancing
is free, right?
Oh, you betcha. Absolutely.
Uh, oh, oh, wait a minute.
These tires won't take a balance.
- They won't?
- Nah, no. You hear that clunk?
- No.
- That tells me you need four new tires.
- Really?
- Yeah. Legally, I can't even
let you drive out of here.
Oh, please, can't you let me
slide this time?
Gee, I'd really like to,
but if my boss found out-
What's going on over here? You gonna let
this man drive out of here on unsafe tires?
- No, boss, I swear.
- That's it. You're fired!
No, wait.
This is all my fault.
Oh, if I could only turn back the clock
and buy four new tires.
##[ Instrumental Easy Listening ]
[ Moans ]
Ooh, I know that look. You came in
for the free wheel balance...
and now it's costing you
500 simoleons.
- Six with the tip.
- Hey, you got off easy.
I just came in to use the phone, and they
got me for the whole Road King package-
alignment, shocks,
Armor All, stem lube.
[ Laughing ]
Stem lube.
Even I didn't fall for that,
although winter is coming.
Man, we are a couple
of grade-A suckers.
- Wally Kogen.
- Hey, I know you.
We were in the same
pyramid scheme.
Oh, don't remind me.
Friends helping friends, my ass!
Say, you wanna grab a beer
while we're waiting?
Yeah. I'm getting tired of them
pointing and laughing at us.
[ Man ] The road to the Super Bowl
is long and pointless.
- I mean, when you think about it.
- Football's so great.
But now the two conference
champs must survive...
a harrowing bye week
that no one enjoys.
Bye weeks! Bronco Nagurski
didn't get no bye weeks.
And now he's dead.
Well, maybe they're a good thing.
Yeah, how 'bout that Super Bowl.
You going this year?
Me? Nah.
[ Gasps ]
Unless there's a coupon for it. Nah.
Well, I run the Springfield
Travel Agency.
We've got a charter bus
going down to the game.
You help us fill it,
you can ride for free.
Homer Simpson at the Super Bowl?
Dang! That was my last quarterback.
Now what am I gonna do? You!
- Me?
- Yeah, you. Get your hand off my wife's leg.
Sorry.
It's a deal. Hey, Moe, you wanna come
with me and Wally to the Super Bowl?
Oh, absolutely.
My favorite team's in it.
The Atlanta Falcons.
Yeah, ever since I was a boy,
I've always loved the Atlanta Falcons.
Yeah, they're good, but I wouldn't
count out the Denver Broncos.
Yeah, I hear that
President Clinton...
is gonna be watching
with his wife, Hillary.
Come on, Lenny. I need four more guys
to fill my Super Bowl bus.
- What do you say?
- Nah.
- Come on!
- Oh, come on!
- Ah-
Yes! Now that Lenny's in,
Carl will fall like a domino.
I'm so happy you're going
to the big game.
My dream has always been
to see the Bolshoi Ballet.
Yeah, yeah. Do we have
any pencils that work?
Wow. You've signed up
quite a few people, Dad-
the Sea Captain, Bumblebee Man,
Comic Book Guy, the Squeaky-voiced Teen.
I gotta hand it to you, Homer.
It's really a good group.
Yeah, not a dame in sight.
Oh, thank God.
Now we can stop holding it in.
[ All Sighing ]
All aboard for Miami.
- [ Grunting ]
- [ Barney ] I don't know if I can last that long.
Super Bowl, please,
and step on it.
- [ All Cheering ]
- Hey, wait up!
Aw, crap.
It's that pip-squeak Rudy.
- What is it, Rudy?
- Can I come too?
Forget it, kid. You're too small
to go to the Super Bowl.
But what I lack in size
I make up for in...
obnoxiousness.
[ All Cheering ]
##[ Upbeat Song ]
Well, sports fans,
I see you've located the beer supply.
So, let's all enjoy it in moderation.
- [ Man ] Boo.!
- Hey, don't make me come back there.
Seriously now,
if you have any questions...
just ask our team leader,
Homer Simpson.
## [ Drunkenly Humming ]
Or me. Better ask me.
[ Sighs ] It's so nice to have
a peaceful weekend together.
- Yeah, I'm bored too.
- Mm-hmm.
Hey, why don't we do one of those
craft kits Aunt Patty always gives us.
Hmm. Oh! How 'bout
paint by numbers?
- It's so rigid and uncreative.
- Okay.
- Oh, leather craft.
- Oh, those poor, helpless cows!
Mm-hmm. What about clay?
You got any problem with clay?
Hey, what's this?
''Vincent Price's Egg Magic.''
Wow. What are we waiting for?
[ All Laughing ]
Now look what you've done.
All right, all right.
You guys have had way too much booze.
- Last call.
- [ Excited Chattering ]
Come on, come on.
Gimme an excuse.
Pro Player Stadium.
Super Bowl.
- [ All Cheering ]
- [ Gunshots ]
Hey, all right!
[ Bleating ]
[ Chuckles ]
I'm sorry.
- The guys made kind of a mess in your bathroom.
- What bathroom?
Uh, okay, fellas.
Enjoy the pregame fun.
I don't wanna be a Panicky Pete...
but it's Sunday
and I haven't been to church yet.
No problem.
The N.F.L.'s got you covered.
And that the wandering
Oakland Raiders may someday find a home.
Lord, hear our prayer.
Can I get an amen to that?
[ All ]
Amen!
Cool! The N.F.L.'s
oldest surviving player.
- I'm 53 years young.
- [ Shuddering ]
Whoo!
Hey, Troy Aikman!
So, Ned, you like dune buggies?
Well, not my cup of-
Sure you do.
Everyone likes dune buggies.
Great spiral, Daniel!
Man, that hurts.
Excuse me. Coming through.
Friends of Dan Marino.
Okay, Dan, fire away!
I'm Dan's manager.
This is Dan.
- Go long, son.
- Yes, sir.
[ Whimpering ]
I'm catching a pass from Dan Marino.
This is the greatest moment of my-
Whoo-hoo!
Homer Simpson with a pick!
- Hey, Bubba, Hacksaw, get that moron.
- [ Growling ]
- Uh-oh. Lateral to Bart.
- [ Growling Continues ]
- D'oh! My spine.
- [ Bone Snaps ]
Oh, honey, that is egg-ceptional.
Okay, now we just have to
stick the feet on.
Right.
Hmm. Lisa, I don't want to alarm you,
but I'm not finding any.
But it clearly says ''feet included.''
They have to be here.
No. Nothing.
I can't believe Vincent Price would lend
his name to such a shoddy product.
- Now what do we do?
- Let's call the company.
Mom, this was made in 1 967.
They're probably out of business.
Well, we'll just see.
Murray Hill 5-923 2.
[ Line Ringing ]
Hello. This is Vincent Price.
[ Gasps ] It's Vincent Price!
I thought he was dead.
You should know the grave could never
tame me. [ Sinister Laughter]
Oh, Mr. Price. I loved you
in The Abominable Doc-
If you are calling about the missing feet,
leave your address...
and the replacement feet
will be rushed to you by my grandson Jody.
And now I must return
to the sweet embrace of the crypt.
But I'll be back.
[ Sinister Laughter ]
So, is he alive or not?
- [ Machine Beeps ]
- 7 42 Evergreen Terrace.
Springfield-
''Oh, hiya,'' Maude.
Come on in.
Who needs tickets? Tickets, right here.
How 'bout you, slick?
Scalping tickets
to the Super Bowl.
Have you no shame, sir?
I should give you a royal caning.
[ All Shouting Agreement ]
Hey, I'm just trying
to make an honest buck.
Ah, get lost,
you bloodsucking parasite.
Wally and I have
all the tickets we need.
Uh, sorry, fellas,
but these tickets are counterfeit.
- What?
- Counterfeit?
Yeah, see, the hologram's missing...
and there's no such team
as the Spungos...
and finally, these seem to be printed
on some sort of cracker.
Stop eating our tickets!
Oh, how could I fall
for fake tickets?
Gee, the fellas
are gonna be crestfallen.
Yes, if by ''crestfallen''
you mean ''kill us''.
Listen, let me talk to them.
Maybe I can smooth this over.
My friends-
- They don't have the tickets!
- Kill 'em!
My friends- Ow!
All right, I'll get you into the game!
Excuse me, uh, Mr. Scalper, sir.
Have I told you that I love you?
Forget it. You'll just hurt me
like all the others.
Okay, Moe, I believe
you had me by the throat.
Reverend Lovejoy
was working the body.
Wait. Dad, look!
Hello. Gentlemen,
I have an idea.
- Run!
- [ All Cheering ]
- Get back here!
- We can still make the kickoff.
- Here comes the kick.
- [ Cheer Building Up ]
- Ow!
- [ All ] Yea!
As a doctor,
I'd say he's had enough.
But as a football fan-
- [ Cheer Building Up ]
- [ Screams ]
[ Wind Gusting ]
[ Honking ]
##[ Rock ]
[ Man Over TV] The Catholic Church-
we've made a few changes:
These Super Bowl commercials
are weird.
[ Man ]Just about ready
for the second quarter here in Miami.
I tell you, Pat, that wild first quarter
blew out my Telestrator.
- And now the fans are screaming for more.
- [ Screaming ]
- Let us out of here!
- Relax, Simpson. Relax.
A little-known fact
about jail cells...
is they always have one phony bar
for, like, emergencies.
Real. Real. Real. Real. Real.
So by the process of elimination,
this one is the fake.
[ Groaning ]
That's painful.
[ Crowd Cheering On TV]
Ah, nuts.
That sounds like a touchdown.
- [ All Moaning ]
- No, no, no. I know my roars.
And that was most definitely
a safety.
- [ All Moaning ]
- Oh, man!
Gosh, fellas, to see
you all stuck in here when...
even guys in China can watch all the action
from their town squares or what have you...
well, I just feel
pretty doggone bad.
If they were electing a president
of Dumbville, I'd have to nominate me.
- You got my vote.
- We're never gonna get out of-
Psst, cleaning lady.
Would you let us out of here?
- Me? I'm Dolly Parton.
- I didn't ask for your life story.
Just give me the key.
Young man, where I come from,
the South, folks say ''please.''
And besides, I gotta go sing a medley
with Rob Lowe and Stump.
- Dolly, wait!
- Wally?
You know Dolly Parton?
Yeah. I book a lot of package tours
to Dollywood and EuroDollywood.
- That's in Alabama.
- Wally Kogen!
What are you doing
in Super Bowl jail?
- Ask her if she'll go out with me.
- We had a little ticket snafu.
Do you think you can bust old Wally
and his pals outta the pokey?
Well, I do have some
of my extra-strength makeup remover.
Shield your eyes.
[ Excited Murmuring ]
- Thanks, Miss Parton.
- [ Barney ] Way to go, Dolly.
- [ Bart ] Thanks, babe.
- Will you go out with me?
Oh, look at the time.
I better scoot to that halftime show.
See y'all!
Man, that's gonna be some show.
Who's ready for some football?
Football!
##[ Upbeat Rock ]
Hey, Homer, we've been running
around cheering for an hour.
- Where the hell's the game?
- [ All Murmuring Agreement ]
You guys are following me?
I was following Flanders.
Hey, look what I found.
- Whoa!
- [ Excited Murmuring ]
- Hey!
- [ Crowd Cheering ]
- Hey, somebody just scored.
- [ Homer] Coming in a minute.
- [ Chattering ]
- [ Belches ]
[ Homer]
Hey, it's the beer copter!
- What the bloody hell?
- Hit the road, gramps.
This is a private skybox.
I'm Rupert Murdoch, the billionaire
tyrant. And this is my skybox.
If you're Rupert Murdoch, prove it.
- [ Whispering ]
- ##[ Fanfare ]
- [ Crowd ] Hi, Rupert!
- [ All ] Uh-oh.
- Well, I'm convinced.
Tell you what, Mr. Murdoch.
Let's just split the difference.
The boys and I will just crouch here
quietly and take it easy on the snacks-
Silence!
- Seize them!
- [ Gasping ]
Oi, oi, oi, oi, oi!
[ Crowd Cheering ]
The game! We're so close.
Follow me, boys.
We're finally going to the Super-
[ Screams ]
- [ Player] We did it! We're number one!
- We're rich!
- How does it feel?
- Did you ever stop believing?
Does this suit make me look fat?
- Players and V.I.P.s only.
- [ All Moan ]
I can't believe it. We're actually in
the winning locker room.
Whoo! I'm going to Disneyland!
Really? 'Cause I'm a travel agent and
I've heard nothing but bad things.
- [ All Grunting ]
- Let go!
- [ Ringing ]
- Y'ello?
- Hello. This is President Clinton.
- Hey, how you doing?
Your determination and grit under
extreme pressure are an inspiration.
- The whole country is proud of you.
- Well, it's about time!
And on behalf of America,
I'd like to-
Ow!
All right, Lovejoy!
You're gonna get it.
Hello? Hello? I command you
to answer me! Hello?
Al, do you have to
do that right now?
What are you gonna do
with your Super Bowl ring, Carl?
I'll probably give it to my wife.
It's our anniversary today.
[ All Sighing ]
Dad, that doesn't belong to you.
But this might be
my last chance to win one.
We sure put together a heck of a trip, Homer.
Ever thought about being a travel agent?
Wally, I'd be lying if I said I hadn't.
'Cause you can really ''go places''
in the travel business.
- Huh? Feel free to use that one.
- What one?
Well,John, what did you think
of tonight's episode?
I loved it. The last-minute addition
of Wally Kogen to the lineup...
was a bit of a gamble,
but it really paid off.
Marge and Lisa painting eggs-
did that work for you?
Oh, big-time! They came
off the bench with a huge effort...
that allowed Homer and Bart
to make some significant gains.
Did it strike you as odd that in
a Super Bowl show with Dolly Parton...
we didn't see any football or singing?
I hadn't thought about it, Pat.
But in retrospect, it was kind of a rip-off.
What a way to treat
the loyal fans...
who've put up with so much nonsense
from this franchise.
- Any final thoughts?
- Nah, I'm too mad. Let's get the heck out of here.
All aboard, boys.
I've been waiting for you.
Now, I'll tell you-
that doesn't make a lick of sense!
I know.
Just get on the bus.
- [ Gears Grinding ]
- [ Price ] Where's that infernal clutch?
- Wait, wait. I'll get it.
- [ Boy ] Give it some gas, Grandpa.
Oh, quiet,Jody.
You're not helping.
##[ Rock ]
##[ Instrumental Easy Listening ]
[ Rupert Murdoch ]
Silence.!
www.tvsubtitles.net