##[ Chorus Singing ]
[ Bell Ringing ]
[ Whistle Blowing ]
[ Beeping ]
## [Jazzy Solo ]
[ Tires Screeching ]
D'oh!
[ Screams ]
[ Screaming ]
##[ Woman Singing ]
## [ Continues ]
## [ Song Ends ]
- [ Crowd Cheering ]
- Thank you, Springfield! I love you! Peace!
[ Man On Speaker ] Thank you,
Cyndi Lauper.Just a reminder, folks.
- We do have a baseball game today.
- Oh, right.
I'm Dennis Conroy.
And here come your Isotopes.
- [ Crowd Booing ]
- [ Coughing ]
Let's welcome two new additions
to the team...
Smash Diggins and Fishbone Walker.
Lucky for us, they were
sent down from the majors...
for drug violations.
- [ Crowd Cheering ]
- ##[ Organ Fanfare ]
Why do you hate the Isotopes
so much, Dad?
Because I loved them once
and they broke my heart.
Let that be a lesson to you,
sweetie. Never love anything.
- Even you?
- Especially me.
But you gotta support the team, Dad.
They're already threatening
to move to MooseJaw.
That's right.
Like my mother always said...
you've gotta stick it out,
even if you picked a loser.
- Hmm.
- To the bitter end.
[ Conroy On Speaker ]
First pitch of the game.
- [ Screaming ]
- That's a rotator cuff.
- His career's over.
- I'm gonna warm up the car.
- But there's only been one pitch.
- And it sucked.
Bases loaded, two outs,
bottom of the ninth, and it's do or die.
## [ Homer Singing ]
That'll bring up Babe Ruth IV.
Of course,
he's no Babe Ruth III...
but the franchise is very excited about
this illegitimate great grand bambino.
And what's this? He's pointing
to the right field bleachers.
Probably at a dying little boy.
- Mom, am I dying?
- No, of course not.
- Is he, Mom? You can tell me.
- No!
[ Conroy ]
Now he's pointing to the ground.
Is he indicating a bunt?
Yes, he's bunting.!
- [ Players Groaning ]
- [ Crowd Booing ]
[ Marge ]
Good hustle, kid.!
## [ Homer Singing ]
- So who won? The losers?
- No, they lost.
- [ Chuckles ] Losers.
- But only by two points.
They didn't resort to stealing bases like
the other team, so it's kind of a moral victory.
With a little middle relief,
they might even make the play-offs.
You'll be in your cold, cold
grave before that ever happens.
Homer, would you please stop talking
about the children's graves?
[ Crowd Chattering ]
[ Laughs ]
All right! Whoo!
[ Grunts ]
What's the hubbub?
Did Moe finally blow his brains out?
Quiet! We're watching the Isotopes.
Shut it off.
They're losers.
Where you been?
The Isotopes are on fire.
Yeah, that sniper at the all-star game
was a blessing in disguise.
Now we're in the championship game.
Championship? Hmm.
Whoo! 'Topes rule!
- [ Gulping ]
- Well, here's a die-hard fan.
Sir, your beloved Isotopes are
about to make history. Any thoughts?
Oh, it's a great team, Kent.
We never gave up hope.
I want to thankJesus
and say hi to my special lady, Marge.
We did it, baby!
Whoo! Whoo!
The inspiring words of a fan who'll always
root, root, root for the home team.
- Even if they lose this game.
- They lost? Those losers!
No, no, no.
The game's not over.
Whoo! Not over! Whoo!
There you have it- ''Whoo.''
- Here it comes, baby. Real big one!
- [ All Shouting ]
[ Conroy On Speaker ] Bottom of the ninth,
two outs. It all comes down to this.
- And here's the pitch.
- [ Bat Strikes Ball ]
Humpin' ''hay-zeus';!
He got all of that one.!
- It's going, going, going-
- [ All Gasping ]
Our technical director today
was Stan Kadlubowski.
It's out ofhere.!
'Topes win.!
- [ All Cheering ]
- Isotopes!
What'd I tell you?
Isotopes.! Whoo.!
[ Gulping ]
- Ah, nobody touched my rumaki.
- [ Screams ] Rumaki.!
- Yea! Isotopes!
- [ Horn Honking ]
- Whoo!
- [ Grunting ]
- Isotopes! [ Grunts ]
- Isotopes!
- [ Horn Continues Honking ]
- Isotopes.! You know what I'm sayin'to you, baby?
Hey! A baseball field!
Batter up!
- [ Cheering ]
- Go, baby!
- Steal second!
- I think I'm gonna puke!
- Hey, who's on first?
- Touchdown!
- [ Barney Yelling ]
- [ Tires Screeching ]
- [ Homer ] Safe.!
- [ All Whooping ]
- Hey, Carl? Isotopes!
- [ All Muttering ]
##[ All Singing Rock ]
- [ Screams ]
- Whoop. Careful.
[ Munching ]
Wow. You look really hungover, Dad.
What did you do last night?
Last night? Um-
##[ Piano ]
##[ Ominous Chord ]
Mm, uh, hello, big Maggie.
Yes.! Yes.! Yes.!
- Someone trashed the school!
- What the ''dillio''?
Where this morning the three R's
stand for ''rowdiness''...
''ransacking''
and ''e-responsibility.''
- Any suspects, Chief?
- None.
That's why we're jumping to the conclusion
that this was the work of no-good punk kids.
- Kids?
- Therefore, effective immediately...
I am imposing a curfew.
Any kid caught on the street
after dark will be shot...
or returned to their parents,
as the situation may warrant.
- Whoa!
- Curfew?
Serves you little punks right.
Maybe next time you'll think
before- Oh, my God!
Look what those rotten kids
did to my car!
The cops can't just slap
a curfew on us! We have rights!
Sure you do.
You have the right to remain silent.
[ Both Laughing ]
- That was cold-blooded, Marge.
- Yeah.
But it's not fair. Adults always
blame kids for everything.
Well, if kids are so innocent,
why is everything bad named after them?
Acting childish,
kidnapping, child abuse.
- What about adultery?
- Not until you're older, Son.
[ Children Giggling ]
Okay, go deep!
- Ice cream truck!
- [ Excited Shouting ]
I was here first!
Get out of my way!
- ## [ Cheerful Tune ]
- [ Children Laughing ]
[ Siren Wailing ]
Achtung, babies!
Curfew is in effect!
Return to your homes immediately.
[ Screaming ]
[ Boy Whining ]
I don't want to return home.
All right. Let's see some I.D.'s, boys.
[ Scoffs ]
You two scofflaws are violating curfew.
I'm taking you downtown.
Oh, uh, sorry to disturb you,
Dr. Hibbert.
[ Deep Voice ]
Not at all, officer.
[ Laughing ]
Oh, what a beautiful night.
Fireflies, full moon-
And here we are, locked inside.
Kids, the carnival's in town
for one night only!
And they've got cotton candy
and hats with feathers!
And there's no lines, because
all the stupid kids have curfew!
So- Oh, right. Sorry.
[ Giggling ]
[ Both Sighing ]
Why don't you kids play
one of your old board games?
When was the last time
you played Citizenship?
- Energy Shortage?
- Hippo in the House?
[ Marge ]
Ooh, the Game of Lent.!
- [ Groans ] Can't we just go to bed?
- It's only 5:30.
Fine. We'll play Hippo in the House.
- Oh, the hippo's missing.
- [ Both Groaning ]
You think that's bad.
I had to talk to my mom all night.
She's got problems.
Scary problems.
Adults blow.
Yeah,just look at 'em over there.
Smokin' their cigarettes.
Drinkin' their coffee.
Scratchin' their big butts.
Your metabolism will change
someday too, young man.
[ Mutters, Clears Throat ]
[ Motor Humming ]
That oughta show little Timmy and Tammy
Scumbag who's in charge around here.
Gee, Chief, all those gears and motors
must've cost a fortune.
-Well, you gotta spend money to make money, Lou.
-Mm-hmm.
[ Yawns ]
You wanna hold it for a while?
Nah.
- ## [ Humming ]
- Marge, kite.
Hey, there is one thing we could do.
[ Gasps ]
Lise, no! It's prime time!
You robbed me of my manhood!
That's petty theft.
- [ TVAudience ] Ooh!
- Don't go there.
[ Laughing, Applause ]
Don't Go There will be right back.
- Oh, no it won't.
- Wait.! There's a commercial.!
[ Wolf Howling ]
- Oh, yeah.
- Whoa.
- [ Wolves Snarling ]
- [ Man Narrating ] Forty years ago...
a film appeared that was
so shocking, so terrifying...
it was sealed in a concrete
vault deep beneath the earth.
But even the new management
of Sony TriStar...
could not contain the pure evil
of... The Bloodening.
[ Woman Screaming ]
Milhouse, do you see
what's on Channel 6?
Uh, yeah. It's really something.
[ Screams ]
- [ Screaming ]
- A registered nurse trained
in the treatment of terror...
will be on duty during
the showing of The Bloodening.
[ Eerie Laughing ]
[ TVAnnouncer ] Now playing
at the Springfield Drive-In... after dark.
Milhouse, spread the word.
We're seeing this movie tonight.
That's right.
We're breaking curfew.
Come on!
- I'm breaking curfew, Mom!
- [ Mother ] We're out of Skoal.!
''Due to the likelihood
of fear-induced heart attacks...
we're offering all patrons
million-dollar life insurance policies.''
Life insurance? Hmm. Will I be able
to borrow against the equity?
I don't know, sir.
It comes free with the popcorn.
- Is that air-popped?
- Skinner.!
- We're losing valuable make-out time.
- [ Giggles ]
[ Grunting ]
A little help.
- Sure.
- [ Grunts, Groans ]
- [ Grunts ] Lisa.
- Nelson.
## [ Chorus Singing ]
[ Wolves Howling ]
Get off of my moor,
you mischievous weans!
[ English Accent ]
Actually, we prefer to stay.
You're thinking about hurting us.
- [ Gasps ]
- Now you're thinking...
''How did they know
what I was thinking?''
Now you're thinking, ''I hope
that's shepherd's pie in my knickers.''
[ Gasping ]
[ Screaming ]
- Wow!
- They showed him!
Man, I never liked Shakespeare
until now.
- [ Crowd Chattering ]
- Right, you little blighters.
We've had quite enough
of your evil mischief.
But you're the one who's been bad.
You've been sneaking puddings.
But- But how did you know?
We know all your secrets.
And you pilfered the poor box.
- [ Gasps ]
- And, Doctor, we know
that you and the bootblack...
have been rogering the fishwife
in the crumpet shop.
- [ Gasps ] Lies!
- How dare you!
Get them! Quickly!
We can't have that.
[ All Gasping ]
[ All Grunting, Groaning ]
[ Screaming ]
- Take that, you suckers!
- Stick him with the pitchfork!
- Way to go!
- In your face, fishwife!
Enjoying the movie, kids?
[ All Screaming ]
Listen up, punks.
The moral of the story is...
the adults always win.
[ Screams ]
For crying out loud, Eddie.
You scared the hell out of me.
Sorry, Chief.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Groaning ]
Don't forget to clean under the jowls.
That spot is Club Med for mildew.
And let this be a lesson to you!
Kids never learn!
[ Snickers ]
[ Groaning, Coughing ]
Oh, that is it! I'm tired of being
pushed around by grown-ups!
It's time to fight back!
- Yeah!
- Fight back! Fight back!
Man, if we had eye power
like those kids in that movie...
we could read the adults' mind
and tell their secrets...
and make 'em pitchfork
each other and junk!
- Oh, yeah!
- Wait!
We don't need supernatural powers.
We already know their secrets.
She's right. Homer's done a ton of crap
that never made the papers.
My mom shoplifts all the time.
Stuff she doesn't even need.
My dad gets in car accidents
on purpose.
Great.
This is all gold.
[ Milhouse ]
We gotta spread this stuff around.
Let's put it on the Internet!
[ Bart ] No! We have to reach people
whose opinions actually matter.
And I think I know how.
Why don't we-
- I can get my dad's amplifier from the garage.
- Yeah, that's a good idea.
Attention, hemline
and midriff monitors.
- [ Glass Squeaking ]
- [ Gasps ]
Willie, get my Windex!
[ Snoring ]
[ Cat Screeches ]
200 channels,
nothin' but cats.
So, Marge, ready for another
episode of Don't Go There?
I'm tired of that show.
But I've been hearing good things
about Talk to the Hand.
Tom Shales says the writing
''snaps, crackles and pops.''
Okay. Whatever takes
my mind off my life.
## [ Chorus Singing ]
Hey, look what I found!
Grampa's old radio.
Oh, wouldn't it be grand
to gather round and have a listen?
Well, turn something on.
I'm startin' to think!
[ Changing Stations ]
[ F.D.R.'s Voice ]
A date which will live in infamy.
Good evening, adults.
We interrupt this broadcast...
to bring you a very special
presentation.
Tonight's program is entitled-
[ Together]
We Know All Your Secrets.
Boring! Go back to that ''infamy'' guy.
[ Bart On Radio ]
Constable Wiggum likes to act tough...
but he also likes to walk the beat
in control-top panty hose.
- [ Both Gasp ]
- [ Chuckles ]
Well, it's not like that's a crime.
has been stealing supplies
from the school cafeteria.
[ Gasps ]
Edna! How could you?
Don't get up.
I'll bus my own tray.
- And now we come to Mr. Homer Simpson.
- [ Screams ]
Did you know he likes to eat
out of the Flanders' garbage?
- Oh, Homer.
- I have a problem.
Tune in tomorrow and every day
until the curfew is lifted...
because we'll be revealing embarrassing
secrets about Springfield's other adults.
Well, at least they've already done me.
- And we have plenty more on Homer Simpson.
- D'oh!
I've called this meeting
to determine what to do...
about those blabbermouth kids
and their creepy English accents.
Hey, shut up, Mayor!
They're tellin' secrets again!
- [ Murmuring ]
- Oh, I hope they don't reveal this is a comb-over.
[ Lisa With English Accent ] Our top secret
tonight- gay divorcee Luann Van Houten...
has been cheating
on her boyfriend, Pyro...
with his best friend, Gyro.
How many times have I fought
beside you, Gyro?
And this is how you repay me?
- [ Both Grunting ]
- Pyro! Gyro! Settle down!
Can't we shut down
that infernal transmitter?
- Can't we just blow it up?
- You go ahead, girlfriend!
- They're the worst!
- Yeah!
- Say it again, girl!
- Settle down, people.
As we speak, Chief Wiggum
is tracking down those little squealers...
using the latest
in crime-fighting technology.
Uh, I got nothing.
How about you, Frinky?
I have captured the signal and am
presently triangulating the vectors...
and compressing the data down...
in order to express it
as a function of my hand.
They're over there!
And guess who's been practicing
medicine without a license?
- [ Gulps ]
- That's right. Homer Simpson.
- [ Homer ] D'oh.!
- Freeze, you little shock jocks!
[ Guns Cocking ]
Brilliant. They transduced
amplitude modulation...
via the concavity of that
oversized beverage conveyance.
I mean, that is some clever ''viving.''
All right, you kids,
come down now.
- We promise we won't kill ya.
- Speak for yourself.
Bart, get down here! I'm gonna
spank you back to the Stone Age!
You can't make us come down!
You adults are always
givin' us orders!
You kids are always
disobeying them.
Well, adults treat kids
like children!
Kids treat adults
like cash machines!
- Adults!
- Kids!
## [ Singing Musical Comedy ]
- ## [ Continues ]
- [ Marge Groans ]
- [ Cat Screeches ]
- [ Screams ]
- ## [ Continues ]
## [ Ends ]
We're gonna teach
all you rug rats a lesson.
Oh, yeah? What can you
old people do to us?
- Yeah, you old fogeys!
- Buzz off, you old-
- What do you got?
- You're all wrinkly!
Somebody should iron you!
This is Kent Brockman
reporting from... my own home...
in accordance with the new
curfew for anyone under 7 0.
- Mm, I can't believe that passed.
- [ Grumbling ]
I warned you guys that seniors
always vote in record numbers.
The controversial measure
passed by a single vote.
[ Groans ]
You really should've voted, Homer.
[ Scoffs ]
It wouldn't have made a difference.
Lights out, you punk kids!
Yea! We took back the night!
Hey, fellas! Hey, you wanna
stop with the kicking?
My pills are in that can.!
Good gravy.!
I don't kick your things.
When you're trying to breathe
on the machine, do I go up and kick it?
Oh, now look at that.
It went down the sewer.! You happy?
I'm gonna sue now.!
Now it's time for the lawyers.!
- Shh.
- Don't tell me to shush, you stupid lady!
www.tvsubtitles.net