##[Drum roll]
[ Man Announcing]
Live from fabulous Centauri City....
it's The Simpsons
10th Halloween Special.
Now, please welcome
your hosts-
if you haven't been probed
by these two...
you haven't been probed-
- Kang and Kodos!
- [ Cheering ]
- Thank you. Thank you.
- Yes. Thank you, ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome to our
10th anniversary show.
Oh. We've got a great-
Kang, what are you doing?.
You said we were going to
warm up the audience.
[Speakers: Laughter]
[ Shudders ] Ladies and gentlemen,
I have to apologize for my partner.
He had to borrow a human brain.
[ Speakers: Laughter]
What do aliens
have to do with Halloween?.
[ Deep Male Voice ]
Silence!.
I still can't believe we escaped from
those horrible vampires.
But it was worth it to get back
our Super Sugar Crisp cereal.
# Can't get enough
of that Sugar Crisp #
I'm having a hard time seeing.
Homer, did you remember
to put the fog lights in ?
# Guess I forgot to put
the fog lights in #
- I better pull over and play it safe.
- [ Thuds ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Gasps ]
Please be a dog.
Oh, no!.
Ned Flanders!
He's dead!
- [ Eye Squishing]
- He's definitely dead!
- [ Squishing]
- Oh, my God. We killed Ned Flanders.
You mean you killed Ned Flanders.
Oh! It was an accident!
An accident!
We've gotta  go to the police.
They'll never believe a Simpson
killed a Flanders by accident.
- Even I have my doubts.
- Don't worry. I got a plan.
Okay, Ned. First thing
we have to do...
is to make sure that no one
knows that you're dead.
And if anyone asks you,
just say that you are not dead.
Hey., Maude! Look who's helping me
clean the chimney..
- Hey. Not now.
- [ Squawks ]
Neddie?.
Where have you been?.
[ Imitating Ned ]
Hi, Maude. Diddly.
I've been having fun
with my pal Homer.
Diddly.
Oh, I'm so relieved.
Whenever you go on one of your late-night
fog walks, I get so worried.
Relax! I'm fine.
But when I do die,
I don't want any autopsies.
Well, come on down, you goofy roofy.
- Wow. It sure is slippery up here.
- [ Bell Dings ]
My pies are done.
Oh, she missed it.
[ Imitating Ned ]
Hey, Maude. I'm home.
Uh-oh! I think
I'm having a heart attack!
[ Maude Screams ]
And that's the end of that chapter.
[ Bell Ringing]
##[ Organ ]
[ Sobbing ]
[ Whispers ]
Try not to look too sad.
It'll seem suspicious.
And now Ned's best friend
will say a few words.
- Homer.
- [ Clears Throat ]
When I think about Ned, I can't help but remember
the look on his face when Marge drove over-
- Homer! Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
- Oh. Wait.
What I'd like to say is we're still
looking for the real killers.
Anyway, in conclusion, a man cannot
be forced to testify against his wife.
[Marge ]
Stop winking!
We'll miss you, buddy.
Hey. We just got away with murder.
And it was so easy!
You know, I've never liked that
little wiener Milhouse.
- [ Tires Screech ]
- [ Marge ] No more murders!
- But you got to kill-
- No!
[ All Gasp ]
[ Marge ]
Someone saw us!
[ All ]
But who?.
Homer, stop that.
[ Thunder Rumbling]
- [ Phone Ringing ]
- Who could be calling at this hour?.
[ Whimpering ]
- Yellow?
- [ Male Voice ] I know you're alone.
[ Whimpering ]
Who is this?.
Is this Maude Flanders?.
No. It's Homer.
Oh! Hey, Homer. It's Moe.
I must have dialed the wrong number.
- [Thunderclap ]
- [ All Screaming ]
[All Whimpering]
- Get in the car.
- [ Thunderclap ]
[ All Screaming ]
Dear God, it's Homer. If you really
love me, you'll save my life now.
D'oh!
- He's getting closer!
- [ All Gasping ]
[ Thunderclap ]
Okay, Marge. You hide in
the abandoned amusement park.
Lisa, the pet cemetery.
Bart, spooky roller disco.
##[ Disco ]
And I'll go skinny-dipping
in that lake...
where the sexy teens were killed
a hundred years ago tonight.
Now, Flanders,
I want you to-
- [ All Screaming ]
- [ Thunderclaps ]
It's impossible!
I killed you!
[ Chuckles ]
You can't kill the undead, silly.
- He's undead, all right.
- Are you a zombie?.
Oh, I wish! You see, that night
when you hit me with your car-
I'm making record time
on this fog walk.
- [ Wolf Howling]
- Better pick up the pace.
- [ Growls ]
- [ Screaming ]
[ Roars ]
# Guess I forgot to put
the fog lights in #
- [ Marge ] I better pull over and play it safe.
- [ Whimpers ]
So you were going to kill us.
[ Chuckles ]
Yeah.
[ All Laughing ]
- [ Roars ]
- Hey, foamy. I want the news, not the weather.
[ Chuckles ] Marge, did you hear me
zing werewolf Flanders?.
[ Snarls ]
Diddly!
[ Gasping ]
- [ Whimpering ]
- [ Snarling ]
[ Gasps ]
- [ Homer Screams ] Flanders! Stop that!
- [ Fabric Tearing]
[ Homer] Eyes bigger than
your stomach, eh, wolfie?
- [ Laughs ]
- [ Flanders Snarling ]
[ Homer Screaming ]
[ Chattering ]
Well, well, well. If it isn't the cutest
police officer in Springfield.
Hey, you know,
we got feelings too, Chief.
Just dump your candy on the X-ray belt,
Ralphie. There's a good boy.
Safe. Safe.
Razorblade. Syringe.
- Oh! White chocolate!
- Check it out, Lisa.
I'm Radioactive Man.
I don't think the real
Radioactive Man...
wears a plastic smock
with a picture of himself on it.
He would on Halloween.
[ Grunting ]
Get in there, you stupid pillowcase!
Stop it!
You'll jam the machine!
Uh-oh! Radiation.
Duck and cover!
- [ Screaming ]
- Cool.
Bart!
[ Groans ]
- [ Children Screaming]
- Oh, my God! Lisa!
She's been crushed. And so have
the hopes of our Mathletics team.
Hold the funeral, poindexter.
[ Gasps ]
Poindexter?.
[ Grunts ]
Whoa, Lise! Those X-rays must have
given you super strength!
I wonder if I got any powers.
Nope. Looks normal.
Wait a minute.
I can stretch!
Look at me!
Ow! Hot, hot, hot.
I must only use this power to annoy.
- [ Knocking]
- Now, who could that be at this hour?.
Yes. Yes. Up. Down. Side to side.
What's your point?.
- Ow!
- [ Laughs ] Gotcha.
Bart, with these powers,
we can become superheroes.
Okay. So do it already.
[ Chorus ]
# Stretch Dude and Clobber Girl #
# He's a human rubber band
and she's a hulk in curls #
[ Women ]
# He's a limber lad#
[ Men ]
# She's a powerful lass #
[ Chorus ] # He'll wring your neck
and she'll kick your ass #
# They’re Stretch Dude #
# And Clobber Girl #
# Stretch Dude
Clobber Girl ##
[ Man Announcing ]
Tonight's episode: "Enter the Collector;'
But I ' m sure that once girls
get to know the real you...
you’ll I get plenty of dates.
Next question.
Yes. Over here.
[ Stammering ]
I n Episode BF1 2, you were
battling barbarians...
while riding a winged Appaloosa.
Yet in the very next scene, my dear,
you're clearly atop a winged  Arabian.
- Please to explain it.
- Ah. Yeah.
Well, whenever you notice
something like that, a wizard did it.
I see. All right. Yes.
But in Episode AG4-
- Wizard.
- Ah, for glavin out loud.
[ Glass Shatters ]
Behold! I am the Collector!
And I'm here to add you
to my collection!
[ Grunting ]
Must remove my breastplate.
Maybe later.
Care for a Rolo, sweet Xena?.
All right, Collector.
Stick this in your tweezers. I'm not Xena!
I'm an actress, you lunatic!
Oh, please. I'm not insane.
I simply wish to take you back
to my lair and make you my bride.
Oh, dear God!
Clobber Girl.
[ Grunts ]
Thank you.
Help!
It's Xena.
She's been kidnapped!
Come on.
Remember. You're vulnerable
to Kryptonite!
Geez, Marge!
Tell the neighborhood.
Fear not, my syndicated sweetie.
You'll be preserved
in this Mylar pouch...
forever remaining in...
near-mint condition between Doctor Who
and, of course, Yasmine Bleeth.
- [ Lisa ] I don't think so.
- [ Gasps ]
I don't think so either.
[ Taunting Vocalizations ]
You're collecting days
are over, Collector!
Stop right there!
I have here the only working
phaser ever built.
It was fired only once.. to keep William Shatner
from making another album.
- [ Cocks ]
- Stretch Dude!
- Help!
-Just a sec.
[ Groans ]
Hey, phaser, phaser, phaser.
[ Grunting ]
- [ Groans ]
- Nah, nah!
Good night, "Retch" Dude
and "Slobber" Girl.
Sweet screams.
[ Laughs ]
I'm unbelievably. amused.
Soon those bratty buttinskies will be
encased in Lucite for all eternity.
While we're waiting, here are some names
you may call me on our wedding night.
[ Clears Throat ]
Obi-Wan. Iron Man. Mr. Mxyzptlk.
And, of course, Big Papa Smurf.
What do you need me for?. You could have
your choice of any of the women in these bags.
You would think so, but no.
Really?.
Well, I mean, maybe we are
meant for each other.
Growing up, I was always tall for my age,
and the other kids made fun of me.
I- I always hoped for another
misunderstood soul to share my pain.
You could be that soul, Collector.
Oh.
Come here, you.
Xena needs "xex."
[ Chuckles ]
- Got your lips!
- [ Groaning ]
[ Shouts ]
Oh! You tricked me...
with a ruse so hackneyed
it would make Stan Lee blush.
Shut up.
[ Ululating ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Groans ]
- [ Shouting ]
- Oh! Ow. Ow. That hurts.
Bart, just let me drop
and save yourself.
What do you think
I've been trying to do?.
Aha! Not even Xena is a match for...
the limited edition
double-edged light saber...
from Star Wars Episode I:
The Phantom Menace.
[ Humming ]
[ Gasps ] You removed it
from its original packaging!
[ Gasps ]
No!
It's no longer a collectible!
Oh! Oh!
[ Groans ]
- What a nerd.
- Lucite hardening.
Must end life
in classic Lorne Greene pose...
from Battle star Galactica.
[ Grunting ]
Best... death... ever!
- Wow. Thanks for saving us.
- No problem.
Now let's get you kids home.
Wait a minute.
Xena can't fly.
- I told you. I'm not Xena. I'm Lucy Lawless.
- Oh.
[ Chorus ]
# Stretch Dude and Clobber Girl#
[ Beeping]
## [ Rock]
- ## [ Ends ]
- [ Cheering]
This is Dick Clark, rockin' down to the year 2000.
And that was White snake.
We're not White snake, dude.
We're Poison.
- I thought we were Quiet Riot.
- It says here we're Ratt.
- [ Chattering ]
- Oh, right. Sorry.
Man alive! What a stinko
thousand years.
Blimp wrecks. Teenagers.
Then again, we had two TV shows
with Andy Griffith.
And 11 with Robert Urich.
##[ TV.: Funk]
# Super freak, Super freak #
# I'm super freakin'
Yow ##
Aw, man.
What'd I do now?.
- [ Crowd Cheering ]
- Wonderful. Now, that song is dedicated...
to all you super geeks who rocked around
the clock to exterminate America's Y2K bugs.
- Slammin'!
- Hey, Homer.
Weren't you the plant's
Y2K compliance officer?.
- Absolutely.
- Must have been hard debugging
all those computers, huh, Homer?.
- Doing what now?.
- You did fix them, right, Dad?.
Because even a single faulty unit could corrupt
every other computer in the world.
That can't be true, honey.
If it were, I'd be terrified.
Eight, seven, six-
We want to thank Dixie brand mayonnaise.
Whoo, Lordy, what a mayonnaise!
Three, two-
[Alarm Blaring]
- That's Homer Simpson's computer.
- Oh, God! It's spreading!
- [ Creaks ]
- Happy New-Wha-
Oh, no. It's happening.
[ Electricity Crackling ]
[Screaming]
Uh-oh.
[ Screaming ]
[ Electricity Crackling ]
[ Groans ]
Who's gonna clean up all those jets?.
- [ Crash ]
- [ Electricity. Crackling]
There goes the clothesline.
Well, those ivory-tower eggheads
have screwed us again. [ Chuckles ]
Let's just have some milk
and go to bed.
[ Gasping ]
Hey. This milk's broken.
- It's got a computer chip in it. Everything does.
- [ Beeping]
[ Gasps ]
[ Beeping Continues ]
Oh! Oh!
[ Groaning ]
- [ Whimpering ]
- [ Man Whimpering ]
Judgment Day is upon us.
I warned you the Lord wouldn't stand for
your mini dresses and Beatle boots.
[ Grunting ] I resisted these for 35 years.
Why did I wear them today?.
But it's not too late to repent your sins
and be embraced by the Almighty.
Hey, everybody! They're looting the mall!
Hurry! I got nine shoe buffers!
[ All Shouting ]
[ Grunting ]
I'm caught on something.
- I don't want you looting.
- But I was gonna loot you a present.
- Oh, all right.
- [ Giggles ]
[Siren Wails ]
[ All Shouting ]
Oh, thank you, Homie.
A Lady Remington.
- [ Buzzing ]
- [ Screams, Grunting ]
[ Screaming ]
Well, look at the wonders
of the computer age now.
Wonders, Lisa?.
Or blunders?.
I think that was implied
by what I said.
Implied, Lisa?.
Or implode?.
- Mom, make him stop.
- [Krusty.Groans ]
- Oh, no. Krusty!
- [ Groaning ]
My pacemaker.
It's stuck on "hummingbird."
Nectar. Nectar. I need to
drink my weight in nectar.
Krusty!
Hey, a note.
"You have been selected
for Operation Exodus."
They're evacuating the Earth.
[ Gasps ] We're saved!
[ Sobbing ]
Thank you, sweet clown.
I n death, you saved us all.
I'm not dead.
I can still hear his voice
on the wind.
[ Bart ]
There it is!
[ Homer]
Just like the dead clown promised!
[ Elevator Bell Dings ]
[ Bart] Wow. There's Bill Gates,
Stephen Hawking...
Paul McCartney.,
Michael Jordan, Michelle Kwan.
They must be starting a new civilization
on Mars with our best and brightest.
- That's us!
- Name, please.
Certainly. I am...
the, uh, piano genius
from the movie Shine.
Uh-huh.
And your name is?.
Uh, Shiny McShine.
Actually, he's Homer Simpson.
That's Bart. I'm Lisa.
Lisa Simpson?. You're the ship's proofreader.
Welcome aboard.
Now, before you enter, you're going to have to
make a very difficult choice.
- You're only allowed to take one parent with you.
- Mom.
- Love ya lots!
- Good-bye, Lisa.
Remember me as I am-
filled with murderous rage!
Well, Son, I guess this is the end.
But we've both had long, full lives.
- Oh. Right.
- Hey, look. Another spaceship.
And there's nobody
guarding it! Let's go.
I can't believe
I destroyed the Earth.
Are you still talking
about the Earth?.
You're right.
I gotta let it go.
All that counts is we're alive
and rubbing elbows with the greats.
[ Gasps ]
Ooh! There's Ross Perot.
Dr. Laura. Spike Lee.
Wait a minute.
They're not so great.
Okay. But there's Dan Quayle
and Courtney Love.
Tonya Harding!
Al Sharpton!
[ Screams ]
Tom Arnold! What the hell's going on?
Wait. Only that ship
is going to Mars.
- Ours is headed for the sun.
- Yeah. Ain't that a kick in the teeth?.
I mean, my shows weren't great, but I never
tied people up and forced 'em to watch.
And I could've, 'cause I'm a big guy,
and I'm good with knots.
So we're all gonna die?.
Afraid so. But hey, the grub's pretty good, huh?.
[ Chuckles ]
The sun?.
That's the hottest place on Earth.
Gonna work on my "tannage," buddy.
Pauly Shore? Wow! Hey..
We should do a show together, man.
That's a sure cure for the blues.
- [ Noisemaker Blows ]
- Hey! Turn those frowns around.
Oh, no.
Rosie O'Donnell!
Come on, everybody!
Sing along!
# Clang, clang, clang went the trolley #
This side only!
# Ding, ding, ding
went the bell #
#Zing, zing, zing
went my heartstrings #
# From the moment
I saw him, I fell #
- #Clang, clang, clang went the trolley.#
- Don't worry, Dad.
- We'll be dead in five minutes.
- Not fast enough!
[ Beeps ]
# Went my heartstrings
From the moment I saw him #
[ Both Sighing ]
- [ Pops ]
# From the moment I saw him
I fell ##
[ Woman Screams ]
www.tvsubtitles.net