[Chorus ]
# The Simpsons #
[ Bell Ringing]
[ Whistle Blowing]
[ Beeping ]
## [Jazzy Solo ]
[ Tires Screeching ]
D'oh!
[ Screams ]
[ Gasps ]
Now be careful with those
video cameras, children.
In order to buy them, the school board
had to eliminate geography.
This globe will never spin again.
Now, class, I want you to be creative
with your video projects.
- I don’t want to see 30 Blair Witch knockoffs.
- [ All Moan ]
[ Both Laughing ]
Stop Hitting Yourself, take one.
- Stop hitting yourself!. Stop hitting yourself!.
- [ Grunting ]
Stop hitting yourself!.
Tonight on the Discovery Channel,
Inside Lisa's Nose.
What will we find,
boogers or Nazi gold?
- Bart, quit it!
- No way.
- Bart sleeps with Raggedy Andy.
- Cut, cut, cut!
Otto, a red traffic light means what?.
Oooh. No time for brainteasers.
Today's the day I ask my girlfriend
to take a ride on the matrimony pony.
# Otto's got a girlfriend
Otto's got a girlfriend #
- That's right, I do.
- I know you do. Baby!
Otto, since when have
you had a girlfriend?.
We met in the summer of love.
Woodstock, '99.
- ##[Rock]
- [ Cheering ]
- Quick! I need some water!
- Eight dollars!
[ Scoffs ]
Not in this lifetime.
Okay. This is it.
Otto?.
# Every rose has its thorn #
#Just like every cowboy#
#Sings a sad, sad song#
Becky, you're my rose.
Will you let me be your thorn?.
Oh, Otto. Of course my answer is-
Oooh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
This solo is kick-ass!
##[ Guitar Solo]
- Honey, could you turn it down?.
- Okay. But this better be worth it.
- Yes, I will marry you.
- Cool.
[ Kids Cheering ]
Hmm. Hmm.
Homer, look!
We're invited to Otto's wedding.
Ooh, and such
delicate tissue paper.
Huh?. Zig-Zag?
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
No knife games
on the kitchen table.
I didn't hit your precious table!
Ohhh, we're "cordially
invited this Saturday...
to join Otto and Becky
at 742 Evergreen Terrace"?.
That's our address!
I told Otto he could have the wedding here.
Hope that's okay.
You should have asked first, Bart.
Weddings are hard work and
cost thousands of dollars!
Hey, it'll be easy. You still got most of
the stuff from Apu's wedding back there.
[ Trumpeting ]
Oh, all right.
Otto can get married here.
But, Homer, you have
to get rid of that elephant.
[Whimpering ]
Let's see. Candles,
flowers, place cards, rice.
Oh, Mom, you're not supposed
to throw rice anymore.
Birds eat it, their stomachs swell,
and they explode.
Why am I just learning this now?.
[ Chuckles ]
##[ Organ ]
Son, your mother and I don't
approve of this marriage...
as we have not approved
of any part of your life to date.
- Well, the important thing is you came.
- We're leaving.
Drive safe.
[ Grunts ]
Always a bridesmaid, only occasionally a bride.
Lisa, it's time you learned
the truth about men.
- They're pigs?.
- The bitterness is strong in this one.
- [ Both Laughing ]
- [Whimpering ]
So, any words for
the bride and groom?.
Not now, Bart.
I'm trying to urinate.
You don't seem
to be trying very hard.
## [ Humming ]
Dad! The bride and groom are supposed
to cut the wedding cake.
Oh, that's just superstition.
- Thank you.
- [ Groans ]
## [ Humming ]
Mm-hmm.
## [Whistling ]
Oh, Becky, you look beautiful.
I thought you might want
to see this bridal magazine.
It's got 900 tips forth perfect marriage-
all don'ts.
Oh, we'll be fine. Otto's got a clean police record
and he doesn't do any needle drugs.
Well, the real key according
to sexperts is mutual interests.
No prob.
We like all the same things.
- Except-
- Mm-hmm?.
Don't tell Otto, but I'm not
into heavy metal and he loves it.
He refers to our lovemaking
as the Head bangers Ball!
Oh, you can fix little defects
like that with gentle nagging.
Make it part of the background
noise of your relationship.
That's how I polished Homer
into the perfect- Homer!
- No! That's ice!
- [ Grunting ]
## [ Humming ]
- ##[ Organ]
- And now- [ Clears Throat]
As forth matter of my honorarium.
- What?.
- You know, my emolument.
- Huh?.
- Pay me- $300.
300?. I could have gotten Rick Dees for that.
##["Here Comes the Bride"]
## [ Heavy Metal ]
Whoo!. [Laughing]
#Ah,yeah#
You got Poison to play
at our wedding?.
- We're Cyanide. A loving tribute to Poison.
- We need a ride home!
You expect me to walk down
the aisle to a monster ballad?.
Let me talk to Otto.
That's okay.
I guess this is sort of...
- [ Sobs ] our song.
- Well, it doesn't have to be.
Otto's just going to have to
decide what's more important-
his heavy metal or you.
##[Heavy Metal]
Becky, what have I done here?.
I'm so sorry.
In about 1 5 minutes,
I'd take off that wedding dress...
or you’re gonna look crazy!
[ Sobbing ]
Moe, can I give you some shrimp
forth road?.
Nah. I'll just take the ring pillow...
and these, uh,
seven presents I bring.
Ah, you know what?.
Cram some shrimp in too.
Head to tail.
That way you can fit more.
How about some sauce?.
Thanks.
Becky, I know
you must feel awful...
but at least this didn't happen
after you were married.
Yeah. It's better now than when
you're too old and fat to get another man.
I feel so low.
What am I going to do?.
Hey, why don’t you stay with us?.
Bart, remember that talk we had about
you volunteering our house?.
Remember that talk we had about
you not wrecking people's weddings?.
[ Groans ]
It's settled.
The stranger stays with us.
- Yea!
- [ Groans ]
# Ch-Ch-Ch-Changes #
#Time to change the oil #
# Changes
Don’t want to be an oily man #
A man innocently
changes his oil when...
a two-ton car
comes crashing down!
- # Changing oil ##
- Crashing down!
[ Grunting, Moans ]
Who'd have thought you could hold
up a car with a wicker basket?.
Now Lisa's going through this phase
where she doesn't eat any meat.
So I usually sneak a little meat juice
into her vegetables.
Wow! You're a real-life
Martha Stewart.
I mean, without the evil.
May I?.
Mmm, yummers!
Nobody's ever called
my gravy yummers before.
Mmm! You know what would be
really nuts?. A little rosemary.
Ooh! I've always wanted to
use rosemary in something.
[ Grunting ]
Mmm!
Mmm. Mom, this gravy tastes
better than God's sweat.
Thanks to our own
spice girl, Becky.
Well, Mom, you really brought
out the mung in these beans.
Actually, that was Becky too.
What are these things
in the mashed potatoes?.
That's the skins.
I left them on.
Well, nobody's perfect.
Let me just pick those out.
No! Oh, Becky, your potatoes
are the best I've ever had.
Oh, God.
- [ Karate Shouts ]
- [ Gasps ]
Stop kicking my baby!
Oh, it's cool. We're just putting some
Jackie Chan moves into Bart's video project.
Yeah, Mom. I need something great. Milhouse
has footage of himself falling down the stairs.
Well, no kicking.
It's too dangerous.
Marge, chill out. I have great control. See?.
[ Karate Shouts ]
That's very impressive,
but I still don't-Stop that!
[ Karate Shouts ]
- ##[Saxophone]
- [Becky Grunting]
Hello? Hello!.
We're jamming, Mom.
She's painting my music...
and I’m playing to her painting.
Isn't it wonderful to have
a hip female influence in the house?.
Yes. Well, I guess
I'll go roll socks.
It's not hip,
but it has to be done.
Actually, you could just tie them at the ends.
That way the elastic doesn't wear out.
Yes. I hate when things
get worn out.
Mmm, socks, welcomes.
She's so helpful.
And everyone loves her.
And, well, this may sound crazy...
but I think my family likes Becky more than me.
[ Laughing ]
- I wouldn’t worry about that.
- Oh, really?.
Yeah. You're gonna be dead
in a week anyway.
- Dead in a week?. What are you talking about?.
- Look, honey.
Never let an attractive woman
into your house.
All they ever do is usurp
your family and then kill you.
Like that documentary,
The Hand that Rocks the Cradle.
- That was a movie.
- Look, all we know...
is she's going to shoot you,
or stab you, or boil you.
Or club you with
an antique wooden doll.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, that was a good one.
Oh. But first, she's going
to seduce your husband.
Becky's going to seduce Homer?.
[ Both Groan ]
It's an act of violence, not love.
- [ Snoring ]
- [ Grunting ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Grunting ]
Oh, I'm sorry. Did I wake you?.
I wanted to return your hair dryer.
- [ Clicks ]
- [ Gasps ]
- Oh, and here's your brush.
- [Whimpers ]
You just enjoy
your grocery shopping, Marge.
And if you pick up some semolina,
I can make couscous for Lisa.
- It's my favorite!
- It is?.
Oh, yeah. You can learn a lot
from your kids if you just listen to 'em.
- [ Laughs ]
- [ Groans ]
Be right back.
Take your time.
Why do I always think of the perfect thing
to say when it's too late?.
"Shut up, Becky!"
Oh, that would have been sweet.
- [ Gasps ]
- [ Beeping ]
The "brakes cut"light!
Hmm?
[ Horn Honking ]
It's red!
- [ Groans ]
- [ Both Men Gasp ]
Wow. Tough glass.
- [ Camera Shutter Clicks ]
- I still say ours is bigger.
[ Screaming ]
Our speed bumps are stronger too.
I don't know, Simpson. How do I know
you didn't cut your own brakes?
- Why would I do that?.
- I don't know.
Get some attention from
a handsome police officer.
- That's crazy!
- [ Sighs ]
Look, I know I don't have any proof.
But this woman is trying to kill me!
Fine. Let me tell you what I tell everybody
who comes in here.
The law is powerless to help you.
Do I have to be dead
before you’ll help me?.
Well, not dead. Dying.
No, no, no, no. Don't walk away.
How 'bout this?.
Just show me the knife,
in your back, not too deep...
but it should be able
to stand by itself.
Come on, Becky.
Tell us your big news.
Well, I wanted to wait
for your mother, but okay.
- I found an apartment and I'm moving out.
- Oh, no.
Becky, I think I speak
for all of us when I say...
when's the ice cream
gonna get here?.
- [Thunderclap ]
- And God said, Gatherye two of every flavor.
Anoint them with 62 sauces,
whipped cream and nuts.
And ye shall call it...
the Ark!
[ Gasps, Panting ]
- Homer!
- Relax. He's gorging.
Okay, maybe not.
We gotta save him!
[ Grunts ]
[Marge Screaming]
Usurper! Usurper! Usurper!
Don't mess with me!
I've got jimmies!
- [ All Screaming ]
- I can only see a horrible rainbow!
- [ Gasps ]
- Shut up, Becky!
- There, I finally said it. [ Grunts ]
- [ Gasps ]
- [ Wiggum ] Drop the cone, sugar!
- [ Gunshot]
- Whoa. Whoopsie.
- Take her away, boys.
[ Groans ]
I thought you said the law was powerless.
Yeah, powerless to help you,
not punish you.
Mmm. Earned my treat.
This isn't over, Becky!
I know where you live!
My house!
Poor Maggie.
How many insanity hearings...
have you been to
in your short little life?.
Mrs. Simpson, before we begin...
- I just want to assure you that this is not a trial.
- [ Both Moan ]
- All right. It's a trial.
- [ Both ] Yes!
Now, Marge, according to this, you recently
went berserk in an ice-cream parlor.
- Yes.
- And, Marge...
did you ever have an unhealthy fixation
on Ringo Starr?.
It was healthy.
He reciprocated.
He reciprocated!
Mmm, please.
Road rage?. Excuse me.
What are you doing?.
Oh. I was just praying to God
that you’ll find me sane.
I see. And this "god,"
is he in this room right now?.
Oh, yes.
He's kind of everywhere.
- Mmm.
- Mm-mmm.
Marge Simpson, you give us no choice
but to declare you utterly-
I'm not insane!
You didn't let me finish.
Insane!
[ Gasps ]
[All Gasping ]
[Whimpering ]
[ Shouts ]
I'm not insane.
Run, Marge! Run!
Pump those crazy legs!
Police say escaped mental patient
Marge Simpson could be anywhere.
Even here at Juggernauts
where it's wet T-shirt month!
- [Women ] Whoo!
- But for now...
this reporter prays that Mad Marge
can be captured before she kills again.
Kills again?.
She hasn't killed once!
Shouldn’t we be out there
trying to find her?.
Don’t worry. She'll show up here sooner
or later to finish off Becky.
Then we'll have Mommy back.
[ Gasps ]
##[Marching Band]
[ Grunting ]
Come back!
Those are prescription pants!
Now, Ralphie, what are you gonna
do if you see Mrs. Simpson?.
Freeze, you crazy mommy!
That a boy. But you gotta aim
a little higher.
There you go.
That's a kill shot.
Well, we've got a special guest.
She just flew in
from the cuckoo's nest.
And, boy, is she crazy.
Crazy Marge Simpson!
- ##[Fanfare]
- [ Chuckles ] Look at that.
[ Man's Voice ]
Hello, Krusty.
Oh, that's funny.
So, Marge...
who's your favorite
Native American warrior?.
Crazy Horse!
Whoo, whoo, whoo!
[Blathering]
All right. Stop it!
Oh, this bit's dying.
Let's go to the
Mad Marge Dancers.
##["Sabre Dance"]
- Too soon.
- Oh, I really miss Mom.
The kids are saying if you say
"Bloody Margie" five times, she'll appear.
But then she gouges
your eyes out.
I hear she mates with men, then eats them.
I'm sure if Marge were here and not
crazy,
she'd be telling you two
to do your homework...
- and you to finish washing the dog.
- [ Flies Buzzing ]
[ Panting ]
Now let's find out
who this Becky really is.
[ Gasps ]
[ Groans ]
Hmm!
I really should read
the whole headline before I react.
Oh, my. I've been so unfair to Becky.
Maybe I am insane.
I mean,
I am talking to myself.
You are?. Oh, I thought
I'd made a friend.
Becky, I want to apologize
to- Usurper!
[ Karate Shout]
- Why, you little-
- [Bart] Cut. Cut!
Mom, it's great to have you back,
but you walked right into my shot.
- Shot?. What are you-
- I hope we didn't scare you, Marge.
Bart's just filming a music video
for his class project.
And I'm directing
the "making of" video.
Oh. Well, then I guess there's
a reasonable explanation for everything...
except you cutting my brakes.
Oh, about that.
When I changed your oil...
I may have drained
your brake fluid.
I didn't say anything 'cause
I thought you’d be mad.
Oh, boy. My bad.
Becky, I'm so sorry
I accused you...
of trying to kill me
and steal my family.
Hey, no biggie.
I was trying to steal your family.
I even thought of
a good place to bury you.
Then I didn't have a shovel, so I went to the
hardware store. They have six different kinds.
- I was, like, "Later"
- Well, that's a relief, too, knowing I'm not crazy.
So I guess everything
really worked out for the-
- [ Gasps ]
- Mom!
- You monsters! You killed her!
- No, they didn't.
- [ All Gasp ]
- God!
We put enough tranquilizers in there
to take down Jonathan Winters.
Oh, I've got too much to do
to take a nap right now.
Lisa, get Maggie out
of that cage.
And, Homer, since
you're dressed for it...
I got some S & M for ya-
scrubbing and mopping.
Thank you.
- [ Murmuring ]
- Shh!
www.tvsubtitles.net