[Chorus ]
# the Simpsons #
BEHIND THE LAUGHTER
[ Bell Ringing]
[ Whistle Blowing]
[ Beeping ]
## [Jazzy Solo ]
[ Tires Screeching ]
D'oh!
[ Screams ]
[ Rattling ]
[ Chorus ]
# the Simpsons #
[ Man Narrating] they were the first family
of American laughter...
surfing a tidal wave of hilarity...
[ Man ]
Look at her vacuum.
onto the sands of Superstar Bay.
## [ Dramatic Cue ]
But behind the chortles, this funny five some
was trapped in a private hell.
Everybody wanted a piece of us.
They told us what to wear...
how to dress,
which clothes we should put on.
The cops found me
driving on the sidewalk.
I had no business hosting the Oscars.
After the show,
Meryl Streep  spit on me.
[Narrator] tonight: the Simpsons,
as you’ve never seen them before...
on Behind the Laughter.
##[ Rock]
##[ Ends ]
[ Narrator]
the Simpson's amazing journey began here...
in the bustling heartland town
of Springfield.
On this unassuming street,
two nobodies...
named Homer and Marge Simpson
settled down to raise a family.
- First came baby Bart.
- [ Babbling ]
- then, Lisa Simpson.
[ Chuckles, Gasps ]
[ Grunting ]
- And finally, Maggie.
- [ Snoring ]
[ Gasps ]
Eh!
Nobody told us
how tough it is to raise kids.
They almost drove me
to fortified wine.
Then we figured out we could
park them in front of the TV.
That's how I was raised,
and I turned out TV.
I'd see 'em sitting
on that couch all day long...
just staring at that
Hollywood Hogwash.
Our favorite show was Hollywood Hogwash,
but we also loved the Dreck Squad.
the Malarkeys,
Dumbin' it Down.
- Sheriff Lowbrow.
- Home Improvement.
But we never saw people
like us on TV.
TV families were always
hugging and tackling issues.
Homer kept saying he could do
a more realistic family show.
Finally, I said, "So do it.
Either [ Bleep]
or get off the pot."
[Narrator]
And[Bleep] he did.
Using his home as the studio
and his family as the cast...
this penniless Peckinpah
shot a crude five-minute video.
My Funny Family, take one!
And... action!
Honey, I 'm home. The boss is coming to dinner,
and I need a clean shirt.
I haven't done the laundry yet.
Mamma mia!
Now I'll have to do it!
## [ Humming ]
- Dad, that's too much detergent.
- Not now!
I'm busy turning on
this washing machine.
- [Whirring ]
- [ Both Gasp]
Simpson!
- Where's my dinner?.
- Mamma mia!
It was amazing how fast Dad betrayed
his vision of a realistic show.
Okay, the material was a little corny.
But Homer and I had
real chemistry on screen.
Every day I thought
about firing Marge.
You know,
just to shake things up.
[Narrator] Homer didn’t fire Marge,
but he did shake things up-
- show business things.
- D'oh!
[ Horn Honks ]
[ Narrator] He tried to show his demo tape
to the major networks...
but couldn't get past the guards.
- [ Clanks ]
[ Clanking Continues ]
Fortunately,
I had a network connection.
The man who cut my hair
was also president of Fox.
##[Studio Fanfare ]
[ Narrator]
the Simpsons had their foot in the door.
Fox ordered 13 episodes.
But would the public respond?
M-E-R.
Okay.
- R-U-P-E-R-T.
- You're almost there. Good.
- # Well, shake it up, baby #
- [ Screaming ]
# Shake it up, baby
Twist and shout, Twist and shout #
- ##[ Continues, Indistinct]
- [ Laughing, Gurgling ]
I first knew the show was a hit
when I walked into school...
and a kid was wearing
a Bart Simpson T-shirt.
Fox had  an endless supply
of clever  slogans, man.
Suddenly I was invited
to every birthday party.
Sometimes I'd have to read the cake
just to know who I was singing to.
[ Narrator]
The Simpsons was a smash.
Viewers couldn't get enough of the show's
fractured take on the modern family.
The funniest stuff
came right out of real life.
Son, let's go out for
frosty chocolate milk shakes.
- Cowabunga, dude!
- And... cut!
Dad, I've never said "Cowabunga" in my life.
Your script sucks.
- Why, you little- [ Sputtering ]
- [ Choking ]
- Hey, that's funny.
- [ Crew Laughing]
- [ Sputtering ]
- [ Choking ]
- [Laughing Continues ]
- And that horrible act of child abuse...
became one of our most
beloved running gags.
[Narrator] With Simpson merchandise
selling like crazy...
and Simpson Gin wetting whistles worldwide,
the money was pouring in.
[ All Laughing ]
[ Both Growling ]
We were using $50 bills
as toilet paper...
and toilet paper as dog toilet paper.
[ All Laughing ]
Mmm. Ah.
[Narrator] Convinced that the good times
would never stop rolling...
the Simpsons moved out of their trademark
house and into M.C. Hammer's.
[ Grunting ]
Mm.
We found a secret room that was filled
to the ceiling with parachute pants.
I'm wearing some now.
## [ Vocalizing ]
- [ Exhales ]
- [Narrator] But pants or no pants...
the Simpsons were flying high.
Yeah, I've seen all
the overnight sensations-
Brad Hall, Rich Hall,
Rich Little, Little Richard-
but the Simpsons
blew 'em all away.
They even had a hit record.
Meanwhile, Krustophenia
sits on the shelf.
None of us had ever sung before,
but Mr. Geffen believed in us.
#We're gonna groove tonight #
#We'll make you feel all right #
# Simpsons boogie ##
[Narrator]
Simpsons Boogie...
Lovely to Love Your Lovin'...
and Simpsons Christmas Boogie
went mega-platinum and swept the Grammys.
Right. And the award for
Best Hard-core Thrash Metal goes to...
Simpsons Christmas Boogie?
# Simpsons Christmas Boogie #
[ Gags, Spits ]
[ Narrator] For America's favorite family,
everything was coming up roses.
But those roses contained
ready-to-sting bees.
- [ Buzzing ]
- When we come back-
I want to set
the record straight.
I thought the cop
was a prostitute.
[ Narrator]
When Behind the Laughter continues.
##[ Rock]
##[Rock]
[Narrator]
Byte end of their first season...
the Simpsons were burning up
Nielsen boxes in the U.S...
and creating a sensation overseas.
Hello, Mr. Lobster! D'oh!
[ Screams ]
[ Spits, Laughing ]
Oh, dear!
[ Laughing ]
[ Narrator]
Bathtubs of money, wheel  barrows of awards...
fire hoses of respect-
the Simpsons had it all.
[ Cheering ]
- [ Groaning ]
- Hmm.
[ Narrator]
But behind the streamers and confetti...
storm clouds were gathering.
- [ Thunderclap ]
- Figurative storm clouds.
Oh, Homer was spending money
like a... teenage Arab. [ Chuckles ]
He bought me a Rolex
and cashmere jeans.
I felt kinda guilty 'cause I was always tryin'
to score with his wife.
So when do we start filming?.
Oh.
Even Bart was
throwin' dough around.
He paid me and Carl a thousand bucks
to kiss each other.
Hey, did we ever get
that money?.
[typing]
[Narrator] But reckless spending
and interracial homoeroticism...
were just volume one
of The Encyclopedia Self-Destructica.
- Even more harrowing were the
events of one April afternoon.
- [Jingling ]
The script originally
called for me to jump the gorge.
But I'd been up all night paying people to kiss,
so Dad volunteered to do the stunt.
Everything was going great at first.
I felt like I was king of the world.
I'm king of the world!
Whoo-hoo! Whoo-hoo!
- Right about here I realize something's wrong.
- [Screaming]
- Yep. There I go.
- [ Grunting ]
then came the rocks-jagged rocks,
hitting me with their jags.
- [ Groaning ]
- [ Narrator] the sequence became
an instant comedy classic.
But what the audience didn't see
was the unfunny aftermath.
[ Screaming ]
[ Sputtering, Gulps ]
Mmm.
[ Narrator] Somehow,
Homer became addicted to painkillers.
It was the only way
he could perform...
- the bone-cracking physical comedy...
- Ow! My leg!
- that made him a star.
- This is the worst pain ever!
- Ow!
- Stop pummeling me!
- It's really painful!
- [ Screaming ]
Why did I take such punishment?.
Let's just say that fame was like a drug.
-[Whistling, Screaming ]
-But what was even more like a drug was the drugs.
[Narrator]
But despite their mounting problems...
the Simpsons’ star continued to rise,
like a plastic bag caught in an updraft.
[ Lisa Narrating] It was such an honor
to be on the Walk of Fame.
I mean, there we were with Hollywood
royalty like Milton Berle and Nelson Mandela.
And just a few stars down
from the Cheerios honeybee.
Awards and honors are great,
but they don't pay the pickle man.
We were earning millions,
but we were always strapped for cash.
One time, Lisa bought a first edition
of Susan B. Anthony Man.
Her check bounced higher
than Rubber Girl.
[ Narrator]
Where did the money go?
Marge lost much of the family fortune
investing in birth control products.
I learned something.
When people reach for their diaphragm...
they don't want to see my picture.
[ Narrator]As the Simpsons’ money
dwindled, their expenses soared.
From the original group of five,
the cast ballooned to dozens...
then hundreds.
I 'd never acted before
in my life, but, uh...
if the sea captain
could be in the show, why not me?
I 've even got a catchphrase.
Nyah! Whaa!
Whaa, whaa, whaa!
Now I lost it.
[ Narrator]
then, another bombshell.
An anonymous tipster
alerted Uncle Sam...
that the Simpsons were
evading their income taxes.
[ Apu's Voice ] Yes, I finked on Homer,
but, you know, he deserved it.
Never have I seen such abuse
of the "Take a penny, leave a penny" tray.
- [ Narrator] the tax men were merciless.
- Hey!
- [ Whirring ]
- [ Sputtering, Screaming ]
- Oh!
- [ Snaps Fingers ]
Hey! They can't take our house!
My potbellied pig is in there!
[ Sobbing ]
Ah, Mr. Porky! No!
[ Sobbing Continues ]
[Narrator]
Inevitably, the behind-the-scenes turmoil...
took its toll on their TV series.
- [ Man ] And... action!
- ## [ theme ]
Hold on! Cut!
- Oh, for crying out loud!
- Oh, man! Oh!
Bart, if it's not
too much trouble-
Fine. I'll do teen Wolf3.
I've got fair-weather friends to feed.
Dad, I want to go to bed.
Aren't there child labor laws?.
Who told you about those laws?.
Was it Marge?.
Hey, you've been riding me all day.
Why don’t you poop in your hat?.
Are you going to need us tonight?.
I have ballet tickets-
not that they'll do much good now.
[Narrator] With the family in disarray,
episodes increasingly resorted...
to  gimmicky premises
and nonsensical plots.
I 'm... an impostor.
- That man is the real Seymour Skinner.
- [ Crowd Gasps ]
[ Narrator] trendy guest stars
were shamelessly trotted out to grab ratings.
[ Electronic Voice ] If you are looking
for trouble, you've found it.
Just try me, you-
Oh!
[ Karate Yells ]
[ Narrator] But there were
bigger problems off-screen.
After judging a Miss Hawaiian tropic
beauty contest...
at the Sheraton
Hali'a Kalua Lea...
- Bart created a ruckus on a Hawaiian Airline jet...
- [ Camera Shutters Clicking ]
attacking several flight attendants.
While he was in rehab,
the part of Bart Simpson was played...
by his good friend Richie Rich.
Bart, what do you mean
you have jury duty?.
Don't have a cow, Mother.
[ Narrator]
Fans reacted to these...
- slapdash episodes with yawns.
- [ Man Yawns ]
- Angry yawns.
- [Angry Yawn ]
Desperate to polish
their tarnished image, the family agreed...
to a live appearance
at the Iowa State Fair.
Right from the start
I had a bad feeling about that gig.
- ## [ Country]
- [ Narrator] It was an evening
none of them would ever forget.
Or would they?
No.
[ Cheering ]
- Hello, Iowa! Does anyone have a doughnut?.
- ##[ Rim Shot ]
[ Laughing ]
Now, Homer, this is no time
to be thinking about food.
Yeah, forget the doughnuts.
We're here to go nuts.
- Musically, that is.
- What kind of song should we play?.
Something that swings
with the beat of New Orleans.
No. Something that rocks.
That's the sound of today.
- Swings!
- Rocks!
[Narrator] Sadly, this argument
was not part of the act.
- I'll kill you!
- [ Grunts ] You don't have the guts, little man!
Folks, we're just having a little family tiff.
If you’ll just bear with us-
Oh, shut up!
Always trying to act so mature.
- I'm glad you make the least money.
- Oh, that's it!
- Hey, hey, stop it!
- Stop it!
- You- Let go of me!
- [Narrator] Before a riot could break out...
Jimmy Carter came to the rescue
with his comedy break dancing.
- # Got a brother named Billy
and my teeth look silly #
- [ Cheering, Laughing]
# Break it down now ##
Whoa! Whoa!
- [ Cheering ]
- [ Exclaims ]
Come on, you!
I'll get- [ Screams ]
- [Narrator] the dream was over.
- [ Busy Signal Beeping ]
Coming up: Was the dream really over?
Yes, it was.
Or was it?
And Homer finds a new passion:
dusting and polishing
mixing boards.
When Behind the Laughter
continues.
## [ Rock]
[ Narrator] the Simpsons' TV show
started out on a wing and a prayer.
But now the wing was on fire,
and the prayer...
- had been answered- by Satan.
- [ Laughing ]
After the state fair fiasco, none of the family
were speaking to each other.
Fox put the show on hiatus
and replaced it...
with hidden camera footage
from the dressing room at Ann Taylor.
That slugfest at the state fair
was really a blessing.
It gave us a chance
to pursue solo projects.
I returned to my first love-
the legitimate theater.
As a young female artist...
I really love living
in this East Village loft.
- [Knocking]
- Oh. That must be our new landlord...
Mr. Stingley.
[ Laughs ]
#Where is the rent
I must have the rent #
# Dollars, dimes and nickels #
# I need them all right now ##
I literally chewed the scenery.
[Narrator] the other family members
were also spreading their creative wings.
- ##[ Rock]
- Bart replaced Lorenzo Lamas...
in the syndicated action
series Renegade.
I f Esposito thinks he's gonna muscle us,
he's wrong.
I hear that, Renegade.
Let's do this thing.
##[Rock]
- [Narrator]
Marge put together a nightclub act.
- ##[Intro ]
# I shot the sheriff #
# But I did not shoot
the deputy #
# She didn't do it
She didn't do it #
So the next time
you see a sheriff, shoot him.
- [ Gasping ]
- A smile.
- [ Laughing ]
- Good night, Laughlin.
- #She didn't do it
She didn't do it ##
- [Applause]
[Narrator]
Lisa sang too-
in a tell-all book
blasting the family.
To prolong
the run of the series...
I was secretly given
anti-growth hormones.
- [ Groaning ]
- [ Shutters Clicking ]
That's ridiculous.
How could I even get all five necessary drops
into her cereal?.
What?.
In that family,
nobody trusted nobody.
They even brought their lawyers
to Thanksgiving dinner.
So, uh, how's everybody doing?.
- You don't have to answer that.
- Shut up, all of you, or I'll sue.
Oh, save it for your next book,
you little snitch.
That's assault!
That is assault!
It was the best Thanksgiving ever.
I mean, emotionally it was terrible,
but the turkey was so moist.
[Narrator] the carcass of the Simpsons'
empire had been picked clean.
- [ Squawking ]
- But then came help from an unexpected source.
I knew there was only one person
who could reunite this troubled clan-
my old fraternity brother
Willie Nelson.
I'd do anything
for keg-meisterJulius.
So I cooked up
a phony awards show.
[ Alarm Wailing ]
Not again.
Time saver, my ass.
When Willie asked me to be a presenter
at the New Awareness Awards...
I had to think about it-
for about a microsecond.
You just don't say no
to the Red Headed Stranger.
And when I heard it was for awareness,
that sealed the deal.
[Narrator] Would Willie's
fence-mending eggs bear fruit?
Or would his olive branch
be torn apart by woodpeckers of mistrust?
that night,
fate wore a cummerbund... of suspense.
[ Applause ]
Thank you, Taco, for that
loving tribute to Falco.
And now, to present the award
for Most Violent Rap Group, Homer Simpson.
- [Applause]
- Hi.
- And Marge Simpson.
- What?.
- [Applause Continues ]
- What's she doing here?.
- And Bart and Lisa Simpson!
- [ Gasps ]
Hey! What's going on?.
Well, I'll be honest. The New Awareness
Awards are all an elaborate sham.
What?. [ Sputters ]
I knew it was too good to be true.
So this whole thing was just a trick
to get us back together?.
Well, I'm also trying to patch things up
between Van Halen and Sammy Hagar.
- [ All ] Hmm.
- But the main thing...
is for you folks to stop
this silly feud.
- Isn't that right, people?.
- [ Cheering ]
- Hug! Hug! Hug!
- [ Crowd] Hug! Hug! Hug!
Hug! Hug! Hug! Hug!
[Narrator] the Simpsons'
bitter past was forgotten.
and now the future looks
brighter than ever for this northern Kentucky  family
We put all the craziness
behind us.
And now it's time to get back
to what matters- the show.
And the Sunday comic strip.
- Which Homer writes himself.
- So you know it's great.
- Why, you little- [ Sputtering ]
- [ Choking ]
[Narrator] So, whether choking their son
or poking some fun...
the Simpsons will keep on
gagging for years to come.
- [ Tape Rewinds ]
- I can't believe it! We won another contest!
The Simpsons are going
to Delaware!
- I want to see Wilmington!
- I want to visit a screen door factory.
This will be the last season.
[Narrator] Next week on
Behind the Laughter:. Huckleberry Hound.
I was so gay.
But I couldn't tell anyone.
##[ Rock]
##[ Disco ]
# We're gonna groove tonight
We'll make you feel all right#
# Simpsons Christmas boogie #
# We're dancing to the beat
We'll make you move your feet#
# Simpsons Christmas boogie #
# Simpsons Christmas boogie ##
- [ Murmuring ]
- Shh!
www.tvsubtitles.net