I got it, I got it.
You're like a bee at a damn picnic,
Marie.
- Morning.
- Hey, buddy.
- Ready to get your rocks on?
- See? I knew it.
"Mineral show" is just some sort of
guy code for "strip club."
Yeah. You got your singles?
- Got it?
- Yeah.
Don't let him get too crazy, okay?
Cram one more giant geode in here,
we'll be sleeping in the garage.
- Got it. I got it.
- I'm sorry.
Christ. Longest week ever.
Here's just hoping
we get something good.
Keep your fingers crossed.
Relax, buddy, this ain't no spy movie.
It's more like Rocky, you know?
Get the bad guy.
Yeah!
- But... What are you doing, buddy?
- Leaving.
You gotta go inside, order something
like last time. Avoid suspicion.
Besides, I want a vanilla shake.
We'll use the drive-through.
All right, baby,
let's see what we got.
What the hell? Look at this.
That's work. That's home.
That's work, that's home.
What, this guy...
...he goes two places every day,
all week?
It's unbelievable.
Chicken-slinging son of a bitch.
Hank, is it possible that maybe,
just maybe...
...he's not your guy?
A guy this clean has got to be dirty.
What's the play here, buddy?
How do I get this guy?
Yeah.
How?
Yes, hi.
I live on the 4900 block
of Doswell Place and I want to report...
He's sitting in a blue sedan...
...and he's been staring at
a particular house for a very long time.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
If you would, I would appreciate it.
All right.
I guess we'd better get started.
I already did.
Yeah?
Hey.
Got one of those for me?
- One of those what?
- Cigarette.
Look, it's still in there, all right?
I didn't get a chance yet.
Just give me one.
So, what have you been up to?
What?
You know, just a day in the life.
What do you do after work?
Go home. watch TV.
What do you watch?
I don't know, stuff.
Well, like what?
Like lce Road Truckers.
Ice Road Truckers.
What happens on that one?
Guys drive on ice.
I am gonna do it.
You gotta inhale, by the way.
What the hell, man? Don't you have
enough cancer already? Look.
I said...
...I'd do it. I'll do it.
Yeah, well...
...what does it matter?
We're both dead men anyway.
- Hi.
Am I catching you at a bad time?
No. I have a few minutes.
So Mr.
I'm-Almost-Sixteen-Leave-Me-Alone...
...doesn't want a big birthday,
just wants to hang out with friends...
- ...which is fine by me. You?
- Fine by me.
Okay. So I figured a low-key family
dinner, no official party...
...and we bite the bullet...
...and buy him a car.
Used, I was thinking, would be best.
But no more than five years old.
Airbags, safety-rated, all that.
Do you have any thoughts
on what kind?
Or should I just go ahead and...
Yeah. You just go ahead.
Okay.
Listen, on another subject,
I just wanted to tell you...
...that business is good.
Really good.
So good that I'm thinking, maybe...
...you don't need to even work...
...your second job.
- You're turning a profit?
- We're coming close.
Give us another month or two and,
yeah, we'll be there.
All of this to say...
...maybe you could start thinking
about an exit strategy.
I'm working on it.
Okay.
- Hello?
- Hey, buddy. Wake you?
No, Hank. I'm up.
Good. What you doing?
I'm...
Hey, listen, I'll cut to it.
Another favor to ask.
I'm thinking about Gus Fring.
How he never goes anywhere.
One restaurant, home,
back and forth?
I'm even more convinced it's bullshit...
...because he owns
13 other restaurants. Right?
So I start thinking
about this little empire of his.
Fourteen restaurants. Who supplies
them? What's the base of operations?
So I do a little digging, and bingo.
Polios Hermanos
has a main distribution center.
It's not far from town.
The place is huge. I mean...
...I'm looking at it online now.
It's a big warehouse...
...and rows
of these long, poultry buildings...
...or hatcheries,
whatever you call them.
Lots of space to hide illicit activity.
Sounds promising, right?
So, what do you say, buddy?
Got another field trip in you?
You know, Hank, I'm... I'm... I'm...
I mean, it sounds great, it really does.
But I'm...
You know, I won't lie.
You've caught me somewhat...
...indisposed.
What do you mean,
like taking-a-dump indisposed?
Yeah. That's embarrassing.
That's it.
You know, it's just upset stomach and,
you know, everything...
- Yeah.
- It's out of control.
And it's really explosive.
Bad Tex-Mex...
- ...at the mall.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. I get it.
You don't have to paint a picture.
One guy in a diaper is enough
for this trip.
- Yeah, and I'm sorry, Hank.
- Hey, don't be.
I've been asking a lot of you lately.
I appreciate it. I'll find another ride.
- Another ride?
- Yeah.
I'm sure I can get someone else
to take me.
My trainer, Chuck.
Maybe I'll ask him.
Well, look, I'm...
This is probably just a 24-hour thing.
Maybe 48 hours at the most.
And do you think you can possibly
hold off for a day or two?
Jeez, buddy, I mean, I...
You know, I just...
I would just really...
...love to be the one
to be able to take you there.
And, I mean, I've just really...
...enjoyed, you know,
the time with you...
- ...and helping you and...
- Well, yeah.
Okay, sure.
If it means that much to you.
Just, you know, give me a call
when you're feeling up to it.
Thank you. I will. Okay.
Bye.
- Yeah.
- Mike, listen.
I just want to say first off,
don't be angry.
What is it, Walter?
My brother-in-law, my DE... He...
Soon, he will probably,
in the near future...
...take a ride out
to a certain distribution center...
...to look around for things.
Just...
...look around for things. And, yeah.
Mike?
- Where's this all going?
- Elsewhere.
Thank you. Please give this
to your car-care professional.
So a hand wax for you today?
Okay, great.
Please give this
to your car-care professional.
And the black Explorer,
we could shampoo your floor mats...
...but deluxe detailing
is the best for your buck.
And SUV's are extra.
And please give this
to your car-care professional.
Thank you.
Please give this
to your car-care professional.
Hey, Sky.
Oh, my God. Ted.
What are you...?
Someone from the office...
...said you worked down here.
So I thought I'd come down and say hi.
Well...
...hello.
You look great.
No. No, I don't.
I probably just look crazed.
Not at all. You look happy.
Last time I saw you...
Hi, there.
I guess, Skyler...
...I'm gonna need to talk to you.
Ted, I really don't think
we have anything to talk about.
Actually, we do.
An audit?
Wait, an audit tomorrow?
- How long have you had this?
- A while.
I debated, you know, contacting you.
Contact me?
What about a lawyer, Ted?
Ted, this is...
This is the CID.
The criminal division.
My God,
you're facing a felony charge here.
A $100,000 fine
on top of the taxes you already owe...
- ...plus five years in prison.
- Yeah.
- It's bad.
It most certainly is.
Look, here's the thing.
I was wondering, maybe...
...if you could help with this.
Help?
Help how?
Well, with your knowledge
of how the books...
...got the way they are,
maybe there's some way...
...you could undo what's in there.
You want me to uncook your books?
Maybe there's some method or some
accounting trick you could use...
Ted, it doesn't work like that.
The damage is already...
My name.
My signatures...
...are all over those books.
Skyler, I'm accountable, not you.
Let me explain
what's going to happen here, okay?
Once the CID
sees this is willful tax fraud...
...they will build the strongest
possible case against you.
Once they start down that path, they
have an 80 percent conviction rate.
That's because they're allowed
to monitor your mail...
...and tap your phones,
and not just you, Ted...
...everyone involved in those books.
I can't have this in my life.
I cannot be audited.
Skyler, you're going to be fine, okay?
They're after me.
It's the captain they want,
not some cashier at a car wash.
No offense.
I'm sorry. I...
Look, I don't want you to worry, okay?
I'm going to figure out
a way through this, somehow. Okay?
Here.
So is he gonna kill him?
Is who gonna kill who?
Gus.
Is he gonna kill Mr. White's
brother-in-law?
I mean, he's the reason
for all of this here, right?
Because it's totally logical for him
to off the dude.
A-hole DEA agent
poking around your junk.
Who needs that, right?
Makes sense to get rid of him
for good.
But killing a cop...
...I don't know.
It could look suspicious...
...if the dude who's investigating you
suddenly up and dies.
Then there's... There's Mr. White...
...who would be even more apeshit
if he had family getting murdered.
He'd never cook for Gus again.
Guess there's a lot of angles
to consider.
If something were to happen to him,
would you have a problem with that?
Who really cares what I think?
Son of a bitch.
You get comfortable, kid.
We may be here a while.
Hey.
Get down!
Tell them...
...the answer is "yes."
- Should I even ask?
- I wouldn't.
So, what? Is this going to be
a regular thing now?
Meth cooking and corpse disposal?
Jesus.
Just grab us a spare barrel,
Walter.
What was it this time?
What did this poor bastard do
to piss off Gus?
Or did Gus need to send
another message?
Shut your mouth.
You shut your mouth
or I'll shut it for you.
I don't want you talking to me
or Jesse. Just get the barrel.
And if you ever plan on calling
the cops on one of my guys again...
...you go ahead and get two barrels.
Like...
...I guess I never thanked you for
what you did.
Thanks.
Next time don't stand there
like an idiot.
Move your feet.
Running and so forth.
But seriously, what...?
- What was the deal with Gus?
- The deal?
That Terminator shit.
Walking right into the bullets.
What the hell was he doing?
The cartel needs Gus.
His distribution network.
They're not looking to kill him.
But, what? The rest of us are like
open season?
Is he doing anything about that,
or do we keep hanging out...
- ...for target practice while he...?
- Kid.
Enough. You got questions,
ask him yourself.
And here again.
Unreported income.
That's more than a year straight so far.
You want to say something about this?
I'm having a hard time figuring it out.
I'd have to...
...have a look at the copies of
the receipts to refresh my memory.
Take all the time you need,
Mr. Beneke. That's why we're here.
Oh, I am so sorry I am late.
I got lost. Hey, Ted.
- Sky.
- This building is so confusing.
There are doors everywhere.
- Hi. You are...?
- Special Agent James Bekaris.
"Special." Skyler White.
Ms. white,
you are the accountant of record...
...for many of these reports,
is that correct?
- Guilty as charged.
- Can you shed light...
...on this history
of missing revenue?
Missing? No, it's there.
No. Revenue most definitely
flowed through this company...
...but it's not all accounted for
in your reports.
Let's take a look.
Oh, well, you know...
...this account here,
that is Mr. Keller's account.
And Mr. Keller is an old friend
of Ted's dad.
He always sends
an electronic payment...
...which I hate,
because I'm a real-paper person.
Mr. Keller is
one of those environmental people.
Since there wasn't
a physical check...
...I didn't enter it into the book.
But the money is there.
Ms. white, you've read Section 61
of the lRC?
I did not follow what you just said.
How gross income for a business is
defined, you're not allowed to do that.
- Well, I think I am.
- No, you're not.
Well, you know what they say about
opinions, right? Everyone's got one.
But seriously, I am.
It doesn't matter if it's an
electronic check or a paper check...
When I input everything
into the Quicken...
...nothing flashed red,
so that's gotta mean it's okay, right?
Quicken.
You used Quicken to manage books
for a business this size.
I did. Do you guys use that here?
Because it is the best.
It's like having a calculator
on your computer. Amazing.
- Ms. white, how did you get this job?
- Ted hired me.
No, I mean your qualifications.
What are your qualifications?
Where did you get your training?
Well, I haven't had any training,
per se.
I've always been naturally good
with numbers.
Got a good instinct for them.
Right, Teddy?
Right.
This is all falling into place now.
Ms. white, I just have to ask.
You're not managing accounts...
- ...anywhere else, are you?
- Right now? No.
I'm a cashier at a car wash.
I'm not really clear about what
happened in there.
What happened was good news.
Ignorance of the law...
...doesn't equate to criminality.
It equates to ignorance.
Pay your back taxes,
pay the penalties...
...and move on from this.
Just put it behind you.
Pay with what?
I owe them $617,000. What am I...?
Look, just figure it out, all right?
And you've just dodged prison.
Sell your assets. Get rid of the BMW,
take out a second mortgage...
Second mortgage?
I have a lien on my house.
I don't have any assets.
There are no assets left to sell.
Ted, if you don't pay them,
they will reopen the investigation...
...and that little fiction I just spun up
there is gonna completely unravel.
You have to settle.
Wish I could.
Come in.
I hope you brought an appetite.
Yeah, I guess.
Mike mentioned you have
some questions.
Yeah.
We'll eat first, and then we'll talk.
Right on.
What am I doing here?
I know you have concerns.
What happened yesterday,
to my man at the farm...
...it was a terrible thing.
The dude getting his head
blown off? Yeah.
I've invited you into my home...
...prepared food
so we could sit and talk.
Discuss what's going on in
this business...
...our business, like men.
And I will explain everything
that is happening.
I will answer your questions.
But first...
...I need you
to answer one question for me.
Can you cook Walter's formula?
What?
Walter's formula.
Can you produce his product
without any help? Alone.
No.
Why?
You're asking me if I can cook
Mr. white's crystal?
Without him?
Me?
The junkie loser
you were about to waste...
...and dump in the desert
a month ago.
This your plan?
Invite me in your house,
make whatever this is...
...be my buddy...
...and make me feel important.
Then get me to keep cooking for you
after you kill Mr. white?
You wanna...
You wanna talk like men?
Let's talk like men. You kill Mr. White,
you're gonna have to kill me too.
That is not what I asked you.
You are here because circumstances
with the cartel are untenable.
And I need your help.
I need you to help prevent
an all-out war.
Now, if you would...
...answer the question.
Hey, you headed out?
Yeah.
Yo, Mr. White, hey. I really gotta
talk to you. I don't know if you're...
...with your family or whatever,
but this is important...
...so I'm hoping you could come over.
Thank God. Come on in.
- You... You want a beer or something?
- No.
- Should I sit down?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. Sorry, go ahead.
Okay, so...
Okay, so word has come down
that they...
They want me to go to Mexico.
There's some...
Some sort of war brewing...
- ...between Gus and the cartel.
- "Word has come down"?
The cartel has been... Has been
messing with Gus' operation.
Like jacking trucks to,
like, send a message.
And yesterday,
that dude we brought to the lab.
I mean, they shot him right in
front of me. Just blew his head open.
Some sniper nailed him from
like a mile away.
Anyway, they've been holding
them off.
But between the cartel
taking potshots...
...and your brother-in-law trying
to throw a net over the whole deal...
...it's like what you call
a rock-and-a-hard-place situation.
So, Gus is... ls gonna cave.
So the cartel wants half
of Gus' entire operation...
...and they want your formula.
And he's gonna give it to them.
Well, I... I gotta give it to them. I mean,
I'm supposed to go to Mexico...
...and teach a bunch of cartel chemists
how to cook a batch of blue.
You know,
and Gus doesn't trust you...
...so I gotta go.
I mean, you're the chemist, man...
...you know, not me.
I mean, let's say I go down to...
You know, go over there.
Go to the jungle or whatever...
...and they got like actual chemists...
...like cartel chemists asking me
chemistry stuff...
...that I don't know how to
answer because I'm not you.
And what if all the equipment
is in Mexican instead of English?
You know?
I don't know. I don't know.
I mean, if I mess this up...
...I'm dead, you know? All of us.
Mr. white, look, I need...
l need your help.
Okay, maybe you could...
Maybe you could coach me...
...or something, you know.
Or give me some notes.
Mr. white?
So you saw Gus?
What? No.
- You didn't see Gus.
- No.
Then who told you all of that?
It was passed down, like I said.
"Passed down." By whom?
By... By Mike and them.
- I mean, they did. They...
- So "they" doesn't include Gus.
You haven't been with Gus.
You haven't seen Gus.
You haven't spoken to Gus.
- Why are you...?
- You weren't at Gus' house last night.
What?
What the hell? Jesus.
Still here.
- It's still here.
- Jesus.
You look me in the eye
and you tell me...
...that you weren't at his house
last night.
L...
Look, I didn't have a chance,
all right?
Okay? I knew you would react
this way.
I knew you would freak out
and wouldn't believe me.
That's why I didn't say anything.
Look, there was just this one
big pot of stew.
He just made this one big pot
and we both ate from it.
What was I supposed to do,
poison myself?
Two hours, 18 minutes, you couldn't
figure out a way to give it to him?
- He never left the room.
- You lying little shit!
You had one thing to do, one thing.
That is the only thing, I might add,
that would save our lives...
...and you were right there.
You were in his house...
...and you didn't have the guts
to do it.
Two hours and 18 minutes?
You never had any intention
of killing him, did you?
How did you know
I was at his house last night?
Were you following me?
This. This is how I knew.
- You bugged my car?
- 7:10 to 9:28 p.m.
Two hours and 18 minutes.
But you had no intentions, did you?
Not the slightest intention.
Everything that I have done for you.
You put a bug on my car?
I'm sorry,
after everything you've done for me?
What you've done for me?
You killed me, is what you've done!
You've signed my death warrant! Now
you want advice? I'll give you advice:
Go to Mexico and screw up
like I know you will.
Wind up in a barrel somewhere!
You son of a...
Can you walk?
Yeah.
Then get the fuck out of here
and never come back.