[ Chorus ]
# The Simpsons #
[ Bell Ringing ]
[ Whistle Blowing ]
[ Beeping ]
## [Jazzy Solo ]
[ Tires Screeching ]
D'oh!
[ Screams ]
- [ Electricity Crackling ]
- [ Grunting, Groaning ]
Now remember. We have
to leave nature just the way we found it.
Everything we pack in, we pack out.
- What if I have to do my business?
- Use this plastic bag.
Aw, how come bears can
crap in the woods and I can't?
[ Growling ]
Ah, we're so lucky to have this untouched
piece of paradise so close to Springfield.
- [ Droning ]
- [ Gasps ] Bees!
They sound angry and Africanized.
Okay, nobody panic.
There's plenty of spray for me.
[ Droning Continues ]
[ Engines Humming, Tires Screeching ]
That doesn't sound like bees.
Oh, my God.
It's a racetrack!
[ Gasps ]
The bird sanctuary!
- They ruined it!
- [ Homer] No, they didn't!
They just surrounded it with
something wonderful!
Like a raisin covered in chocolate.
Or a monkey in a cowboy suit.
[ All Gasp ]
See? Animals can
get used to anything.
[ Growling, Chittering ]
[ Squawks ]
Start your engines.
Show us your boobs.
[ Grunts ]
You better do what he says, Marge.
Cool. Way to adapt, little guy.
Why do jerks think everyone
wants to see their stupid name?
[ Tires Screeching ]
- [ Munching Loudly ]
- [ Screams ]
Sorry to break up
your picnic, folks.
- I'm two-time fast-car champ, Clay Babcock.
- You're on fire!
Yeah, I have won a lot of races.
It's all thanks to my crew, really.
[ Grunts ]
There it is.
Mr. Babcock, can I ride in your car?
Well, my ''A'' car was just incinerated,
but, uh, you can ride in my ''B'' car.
- [ Flame Roars ]
- I don't see why not.
Bart, these are the ''time trials''...
that determine the ''pole position.''
Shouldn't you be keeping
your hands on the wheel?
Oh, sure, if you want to drive
the ''traditional'' way.
- [ Grinding Metal ]
- Sorry.
Boy, these cars
are surprisingly roomy.
Yeah, we like to bring our families along
on the longer races.
If I get tired, I let my wife drive.
She's good.
Get your feet off the upholstery!
[ Engine Slows ]
I got some spare tickets
if you'd like to stick around for the race.
That's very sweet,
but we have a full day of hiking planned.
We can hike anytime.
- This is our chance to see cars driving.
- [ Sighs ]
[ Engines Roar]
Hi-diddly-ho,
pedal-to-the-metal-o-philes.
Flanders! Since when
do you like anything cool?
Well, I don't care for the speed...
but I can't get enough
of that safety gear-
Helmets, roll bars, caution flags.
I like the fresh air and looking
at the poor people in the infield.
[ Cheering ]
- [ Moaning ]
- Dang, Cletus.
Why'd you have to park
by my parents?
Now, honey, they's my parents too.
- ## [ Riff]
- [ Chuckles ]
- [ Announcer] Gentlemen, start your engines.
- [ Engines Roar]
- Daddy, can we move closer?
- Abso-not-ly, hot Roddy.
We're up here out of range of the crashes
and the drivers' cussin'.
- Move your damn butt.
- Bite me.
[ All Gasp ]
[ All Groan ]
[ All Gasp, Groan ]
Come on! Somebody crash!
Be patient, Son.
A watched car never crashes.
- [ Car Crashes ]
- Oh, I missed one!
- [ Engines Roar]
- Let's go! Let's go!
The dice!
The dice! The dice!
Eight seconds.
Great job, boys!
[ Engine Sputters, Backfires ]
Let's go. New tires.
Come on. Come on.
We're goin' as fast as we can, m-
Hey, who are you?
- Oh, how rude of me. My name is-
- [ Tires Squeal ]
My bad.
[ Announcer]
And now here's something for the guys.
Finally.
Let's hear it for...
Fan-demonium!
Hey, racing fans.
Who wants a free T-shirt?
- [ Cheering ]
- Me! Me!
- ;'Aqui! Aqui!
- I do! I do!
Wait. No, I don't.
Hmm. A Ford urinating on a Chevrolet.
- Don't you usually laugh at everything?
- Yes. Yes, I do.
- Come on! Right here! [ Screams ]
- [ Gasping ]
- I'm okay, folks.
- [ All Groan ]
I need a shirt!
Give me a shirt!
- Mommy has bosoms like that.
- [ Chuckles ] Yeah, I wish.
Neddie, I've had about
all I can take of Homer Simpson's torso.
- I'll get some hot dogs.
- No foot-longs.
I know.
They make you uncomfortable.
Well, I guess no one else
wants a T-shirt.
That's a damn lie, and you know it!
Gimme a shirt!
You heard him, girls.
Hey, T-shirt, T-shirt, T-shirt.
Fire!
Ooh, a bobby pin!
- [ Screams ]
- [ Thuds ]
[ Gasps ]
Maude?
[ Murmuring ]
Oh, my Lord, she's dead!
[ Groans ]
It's hard to believe
we're never going to see Maude again.
And poor Ned
didn't get a chance to say good-bye.
Well, from now on,
I'm never gonna let you leave the room...
without telling you how much I love you,
and how truly special-
This is eating up a lot of time.
Maybe just a pat on the butt.
- [ Light Smack ]
- Yeah, that works.
Now, Homie, you know, Ned and the boys
need us. And you know what that means.
- I know. No more being a jerk.
- That's right.
[ Sniffles ]
In many ways, Maude Flanders
was a supporting player in our lives.
She didn't grab our attention
with memorable catchphrases...
or comical accents.
- Aye.
- Yarr.
Oh, glavin!
Why, glavin?
But, whether you noticed her or not,
Maude was always there.
And we thought she always would be.
My friends, life is about change.
Just yesterday,
Apu was a lonely bachelor.
- [ Crying ]
- Yes, thank God those days are over.
And the Van Houtens
were enjoying a storybook marriage.
Yeah. Lots of storybooks
have witches.
- Shut up, Kirk!
- [ Quickly ] Sorry.
And now, the good people at Fan-demonium,
as part of a generous settlement...
will fire a 21 T-shirt salute.
[ Cocking Air Guns ]
##[ Bagpipe.' ''Amazing Grace'']
Finally.
Ned, my friend, please know
that the Kwik-E-Mart is there for you...
- 2 4 hours a day.
- Oh, thank you, Apu.
And I'm going to give you
all of Maude's frequent Squishy points.
The boys at headquarters
will not like it...
but I'm getting pretty sick of
them and their Bombay attitude!
That's enough there, Apu. Look, Ned,
I know we ain't hung out much...
what with your insane
fear of drinking...
and me being banned
from the church and all...
but, uh, but that Maude,
she was really somethin'.
Oh, wasn't she?
Thank you, Moe. I appreciate that.
Oh, I really mean it though. I mean, if it was
you that died, I would've been on her so fast!
- What are you saying?
- What? Nothing. She was hot.
- What? You can't take a compliment?
- Hot?
You monster!
[ Grunting ]
That's good. No.
Let it out. That's it. Let it out.
Send me to Maude. That's it.
Here I come, baby. Oh, yeah!
Bart, honey, I think you should
go play with Rod and Todd.
Oh, man. Why does everything bad
have to happen to me?
When I'm feeling low,
you know what always cheers me up?
- Is it love?
- Kindness?
Ooh, tough room.
Video games. What do you got?
Billy Graham's Bible Blaster?
Keep firing!
Convert the heathens!
## [ ''Bringing in the Sheaves'' ]
- Got him!
- No, you just winged him
and made him a Unitarian.
Look out, Bart! A gentle Baha'i.
- ## [ Fanfare ]
- All right! Full conversion!
Thanks, guys.
This really cheered me up.
[ Man ]
Second Coming! Reload! Reload!
- Can we play now?
- You are playing. We're a team.
[ Together]
Yea!
Now, if there's anything,
anything at all I can do to help out.
Quit hogging Flanders.
I want to comfort him.
[ Chuckles ] That's nice of you, Homer,
but I think I'll just go to bed.
Then I insist on walking you home.
Homer, this really isn't necessary.
Those feelings are normal, Ned.
They're part of the process.
Watch the sprinkler.
- Hey! That's my sprinkler.
- It's natural to feel that way.
But the sprinkler is gone.
It's time to let go.
I just bought that.
I know. I know.
It's never easy.
You want anything else?
Water? Chili fries?
How about some white noise?
[ Hisses ]
Oh, Homer. You don't... have to-
[ Snoring ]
Sleep tight, Neddie.
- [ Tapping On Glass ]
- [ Groans ] What is that?
Oh, you wanna rock fight, eh?
- [ Laughs ]
- No, Homer. I just need to talk.
Okay. Be right down.
[ Chuckles ]
I just keep replaying
the whole thing in my head.
I can't believe my last words to Maude
were, ''No foot-longs.''
Yep. It would have been a lot
better if you'd said...
''I love you'' or, ''You're special.''
You know, something sweet
instead of that hot dog crack.
If I'd only been a gentlemen
and got the hot dogs myself...
she'd still be here.
Now, now, now.
Don't beat yourself up.
I'm the one who drove her
out of her seat.
I'm the one who provoked
the lethal barrage ofT-shirts.
I'm the one who parked in the ambulance zone,
preventing any possible resuscitation.
Uh, but there's no point
in playing the blame game.
Ah, you're right.
I just gotta work through the grief.
There's not gonna be an easy answer.
Easy answer, eh?
Oh, yeah. That's it, baby.
That's the money shot.
Yeah, the camera loves you. Oh,you tease,you.
[ Chuckles ]
- Why are you taping Flanders, Dad?
- You'll see.
Do you even have a job anymore?
I think it's pretty obvious
that I don't!
Okay, I finished
the gardening sequence.
Okay, from here we star wipe to
a glamour shot of Flanders paying his bills.
Then we star wipe to Flanders
brushing his-
Dad, there are other wipes
besides star wipes.
Why eat hamburger
when you can have steak?
I'm taking my name off this thing.
- So, how you doin', Ned?
- Oh, it's been a hard couple of months...
but I feel like
I've turned a corner.
Well, that's all gonna change,
thanks to this tape!
- Tape?
- Now the audio needs some tweaking...
and there's some footage of Maggie
being born that I couldn't get rid of.
- Anyway, enjoy.
- [ Tape Loading ]
[ Homer's Voice ]
Single women of Springfield...
-your prayers have been ''Flanswered''.
- ## [ Fanfare ]
Ned Flanswered, that is.
- Is this a dating video?
- Shush!
What would you say about a man who
owns his own house and his own car?
That's Ned Flanders!
A man who's not afraid to cry.
- Hey, Ned!
- [ Sobs ]
- So that's why you maced me.
- [ Chuckles ] Yeah.
Ned does everything with class.
Whether he's punching in
his A.T.M. code...
or keeping clean in the shower.
- Homer!
- But don't take my word for it.
Listen to this testimonial.
Oh, I would date Ned in a second
if I was a woman or gay.
He looks like a cuddler,
that Ned. I-I like that.
I like to be held.
I like to be pampered.
step up to the best.
Ned Flanders, the man with the chest.
[ Panting, Grunting ]
Ew!
Now we'll just send this
to the dating service...
the chicks'll fall for you, and bam!
The healing begins.
Uh, Homer, you obviously
went to a lot of trouble, but dating?
It just feels way too soon.
[ Chuckles ]
That's great!
Chicks really dig sensitivity.
- Did you get that, Bart?
- Got it.
Beautiful.
And star wipe, and we're out.
Hmm.
Well, with triple word score,
that's 90.
[ Laughs ]
I guess my luck is starting to even out.
[ Sighs ]
I'm just a ''Q'' without a ''U''.
Mmm.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Laughs ]
Uh, hello? Mailman?
These are the women who
saw your videotape and are interested.
And feel free to root around
in the one-nighter bin.
- The bin is spoken for.
- Are you gonna call all those women?
No, the tapes will do just fine.
Thank you.
Homer, I'm having second thoughts.
This feels so disloyal to Maude.
Oh, wake up, Ned.
You think Maude isn't dating in heaven?
- You think she would?
- How could she not?
The place is full
of eligible bachelors.
John Wayne, Tupac Shakur,
Sherlock Holmes.
[ Chuckles ]
Sherlock Holmes is a character.
[ Chuckles ] He sure is.
[ Growls ]
Okay Here goes nothing
If you select me
you'll get a lot more than
a Wharton M.B.A. pulling in 200 K.
You'll get a woman
who's poised, articulate...
sophisticated, confident
and highly sexual.
Hang on.
I'm getting a fax.
Damn, I've just been indicted.
Looks like we're gonna have to reschedule.
How's your July?
- Well, I-
- Mine's terrible. Let's talk in August.
[ Sighs ]
Mmm. Dinner was delicious, Edna.
But I can't shake the feeling that you're
just using me to get Principal Skinner jealous.
Oh, please. I don't care
what Mr. ''Engaged to be Engaged'' thinks.
Hear that, Seymour?
- [ Skinner] Edna, this is childish.
- Fine, then hang up.
- I will hang up when he leaves.
- [ Sighs ]
Well, Diane, I've sure enjoyed chatting with you
about your problems with your mother.
Did you hear that, Foofie?
Sounds like somebody ''wuvs'' us.
- Yes, it does.
- [ Chuckles ] Yeah.
Well, maybe
I'll call you again sometime.
Ooh. Foofie doesn't like
the sound of that ''maybe.''
'Cause him's a commitment dog,
isn't him?
[ Gasping, Panting ]
So, how'd you do tonight, Romeo?
Well, I just can't relate
to the women of today, Homer.
Ah, it's probably me.
I'm about as exciting as a baked potato.
You're darn right you are! And you've got
lots of other great qualities too!
That's right, Ned. Those floozies we married
in Vegas were crazy about you.
What floozies?
What are you talking-
Marge! We're trying to help Ned!
Lord, I never question you...
but I've been wondering if your decision
to take Maude was, well, wrong.
U-Unless this is part of
your divine plan.
[ Clicks Tongue ]
Could you just give me some kind of sign?
Anything?
Aw, and after all that
church chocolate I bought...
which, by the way,
was gritty and had that white stuff on it!
Well, I've had it!
Daddy, get up.
You'll be late for church.
Well, you boys can go with the Simpsons.
I'm not going to church today.
- [ Gasps ]
- That's right.
And I may not go to church tomorrow.
[ Whimpering, Screaming ]
No, I'm not kiddin'!
I am gonna sit right here and miss church.
You just watch.
Sorry! Sorry! Sorry! Sorry!
Sorry! Sorry!
While our organist
is on a much-needed vacation...
we thought we'd try something new.
So get down and put your knees together
for the Christian rock stylings of...
- Kovenant!
- ## [ Rock ]
Hey, isn't that the bass player
from Satanica?
I think it is.
- ##[ Continues ]
- [ Gasps ] Electric guitars in church!
Oh, my gosh. Some dropouts must have
overpowered the reverend.
This is a love song about a dude I met
in a sleazy motel.
- [ Gasps ]
- A dude named God.
Oh.
# In a motel room
in Delacroix #
# I was drinking like
a Dartmouth boy #
-#And thinking 'bout the wrong turns that I took #
-[ Snoring ]
#Well, I woke up
on the puke-green floor #
#And opened up
a dresser drawer #
# Lookin' for a bottle
but instead, I found a book #
She's talking about the Bible.
- So? She's good-lookin'. Shut up.
- You shut up.
#A book about a man #
#A book about the dude
who lives above #
#A book about a man #
#Who drives a pickup full
of sweet, sweet love #
- ## [ Humming ]
- [ Clattering ]
# Now if you think
he doesn't care #
# Or maybe that he isn't there #
#It's not too late
to see how wrong you are #
# So when your soul
has gone astray #
#Just let God be your triple A #
# He'll tow you to salvation #
#And he'll overhaul your heart ##
Glad you made it, Ned.
I knew he would!
[ Grunts ]
I'll be right back, boys.
I've gotta go help that lady.
- Homer, you help too.
- I toileth not on ye Sabbath, woman!
- A pox on thee!
- [ Groans ]
- [ Grunts ]
[ Sighs ]
That was a lovely song.
- It really got to me.
- Been through some rough times yourself?
I-I recently lost my wife.
[ Gasps ] I'm real sorry to hear that.
We just lost our drummer...
to a Pentecostal ska band.
I know it's not the same-
No, I hear what you're saying.
It's always hard to replace someone.
Yeah. My name's RachelJordan.
If you feel like talking,
maybe we could grab a coffee?
Well, that- that sounds
real nice, Rachel...
but I'm, uh, I'm not quite-
I understand.
Listen. We're heading out on tour
with the Monsters of Christian Rock.
Maybe when we get back,
you and I could get together.
[ Chuckles ]
Maybe we can. My name's Ned Flanders.
And I'm here every week,
rain or shine.
[ Rachel ]
#It's a show about Ned #
#About him losin'his sweet wife #
#She landed on her head #
#But now it's time to get on
with his life ##
- [ Murmuring ]
- Shh!
www.tvsubtitles.net