Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Well, you're certainly doing your
job today, Mr. Sun.
Oh, rats.
And here we have
the world-famous Beatles...
...exactly as they looked performing
on The Ed Sullivan Show.
I hardly think it's fair to be
charged full price.
I'm up to my knees
in the original cast of M* A * S *H.
- Homer, my hat goes off to you.
- It's cool in here, boy.
For the rest of the summer,
we can live inside the refrigerator.
Homer, the fridge wasn't meant
to be used this way.
Although I must say,
it's certainly refreshing.
I got the idea when I noticed
the refrigerator was cold.
Won't this overload the motor?
Marge, can you set the oven to cold?
Ice cream! Ice cream!
I'm all out of ice cream! It's true,
you know. Ice cream! Ice cream!
Fresh out of ice cream!
Chili! Red-hot, Texas-style chili!
And we got ginger ale.
Boiling hot, Texas-style ginger ale!
Texas!
Face it, Bart. Our salvation isn't gonna
roll by on the back of some stupid truck.
I gotta replace that window.
- Pool-mobile?
Look, Lis, I snatched five
bathing suits. All Martin's.
Take your best shot.
I'm wearing 17 layers.
I brought this on myself.
Okay, little dudes, time's up.
Everybody out!
- Time's up?
- So long, Lis.
I'm gonna stow away underwater
and go where the pool goes.
Have a good life.
Sorry, Bart, dude. We gotta fill
this thing with Epsom salts...
...and jam over to the old folks' home.
- Oh, well. Same time tomorrow, Otto?
No way, man. One day of summer's
all we're budgeted for.
I guess it is kind of a tease.
Dad?
- Dad!
- Yes, Lisa?
Dad, as you know,
we've been swimming.
And we've developed a taste for it.
We both agree that getting
our own pool is the only way to go.
Now, before you respond,
understand that your refusal...
...would result in
months and months of:
- Can we have a pool, Dad?
I understand.
Let us celebrate our new arrangement
with the adding of chocolate to milk.
Over here we have the Hick Tub,
the Insta-Rust.
That's the Lightning Magnet.
- That's the Tinkler.
- The Tinkler.
I like the sound of that.
We'll take it.
Is it true we should wait at least
an hour after eating before we go in?
Look, question lady, this job is not
what I really do, okay? I play keyboards.
All right, everybody in the pool!
'Tis a fine barn,
but sure 'tis no pool, English.
- Is it a pool yet?
- Yes, Dad.
Who could that be?
Hello, Mrs. Bart.
Is your pool ready yet?
Bart, are all these children
friends of yours?
Friends and well-wishers, yes.
- Hey, Bart.
- Hi, Bart.
- Hey, my buddy, Bart.
- Hello, Mrs. Converdale.
People! People, it's time we all
discussed the pool-safety rules.
Jump, Bart, jump!
You got it.
Hey, Bart! Your epidermis is showing!
It is?
See, epidermis means your hair.
So technically it's true.
That's what makes it so funny.
Pardon me a moment.
Hey, Nelson. He's really hurt.
I think he broke his leg.
I said:
Get this kid a magazine, stat.
I'm sorry, that leg's gonna
have to come off.
Did I say leg?
I meant that wet bathing suit.
I'm afraid you'll need a cast
on that broken bone.
I'm gonna miss the whole summer.
Don't worry, boy. When you get a job
like me, you'll miss every summer.
Isn't it amazing, the same
day you got a pool...
...is the same day we realized
we liked you?
The timing worked out great,
don't you think?
- Hi.
- Hey, guys! Sign my cast?
Sign my cast? Guys?
- Milhouse!
- Hi, Bart.
Faithful Milhouse. You'll spend the long,
hot days by my side, won't you?
I think I lost my glasses in your pool.
I better go in and find them.
- But you're wearing your glasses.
- No, I'm not.
Oh, look. Bart's all alone.
Maybe I should keep him company,
at least for a little while.
- Hey, come watch this.
- Lisa! Hey, look.
Coming!
Well, it looks like it's just
you and me, Barty boy.
Great. I get to spend
the summer with my brain.
What fun can you have in a pool anyway
that you can't have in a bathtub...
...with a garbage bag taped
around your cast?
Traitors! Go on and have your pool!
I'm fine by myself right here.
You know, this isn't so bad.
I'll just spend the summer
getting better acquainted...
...with an old friend called television.
Hope you enjoyed that, kids, because
Krusty's out of here for the summer.
In the meantime, we'll be running...
...classic Krusty. Enjoy!
Good evening. Tonight my guest
is AFL-CIO Chairman George Meany...
...who will be discussing
collective-bargaining agreements.
- It's a pleasure to be here, Krusty.
- Let me be blunt.
Is there a labor crisis
in America today?
Well, that depends
what you mean by crisis.
There's nothing like
rising with the sun...
...for a quiet, peaceful dip
in your very own pool.
Lisa, the blob has got me!
Don't touch me or it'll get you too!
Dad, you have to put chlorine in
the water every day to keep it clean.
Chlorine, eh?
My face is on fire!
Oh, look. There's Bart. Wave to him.
Maybe we should spend
more time with Bart.
He's becoming isolated and weird.
"I swear I don't know where the
bombs are! Only the miners know that!"
"Maybe this will loosen your tongue. "
"No!"
- Bart?
- Don't turn on that light!
Sorry, I just came to see
how you were feeling.
- I'm fine, just fine.
- What are you writing here, a play?
- No.
- "Cast of characters:
Viceroy Fizzlebottom,
a hearty cherub of a man... "
Give me that! It's a work in progress.
So.
How do you like
being Miss Popularity?
Oh, well, you know, it ain't so great.
Bart, it's the best thing that ever
happened to me in my whole life!
Well, anyway, I brought you a present.
Look, it's the telescope I won...
...at the Optics Festival.
There was an Optics Festival
and I wasn't informed? You go now.
- But...
- Go!
What have we here?
"The Lighter Side of Hippies. "
They don't care whose toes
they step on.
This was a lovely idea, Homie.
Come here and kiss me.
Do not be alarmed.
Continue swimming naked.
Come on. Continue. Come on...
All right, Lou, open fire.
Wow, the universe is so boring.
I know. I'll use this to peer into
Springfield's seamy underbelly.
It turned out it was his evil twin.
Grace, come here. There's a
sinister-looking kid I want you to see.
I'm never gonna see anything interesting
with this stupid piece of junk.
That came from Flanders' house.
Oh, my God! What have I done?
I've killed her!
It can't be what it looks like.
This is Flanders we're talking about.
I'll just watch some TV.
Now, what you've been waiting for:
Another long raga by Ravi Shankar.
- Shankar.
Groovy, man.
This can't be what it looks like.
There's gotta be some other explanation.
I wish there was some other
explanation for this, but there isn't!
I'm a murderer! I'm a murderer!
Then that's not the real Ned Flanders.
I'm a mur-diddly-erdiler!
If that's not Flanders,
he's done his homework.
Daddy, where's Mommy?
We miss her.
Mommy had to go away.
She's with God now.
Can we go there too?
Soon enough.
He's gonna kill Rod and Todd too!
That's horrible...
...in principle.
Look, Lisa. I found this change
on the bottom of the pool.
- You can have it.
- Thanks, Nelson.
Somebody took my juice money.
Lisa, please join my family
for a weekend in the country.
There'll be hunting, charades...
...and ever so many delightful,
romantic misunderstandings.
- Lisa, Lisa!
- Watch me!
They're only using you
for your pool, you know.
Shut up, brain. I got friends now.
I don't need you anymore.
Yeah, I'd love to go to your house.
My plan has come to fruition.
Soon I'll be queen of summertime.
Oh, king. King!
Dude, buzz has it an even wussier kid
has an even better pool than this.
Hello? Hey, I'm stuck in here.
I gotta think of a way to get out.
Well, well, well.
Look who's come crawling back.
Listen, Ned Flanders murdered his wife!
But why? She's such a fox.
I mean, what's on Fox tonight?
Something ribald, no doubt.
I wish you'd stop spreading
bad rumors about people.
Remember how you got Grampa
tarred and feathered?
Sure. That was 20 minutes ago.
Gonna be in the tub for a while.
Bart, I'm really sorry
I've been ignoring you lately.
I got carried away with being popular.
But now that I'm unpopular again,
I want you to know I'm here for you.
You can start making it up
to me right now.
Flanders is leaving the house.
I want you to sneak in there...
...and bring me some evidence!
And something sweet.
Bart, I'm not gonna
break into somebody's house.
All right. You're right.
Let's just forget about that.
Here, let me read to you
from my play.
"Kippers for breakfast, Aunt Helga?
Is it Saint Swiven's Day already?
- 'Tis, replied Aunt Helga... "
- I'm going, I'm going.
A human head!
Of course.
Oh, no.
He's back. Flanders is back.
Lisa, get out of there!
No, Lisa, don't go upstairs.
You'll be trapped!
An ax! He's got an ax!
I'll save you, Lisa!
I'll save you by calling the police.
Hello, and welcome to the Springfield
Police Department Rescue Phone.
If you know the name of the felony
being committed, press one.
To choose from a list of felonies,
press two.
If you are being murdered
or calling from a rotary phone...
...please stay on the line.
You have selected regicide.
If you know the name of the king
or queen being murdered, press one.
I'll save you, cast or no cast!
Gotta save Lisa,
trash can or no trash can.
Oh, no. That sinister-looking kid
is coming to kill me.
Help! Help!
Oh, no. Oh, no.
It's time to put you away.
Put you away for good.
No!
What the gumdrops is going on here?
I came to stop you from murdering Lisa
like you murdered your wife!
Murdered?
Murdered? No, I've just been
in the country for a week.
But I distinctly heard you say
that Maude was with God.
That's right. I was at Bible camp. I was
learning how to be more judgmental.
But I saw the murder, and then I saw
you bury the corpse in the backyard!
All right, it's true! I am a murderer!
I over-watered Maude's
favorite ficus plant...
...I panicked, and then
I buried the remains.
I was hoping to replace it
before you got home.
But I heard a woman scream.
- Well, now, that I can't explain.
- We found it, chief.
Well, I guess that explains everything.
Not everything. There's still the little
matter of the whereabouts of your wife.
- I'm right here.
- Oh, I see.
Then everything is wrapped up
in a neat little package.
Really, I mean that.
Sorry if it sounded sarcastic.
More friends! More allies!
More, I say.
Hang those who talk of less.
There's a few inches over here.
My precious pool
and its lifestyle accouterments.
No!
- What a drag.
- I hear you.
The gentle caress of a summer breeze.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org