All right, everybody. Listen up.
Tuco Salamanca. For those of you
who were not with us this morning...
...we raided his headquarters.
Also his last-known address.
Even the little den of iniquity
he keeps for his meth-hag girlfriend.
We netted a bunch of his lieutenants.
The man himself smelled us coming.
So study the face. Study the file.
Get a big old raging hard-on...
...at the idea
of catching this piece of shit.
My apologies
to the H.R. department.
Grow tumescent with anticipation.
All right.
On the hit parade, 1998.
Reputed to have whacked
one "Dog" Paulson...
...back when our bandidos
were wresting the crank trade away...
...from the SoCal biker gangs.
Also, we're pretty sure
he knifed a Mexican national in '03.
And for my money, seeing
how he customarily deals with rivals...
...I'd say he is a prime suspect
in the disappearance...
...of our dearly missed Krazy-8.
Hats over your heart for that dirtball.
We hauled Tuco in
for questioning on that...
...but we couldn't make it stick.
Yeah, he runs a tight ship.
Smug bastard.
And even worse, EI Paso says he's
got some kind of cartel connection.
Yeah, yeah. I know. We all know
what's going on down there.
We sure don't want it going on
up here...
...which brings us to the good news.
We finally got some actual,
honest-to-God evidence.
This is one of Tuco's henchmen.
Street name: No-Doze.
Found him tucked in the junkyard
along with Tuco's own brother-in-law...
...a.k.a. Gonzo.
Gonzo, this rocket scientist,
was moving No-Doze's body-
Either hiding it there
or pulling it out. Not sure.
when he got his arm crushed
clean off.
Anyone wanna see the photos,
they're on my website. Hilarious.
Anyway. The upshot is...
...we got us a nice, big, juicy,
bloody fingerprint...
...which belongs to Señor Tuco.
Christmas came early
to the Schrader household.
That is, provided we find this guy.
So to all present, I ask you,
you wanna find this guy?
Yes.
-Yes.
What the hell was that? Jesus.
Wanna try that again?
Do you wanna find this guy?
-Yes!
Are we going to find this guy?
Louder, damn it!
-Yes!
Give me a "hell, yeah!"
-Hell, yeah!
Hell, yeah!
Hell, yeah. Hell, yeah, Hell, yeah.
They ain't gonna find him.
Guy is in México by now.
Appearances, Gomey.
It's all about appearances.
Listen, I gotta take
some personal time.
Now, in the middle of a manhunt?
Skyler called last night.
It's Walt. He's missing.
Just disappeared from the house,
and no one's heard from him since.
Damn. You don't think he...?
Holler if you need me.
All right. Thanks a lot, man.
Appreciate that.
This is the most recent photo.
We haven't taken many lately, so...
But that's what he looks like now.
Without the hair.
Hey, it's me.
Hey, Tim. Really appreciate you
sparing us your day off.
No worries. Happy to help.
Yeah, this is helpful. Good.
What about height and weight?
-Five eleven...
...most recently, about 170.
One sixty-five. That's what I weigh.
I guess he weighs a little less.
That's fine.
That's close enough. Good.
What about
other distinguishing features?
Tattoos or moles or scars?
Anything that might help us.
-Tattoos? No. Not really. No.
That's fine.
Is that the list of medications?
-Yes.
I wrote them all down.
And there's no drug interactions.
None that are listed.
I called his doctor, so, no.
Has he been depressed?
He's been withdrawn lately.
A little withdrawn.
Yeah.
Last night, he was agitated.
Agitated?
Yeah. When he came home last night,
he was agitated, upset.
Upset in general? Or upset
because of something particular?
When I asked him what was wrong,
he said:
"I don't know where to begin."
Then he just walked out of the room-
Out of the bathroom.
I was in the tub, taking a bath.
and when I came out
about 10 minutes later, he was gone.
Nothing else missing?
His keys, wallet, cell phone.
Just what was on him.
But-What about the phone call?
I'm looking into it.
What phone call?
-Walt's cell phone rang.
He pulled it out, looked at it,
and didn't answer it.
But then, a short time after,
he wandered out of the bathroom.
I mean...
...couldn't that be...
...important, right?
Anything else you can think of?
Anything else.
No. I called
the credit card providers...
...and there's no report
of any recent activity.
I-Let's see. I checked
with every hospital within 50 miles.
Every police station. Every morgue.
So, no, I really don't-
I don't have anything else.
I was actually hoping
that you had something else...
...being that you're the expert.
I'm sorry.
No worries.
I think this is good enough to start.
Gives us plenty to work on.
Mrs. White.
-Thank you.
Walter.
So that cell-phone call
she's talking about? I ran it.
And?
-Never happened.
No record of it.
Second cell phone.
-Yeah. I'm thinking.
I understand.
Out.
Get away from me!
Settle down, bitch.
You gonna shoot me, huh?
Shoot me in here!
I hope I bleed like a mother too!
That way, you have to clean it up!
It's your ride, retard.
I ain't gotta clean jack. Now, get out.
Get up.
Oh, my God.
Don't do this, Tuco.
No more posters?
Walter Jr.'s making more.
Thank you, Marie.
I don't think he'll hurt himself.
I mean, he just doesn't strike me
as the type.
He'll turn up.
Okay, the whole tiara thing...
...I just find it bewildering that...
-Marie.
...you didn't believe that-
Not now.
Empty your pockets.
Thought your name was
Heisenberg...
..."Walter Hartwell White."
Heisenberg is kind of a pseudonym.
You know, a business name.
Yeah.
I like doing business
with a family man.
There's always a lot of collateral.
Answer me one thing.
Can I trust you?
Yes. Yes, absolutely.
Sit down.
DEA...
...hit my place of business
this morning.
About a hundred cops
looking for me.
You two haven't been talking, right?
-No.
No.
Picked up my whole crew,
top to bottom.
Everybody except Gonzo.
That's weird, right?
I mean, don't you think
that that's weird?
It's weird. Yes.
Unusual.
Last two days,
I couldn't get Gonzo on the phone.
He's been acting all pouty
on account of No-Doze.
Explain to me.
How is it my fault that that little
bitch did not know his place?
I saw this coming.
I can see the future, you know?
It's this gift that I have
deep inside my head.
I knew last night they were gonna
come try and bust me.
Gonzo.
He went and snitched to the cops!
That lousy son of a bitch!
I trusted him like a brother!
I was good to him! I was good!
I see Gonzo, I'm gonna gut him,
I'm gonna skin him...
...and I'm gonna stuff his hide
for a heavy bag...
...and every time I hit him,
it's gonna be like a lesson to myself!
You never,
never trust the people that you love!
So you plan to ice Gonzo,
like, future tense?
What?
You're saying, Tuco...
You're saying that Gonzo...
...is currently operating
as a police informant...
...as far as you know?
I'm very sorry to hear that.
That's disappointing.
Yeah.
I'd waste him too, yo.
-Shut up.
Okay.
They're out there looking for me
right now.
They got ghetto birds
and black ops.
I need to get high.
I need to get good and high.
What's with this gak?
It smells like headcheese.
No, it's-It's killer.
Yeah, seriously.
So I was thinking last night.
I came up with this great idea.
Mexico?
-We'll disappear way out in the jungle.
We'll set you up in a superlab.
We'll do nothing but cook 24/7.
And no Federales
are gonna mess with us...
...because I got my people there.
Connections.
We're going to make beaucoup bucks,
Heisenberg, huh?
Tuco, I...
I have a wife and family.
So what? You'll get another one.
I don't want you to take
this the wrong way, but I can't just...
...uproot my life like that.
Yeah, man. I mean, me neither.
Who's talking to you?
You need me, man...
...because I cooked that scante
in your hands.
Yeah.
I'll tell you something, yo.
You never tried nothing like it.
Stink or no stink...
...one bump,
you'll be flying high for days.
It's a new product him
and I've been working up.
Careful when you hit it.
It kicks like a 12 gauge
when it comes on.
It's got a secret ingredient.
What secret ingredient?
Chilli powder.
I hate chilli powder.
This blue magic, this is money.
You keep cooking this, Heisenberg.
We're gonna rewrite history
with this.
All right. Time to clean the menudo
out from between your ears.
No, no, no. No, I need him, Tuco.
I need him very, very badly.
He's my partner.
And if he doesn't go, I don't go.
I'll tell you this. My cousins
are driving up here right now...
...to smuggle us back,
and they're gonna be here by sunset...
...and you're gonna be on that truck,
or you're gonna be dead!
And you...
You better hope they got room
in the trunk.
Where are you going?
-Louis is taking me to the train station.
We'll put these up.
No, no, honey. No, I'll do it.
-He wants to help, let him help.
I mean, how long has it been
since you've slept?
Yeah, she's right, Sky.
Why don't you lay down a while?
For chrissake,
you got a bun in the oven.
I got my cell if you need me.
Okay?
-Okay.
Bye, sweetie. I'll see you later.
-All right. Bye.
Actually, I think the very fact
they haven't found him yet...
...bodes well.
Well, I mean, if he-You know.
Somebody would've
smelled something by now.
There's got to be something.
Some detail
that we haven't picked up on.
What about the second cell phone?
-Jesus.
What? We can't just ignore
a potential clue, Hank.
Okay. What are you talking about?
The call you said Walt got
before he disappeared?
There's no record of it
with the phone company.
No incoming,
no dropped calls, nothing.
But his phone rang. I heard it.
All right. Well, then if that's the case,
he must have a second phone.
Why? What sense would there be
in that?
Yeah. All right. Okay.
I'm not here to argue with you.
No, Hank. You can't just bring up
secret cell phone and then drop it.
What does it mean?
I don't know, Sky.
What do you want me to say?
It means Walt has a secret.
Everyone's got one from somebody,
big or little.
Okay. Everyone. Okay.
-Skyler, come on.
He kept cancer from you for weeks.
Okay, then, let's assume
there's a second cell phone.
So what?
What, is he having an affair?
Walt? Please.
What about the marijuana?
-He's not on pot anymore.
Says who? Him?
Chemotherapy
and marijuana go together...
...like apple pie and Chevrolet.
Maybe he's addicted to the pot...
...and he owes his drug dealer
a lot of money.
Marie, you don't get hooked on pot
like that.
How do you know? You didn't even
know he had a second cell phone.
Hank, you have to question
this drug-dealer person.
He may know something.
Well, I'm telling you,
we're grasping at straws here.
Then grasp.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Hi, I'm looking for Jesse.
He around?
No. I'm afraid not.
Why?
-I'm sorry. Hank Schrader.
I'm actually hoping to talk to Jesse
about my brother-in-law, Walter White.
He taught your son chemistry
in high school.
Oh, Mr. White.
Yes, I remember him.
That was a long time ago.
-Yes, ma'am.
It's my understanding that he
and Jesse, they've stayed in touch.
Really?
-Yeah.
Mr. White must've seen
some potential in Jesse.
He really tried to motivate him.
He was one of the few teachers
who cared.
Yeah, Walt's that way.
He's a good man.
I'm so sorry
to hear about his illness.
Please pass along our best wishes.
I certainly will,
as soon as he turns up.
He's missing, actually.
Just kind of walked off, or...
Anyway, which is why
I'm going around...
...trying to think of anyone
who knows him, even slightly.
That's terrible.
Anything we can do to help.
Well, if you could put me in touch
with your son...
Like I said,
we're kind of desperate for leads.
Jesse's not answering either number,
and no one seems to be at his house.
And why do you think my son
and Mr. White would be in touch?
I don't necessarily. I just-
Are you with the police?
-No, ma'am. Not at all.
I'm with
the Drug Enforcement Administration.
Oh, my God.
Is my son in trouble?
I have absolutely no reason
to think that, no.
Do I need to get a lawyer?
You know, you don't seem
very forthright about this...
...coming here and asking questions
about my son and-
Mrs. Pinkman,
I'm not here on official capacity.
I do not care what your son may
or may not have done wrong.
I just wanna find my brother-in-law.
His wife is worried sick,
and she's got a baby on the way.
I'm sorry. I would like to help you...
...but I have not seen my son
in over a month.
I don't expect to see him
anytime soon.
Well, thanks for your time.
If you could tell me one more thing.
Is Jesse still driving the '89 Chevy
Monte Carlo, as far as you know?
If he had spent half as much time
and money on his education...
...as he has
on that ridiculous bouncing car...
Low rider, huh?
Gomey, hey.
No, nothing yet. Hey, listen,
do me a solid and check out...
...a '89 Chevy Monte Carlo...
...registered to a one
Jesse Pinkman.
Specifically, I wanna know
if the car's got a LoJack.
It's one of those jack-off low riders,
so I'm betting there is.
If so, can you go ahead
and get me a fix on it? Thanks, buddy.
Chilli powder.
Did I not already tell you
how moronic that was?
Whatever, man.
At least I tried something.
Hey, it almost worked too.
How's about
you leaving my gun, huh?
First you boost it,
then you leave it in your house.
My gun.
How was I supposed to know you were
chauffeuring Tuco to my doorstep?
Well, at least he wants you alive.
Hey, I don't get it.
If Tuco didn't kill Gonzo,
then who did?
I don't know.
Does it really matter?
If he finds out that Gonzo is dead
and not a police informant...
...who does he
automatically blame?
Us.
We need a plan.
Think, think.
-Let's just bum-rush him, man.
You crack him over
the head with something...
...and I'll go for his gun.
Crack him over the head
with something?
Hey, you got the C-bomb, man,
all right?
You're as good
as checked out already.
Okay? You should be, like, all
sacrificial, jumping on a grenade, yo.
Just...
Oh, so my life
is not the priority here...
...because I'm gonna be
dead soon anyway.
That's your point?
Yeah.
We gotta get him to take this.
Well, he don't much like
the taste of chilli P.
That much has been established.
So unless you can convince him
to booty bump...
Eat. We got a long ride ahead of us.
Go on, sit. You're looking
a little weak, Heisenberg.
I don't want you to go belly up
before we get there.
Take it easy, Tio.
I will feed you.
I eat first. That's the deal.
What?
I get it, I get it, I get it.
Oh, you greedy old bastard.
I tell you, Heisenberg.
Old people.
You feed them, huh?
You put them in a really nice crib
in the country...
...and yet they gotta steal
the food off your plate.
You better eat every bite of that.
What did you do that for?
God!
Hey, look. Look.
There's nothing left.
What? What do you want?
No.
Don't even tell me
that you're hungry.
Don't go there.
Are you mad-dogging them, Tio?
What, you don't like them?
One ding.
That means yes. Tio don't like you.
Why don't you like them, Tio?
You don't trust them?
-Why don't you trust them, Tio?
-Tuco, come on. He's...
There clearly some dementia.
He's not lucid.
Did they do something to you, Tio?
Something that you don't like?
What did they do to you?
What did you do to my tio?
Nothing. Nothing.
-Bullshit! My tio does not lie!
-I don't know. I swear. I don't know.
No, I-Maybe it was-I did change
the channel on his TV, but...
Yeah, that's it.
While you were cooking...
...he was watching
one of those telenovels...
...with all those ripe honeys on it.
He was really into it.
I told you
not to change the channel.
You know, dude needs his eye candy.
That's it.
Is that it, Tio?
Did they change your mamitas?
What are you telling me, Tio?
Are they punking me?
Hey. No.
No, man. No.
Come here!
-No.
No, no, Tuco.
Tuco, no. Tuco.
Shut up!
No. Please, no. God. Please, no.
No, God. I don't wanna die.
Tell me what you did, Walter!
Jesus, I don't wanna die.
No!
-Tell me what you did!
We tried to poison you.
We tried to poison you...
...because you're an insane,
degenerate piece of filth...
...and you deserve to die.
Who's the bitch now?
Let him bleed.
The keys.
Tuco.
Oh, my God.
The cousins?
What the hell is going on?
Jesse Pinkman.
You're a hard man to find.
Oh, shit.
Easy.
Oh, my God.
Oh, God. Hank.
Who?
-Hank.
What?
Oh, my God.
-What?
-Stay. What are you doing?